// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x2tagDarklands_elred_A1=You want to go to Asgard? Hah. Good luck with that!If it was easy, I would be on my way there myself.
x2tagDarklands_elred_B1=Wait, human. Forgive me - I had not introduced myself. I am Eldred, master tinkerer. What these brothers forge, I imbue with purpose!Since you seem to be serious about that Asgard business... if you really get there, you might do me a favor. You see, we Dvergr are no longer quite welcome there. But we were once, and built many a wonderful thing for the Aesir.My masterpiece was a statue. But not just any statue, but one built around a unique power core forged from a dozen Golem Hearts. It was not like the others. A gift to Tyr himself!He refused to give it back to me. Well, probably because it was a gift. But if you happen to find it and, well, smash it... could you retrieve its core for me?
x2tagDarklands_elred_B7=Ah, the things I could do with that power core today!
x2tagDarklands_elred_C1=You really found the power core? Excellent! Human, you have my thanks.
x2tagDarklands_elred_C7=Shame about the statue, but that core will be of great use in my next invention!
x2tagAsgard_ida_A1=Help me, stranger! A venomous snake struck me! I wanted to get to the Well of Urd, to cleanse the poison with its purifying white water... but I am afraid I am too ill already.Could you go there and fill this vial? Just straight ahead through these roots. It should be rather safe.
x2tagAsgard_ida_A2=Please stranger. You need to go deeper into the cave... I will wait here and watch.
x2tagAsgard_ida_A7=Hnngh.... Ooh, the pain!
x2tagAsgard_ida_B1=You... you got it? How!? The Nidhoggr should have ripped you to shreds! {^n}{^n}This must be a bad joke. I'm out of here!
x2tagAsgard_ida_B7=Master Loki will be furious!
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_A1=Greetings! Someone like yourself, out here with all that gear equipped, must be one eager to prove themselves, right? {^n}{^n}See, we have traveled these roads for a long time, moving our goods and conducting our business. And the forest was always a place to avoid, but lately even the area around it seems to have grown more dangerous. Last night, on the road east of here, we were attacked by a whole gang of spiders coming out of the trees, gathered around an enormous mother! I barely escaped with my life... {^n}{^n}If you are looking for a glorious kill, that abomination would be it!
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_A2=The creatures get more bold by the day. Maybe they breed too much, or those witches imbue them with magic. And I fear I soon won't be able to travel this area.
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_A7=I do not know in which hole that creature hides, of course. As said, we met it east of here. You may first have to get its attention by killing some of its spawn...
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_B1=You have slayed the creatures you say? What about the giant monstrosity that attacked me last night, did you encounter it? Unless the mother is annihilated, I'm afraid these routes won't be safe.
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_C1=The creature is vanquished?! Stupendous! You are a true hero! {^n}{^n}Here, have this for free!
x2tagJotunheim_valdrarum_C7=Thanks to you our business is safer again. May you be prosperous in your future endeavours, my friend.
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_A1=A fellow explorer, are you? I have been searching these dire lands for a particular sort of gems rumored to be found here, but with all these giants roaming about it's no easy task for one of my stature. Maybe you could help me look a bit? I would compensate you of course!
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_A2=Since they are gemstones, I would assume they can be found in the caves around this area. But if there is any truth to that is another thing...
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_A7=Come back to me when you've found something!
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_B1=You found some gems?! Amazing! Now, if you could bring a few more we could come to an agreement.
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_B7=It is great - the gems actually exist! But I am sure you can get more than just those few, right?
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_C1=You found them! That will be enough gems! Eternal love, here I come!
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_C7=The stones, finally mine! Hee hee hee...
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_D1=This is not one of the stones I'm after, but... wait a minute... what? Could it be? I thought I'd never see the day - The Stone of Bergelmir! Finally mine! Ahahaa!!! {^n}{^n}Ahemhm... Alright, we're done here. Take this for your troubles.
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_D2=Did the Rimturs not chase you for this? Well, I'd better go...
x2tagJotunheim_allvis_D7=Scurry along now, nothing more to see here...
x2tagMuspelheim_svarti_A1=Hmm, you are a curious one. On your way to attack the fortress - seriously!? {^n}{^n}Well, I might have some information that helps if you want to weaken Surtr. These fields are overseen by two mighty Eldjötnar called the Lords of Ember. Wholly unpleasant fellows who are way too much into loyalty. If you strike at them first, Surtr's troops will be unorganized for a while.
x2tagMuspelheim_svarti_A7=You will find them patrolling further inland. Have fun trying, adventurer.
x2tagMuspelheim_svarti_B1=Ah, one of the lords is no more? Great! A promising outset indeed. Well, but you don't want to leave the job half finished, do you? {^n}{^n}Get the second one, and I will tell you something else.
x2tagMuspelheim_svarti_C1=Ahaha! Well done, my tenacious friend! The destruction of the Ember Lords was long overdue! {^n}{^n}Next on your path, there is in fact a third lord, if you will. A lady - Surtr's mistress. Her domain is the Fire Shrine in the western cliff. You will have to go in there if you are looking for a way into the fortress.
x2tagMuspelheim_svarti_C7=My deference and gratitude. You have been most useful.
