// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagSq01_Title=The Lost Wanderer
x3tagSq01_Anathe=Anathe ~ Gadirian Resident
x3tagSq01_Hyram=Hyram ~ Lost Wanderer
x3tagSq01_HyramSafe=Hyram ~ Returned Wanderer
x3tagSq01_Desc_A=Anathe, a local resident of Gadir is missing her friend Hyram. She mentioned that he likes to wander the nearby lands, but have been missing for an unusually long time. Find the lost friend.
x3tagSq01_Desc_B=Anathe, a local resident of Gadir is missing her friend Hyram. She mentioned that he likes to wander the nearby lands, but have been missing for an unusually long time. You found and rescued Hyram from some ill-minded creatures. Return to Anathe.
x3tagSq01_Desc_C=You helped Anathe, a local resident of Gadir, by finding her missing friend Hyram. He got lost exploring a cave north-east of Gadir full of monsters. Knowing that her friend is safe and sound thanks to you, Anathe was overjoyed.
x3tagSq02_Title=Nightly Guests
x3tagSq02_Jibran=Jibran ~ Merchant Sailor
x3tagSq02_Hookah=Shisha
x3tagSq02_HookahDesc=A water pipe. It is covered in sticky slime but seems to be intact otherwise.
x3tagSq02_Desc_A=You met a sailing merchant named Jibran who claims to have been set upon by strange creatures in the dead of night. Fleeing his temporary encampment in a nearby cave, Jibran didn’t have time to grab his beloved shisha and would like you to find it.
x3tagSq02_Desc_B=You met a sailing merchant named Jibran who claims to have been set upon by strange creatures in the dead of night. Fleeing his temporary encampment in a nearby cave, Jibran didn’t have time to grab his beloved shisha and would like you to find it. After searching through the cave where he lost it, you found theshisha! Bring it back to Jibran.
x3tagSq02_Desc_C=You found a finely crafted hookah in a cave, who might it belong to?
x3tagSq02_Desc_D=You met a sailing merchant named Jibran who claims to have been set upon by strange creatures in the dead of night. Fleeing his temporary encampment in a nearby cave, Jibran didn’t have time to grab his beloved shisha. You went inside the cave and found the shisha. Jibran was relived to get it back from the strange creatures.
x3tagSq03_Title=Of Goats and Bards
x3tagSq03_Abdhamon=Abdhamon ~ Local Herder
x3tagSq03_Baaliahon=Baaliahon ~ Local Musician
x3tagSq03_Goat=Melita ~ The Best Goat
x3tagSq03_Satyrhead=Aegipan Head
x3tagSq03_SatyrheadDesc=A rather large severed head. What a trophy!
x3tagSq03_Arganoil=Bottle of Argan Oil
x3tagSq03_ArganoilDesc=This bottle contains Argan Oil.
x3tagSq03_Desc_A=Abdhamon the goat herder has lost his best goat and he wants it back. He suspects the local musician, Baaliahon, who lives up in the mountains has taken it…
x3tagSq03_Desc_B=Abdhamon the goat herder has lost his best goat and he wants it back. You find the goat happily eating grass beside Baaliahon. However, Baaliahon insists that the goat belongs to him. You find that he is willing to trade the goat for the head of an Aegipan. Ideally from the nearby Aegipan camp further up the trail.
x3tagSq03_Desc_C=Abdhamon the goat herder has lost his best goat and he wants it back. You find the goat happily eating grass beside Baaliahon. However, Baaliahon insists that the goat belongs to him. You find that he is willing to trade the goat for the head of an Aegipan. Bring back the head to Baaliahon.
x3tagSq03_Desc_D=Baaliahon was happy to have an Aegipan’s head for whatever twisted ritual he had planned, and Abdhamon was pleased to have his beloved goat back. Seems everything turned out well in the end.
x3tagSq04_Title=The Letter
x3tagSq04_Okha=Okha ~ Bedouin
x3tagSq04_Sheyma=Sheyma ~ Bedouin
x3tagSq04_Letter=Letter
x3tagSq04_LetterDesc=A letter from Okha to Sheyma.
x3tagSq04_Desc_A=A bedouin named Okha wants you to deliver a letter to his sweetheart Sheyma who lives further up in the mountains.
x3tagSq04_Desc_B=A bedouin named Okha wanted you to deliver a letter to his sweetheart Sheyma who lives further up in the mountains. You delivered the letter to Sheyma who promptly sets out to visit Okha.
x3tagAtlas_sheyma_X1=...
x3tagSq05_Title=The Secret Depot
x3tagSq05_Baka=Baka ~ Local Merchant
x3tagSq05_Stonebutton=Suspicious Stone
x3tagSq05_Desc_A=A spice trader named Baka asked for your help in clearing out a group of basilisks that has invaded his secret storeroom, enticed by the spices contained within. Hidden in a mountain cave, the room can be accessed by pushing a stone in the nearby wall.
x3tagSq05_Desc_B=A spice trader named Baka asked for your help in clearing out a group of basilisks that has invaded his secret storeroom, enticed by the spices contained within. You cleared Baka’s storeroom of the basilisks, with most of the spices still intact. Return to Baka for your reward.
x3tagSq05_Desc_C=A spice trader named Baka asked for your help in clearing out a group of basilisks that has invaded his secret storeroom, enticed by the spices contained within. Having taken care of the basilisks, you were rewarded by Baka who can now return to selling spices.
x3tagSq06_Title=The Foraging Mission
x3tagSq06_Patrobas=Patrobas ~ Ships' Cook
x3tagSq06_Strangetree=Weird Tree
x3tagSq06_Strangefruit=Weird Fruit
x3tagSq06_StrangefruitDesc=Altough a bit icky, this fruit seems to be edible.
x3tagSq06_Desc_A=Afraid that supplies are running low, Patrobas the ship's cook, has sent you on a foraging mission into the jungle to find something edible for the journey back home.
x3tagSq06_Desc_B=Afraid that supplies are running low, Patrobas the ships’ cook has sent you on a foraging mission into the jungle to find something edible for the journey back home. You found a weird fruit in the jungle that seems edible. Bring it back to Patrobas at the beach landing.
x3tagSq06_Desc_C=Afraid that supplies are running low, Patrobas sent you on a foraging mission into the jungle to find something edible for the journey back home. You brought Patrobas a weird fruit and he sent out a foraging party to gather some more. Hopefully they can find enough to fill the ship stores again.
x3tagSq07_Title=The Mysterious Artifacts
x3tagSq07_Auriana=Auriana ~ Atlantean Spirit
x3tagSq07_Artifact01=Impossible Puzzlebox
x3tagSq07_Artifact01Desc=The seemingly impossible curvatures of this piece brings forth images of cyclopean dimensions.
x3tagSq07_Artifact02=Suggestive Sculpture
x3tagSq07_Artifact02Desc=Exquisite yet raw, you feel hot flashes just looking at this... thing.
x3tagSq07_Artifact03=Clockwork Contraption
x3tagSq07_Artifact03Desc=As countless gears and cogs tick away, you come to realize that you will never understand what this is.
x3tagSq07_Desc_A=Auriana, a spirit of Atlantis, asked for your help in bringing back three invaluable artifacts that were swept away in the destruction and subsequent flooding of the city. They’re all probably swept up on foreign shores, some perhaps even worshipped as sacred objects by ‘primitive’ civilizations.
x3tagSq07_Desc_B=Auriana, a spirit of Atlantis, asked for your help in bringing back three invaluable artifacts that were swept away in the destruction and subsequent flooding of the city. You’ve found three strange objects, which probably are the artifacts Auriana spoke of... You should return with them to her.
x3tagSq07_Desc_C=Auriana, a spirit of Atlantis, asked for your help in bringing back invaluable artifacts that were swept away in the destruction and subsequent flooding of the city. You found several and Auriana was grateful for the repatriation of the artifacts and can finally be at peace knowing they are safe again.
x3tagSq07_Desc_D=You have found three strange artifacts, their purpose unknown but the advanced craftwork and quality feels like they could be atlantean in origin. Maybe someone there knows more?
x3tagSq08_Title=The Exterminator
x3tagSq08_Airon=Airon ~ Atlantean Spirit
x3tagSq08_Desc_A=Airon, a very well-spoken former Atlantean, wants you to rid his demesne of two Tritone heroes.
x3tagSq08_Desc_B=Airon, a very well-spoken former Atlantean, wants you to rid his demesne of two Tritone heroes. You have already found and vanquished one of them.
x3tagSq08_Desc_C=Airon, a very well-spoken former Atlantean, wants you to rid his demesne of two Tritone heroes. Both the heroes are vanquished, return to Airon.
x3tagSq08_Desc_D=Airon, a very well-spoken former Atlantean, wanted you to rid his demesne of two Tritone heroes. With both heroes dead, Airon has finally found a sense of closure and can rest easy.
x3tagSq08_MonsterA=Zerphare ~ King Triton Officer
x3tagSq08_MonsterB=Moa'lin ~ King Triton High Judicator
x3tagSq09_Title=A Score to Settle
x3tagSq09_Desc_A=A group of Tritones still loyal to Poseidon, led by the Priestess Okyroe, has asked you to find and kill a Serpentoid High Priest, Ssaquath, who betrayed them long ago.
x3tagSq09_Desc_B=A group of Tritones still loyal to Poseidon, led by the Priestess Okyroe, has asked you to find and kill a Serpentoid High Priest, Ssaquath, who betrayed them long ago. You have killed the Ssaquath. Return to Okyroe for your reward.
x3tagSq09_Desc_C=Priestess Okyroe is grateful for your help to finally avenge the betrayal of High Priest Ssaquath against her group and has promised to help you on your way.
x3tagSq09_Okyroe=Okyroe ~ Tritones Priestess
x3tagSq09_Ssaquath=Ssaquath ~ High Priest
x3tagSq09_Guard=Tritones ~ Resistance Fighter
x3tagSq10_Title=Ancient Craft
x3tagSq10_Meidias=Meidias ~ Atlantean Spirit
x3tagSq10_Material01=Artisan's Anvil
x3tagSq10_Material01Desc=An anvil used for artistic metalworking.
x3tagSq10_Material02=Copper Coil
x3tagSq10_Material02Desc=A dense coil of fine wire that had been sheltered from corrosion.
x3tagSq10_Material03=Rod of Ferrophilum
x3tagSq10_Material03Desc=A short rod made of dark metal. A magical force seems to make it move towards some of your items.
x3tagSq10_Material04=Spare Parts
x3tagSq10_Material04Desc=A set of intricate metal parts, no doubt used by the Atlantean inventors.
x3tagSq10_Desc_A=Meidias, a former craftswoman of Atlantis, is willing to show you some of her crafting skills if you find the required ingredients: An anvil, a copper coil, a rod of ferrophilum, and some spare parts like gears and wires. All of them can be found in Atlantis.
x3tagSq10_Desc_B=Meidias, a former craftswoman of Atlantis, is willing to show you some of her crafting skills if you find the required ingredients. You’ve gathered all the necessary ingredients, so return to Meidias.
x3tagSq10_Desc_C=Meidias, a former craftswoman of Atlantis, was willing to teach you some of her crafting skills if you found the required ingredients which you did. Meidias showed you how to craft a powerful attachment for your gear.
x3tagSq10_Item_CraftedNecklace=Necklace of Atlantis
x3tagSq10_Item_CraftedNecklaceDesc=The completed necklace.
x3tagSq10Recipe=Arcane Formula ~ Atlantean Artifice
x3tagSq10Recipe_e=Arcane Formula ~ Epic Atlantean Artifice
x3tagSq10Recipe_l=Arcane Formula ~ Legendary Atlantean Artifice
x3tagSq10RecipeDesc=Recipe for a special Atlantean gear improvement.
x3tagSq11_Title=Friends Like These
x3tagSq11_Desc_A=A somewhat friendly but perhaps a bit unstable Serpentoid, Ni'sr, has asked you to collect "contracts" of two Potamoi leaders located further inland. This probably means you need to kill them.
x3tagSq11_Desc_B=A somewhat friendly but perhaps a bit unstable Serpentoid, Ni'sr, has asked you to collect "contracts" of two Potamoi leaders located further inland. You have killed one of the Potamoi Leaders so one "contract" left.
x3tagSq11_Desc_C=A somewhat friendly but perhaps a bit unstable Serpentoid, Ni'sr, has asked you to collect "contracts" of two Potamoi leaders located further inland. You have killed both Potamoi Leaders. Return to Ni'sr for your reward...
x3tagSq11_Desc_D=Ni'sr seems gleefully happy and grateful that you collected his "contracts" on the Potamoi Leaders. A mad glint in his eyes makes you wonder who is the next "contract"...
x3tagSq11_Nisr=Ni'sr ~ Serpentoid Agent
x3tagSq11_Vadas=Vadas ~ Potamoi Leader
x3tagSq11_Nildis=Nildis ~  Potamoi Leader  
