// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagGadir_senechal_A1=Greetings Hero, your reputation precedes you... My Master would like to extend an invitation to you... To test your mettle in the horrible *Pits of Tartarus*, to face the indomitable *Hordes of Eternity*! A challenge worthy of the Slayer of Typhon! {^n}{^n}Sounds interesting? Of course there will be *rewards* in it for you, should you choose to accept... {^n}{^n}When you are ready, please step into this portal. If you want to know more specifics, we can talk some more.
x3tagGadir_senechal_A7=Aah, your thirst for knowledge matches your thirst for blood! Very well, I will tell you how my Master's challenge works. {^n}{^n}Upon entering Tartarus, you will face a host of varying creatures, gathered from all over the known world. You will fight these hordes across a multitude of devious battlefields, specifically created for this little game. {^n}{^n}If you make it far enough my Master himself will face you in single combat! Needless to say you won't have a chance to beat him... But to keep things interesting a *substantial* reward would be bestowed upon you if you did. {^n}{^n}That is not all, however! True to the genius of my Master, he has decreed that this challenge shall be eternal; a never-ending gauntlet of foes ready to take you on! But *beware*, your opponents will grow stronger and stronger until you find yourself attempting an impossible task... {^n}{^n}You have been warned, Hero. Now, it is time to fulfill your destiny and take on the *Challenge of Tartarus*!
x3tagTartarus_tartarus_A1=Welcome, mortal, to Tartarus, realm of eternal punishment! You are brave indeed to have accepted my challenge, I look forward to seeing you struggle against my hordes! Hehehe! {^n}{^n}Enough talk! Step forward into the arena to begin! I will be waiting for you, if you make it far enough... Hahahaha!
