// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagRegionName01=Summer Palace
x4tagRegionName02=Crimson Shore
x4tagRegionName03=Hinterland Marshes
x4tagRegionName04=Haunted Grove
x4tagRegionName05=Abandoned Village
x4tagRegionName06=Riverside
x4tagRegionName07=Upper Wilds
x4tagRegionName08=Haunted Shipwreck
x4tagRegionName09=Flooded Caves
x4tagRegionName10=Lai Farmlands 
x4tagRegionName11=Village of Lai
x4tagRegionName12=Lai Countryside
x4tagRegionName13=Forgotten Tower
x4tagRegionName14=Silk Road Approach
x4tagRegionName15=Silk Road Trading Post
x4tagRegionName16=The Great Wall
x4tagRegionName17=Lakeside Fields
x4tagRegionName18=Ruined Fort
x4tagRegionName19=Hinterlands
x4tagRegionName20=The Crater
x4tagRegionName21=Infested Plains
x4tagRegionName22=Shrine of the Stars
x4tagRegionName23=Imperial Overlook
x4tagRegionName24=Xiao Farmlands
x4tagRegionName25=Fiery Fissure
x4tagRegionName26=Village of Xiao
x4tagRegionName27=Broken Bridge
x4tagRegionName28=Kunlun Approach
x4tagRegionName29=Ruined Fields
x4tagRegionName30=Old Mountain Sanctum
x4tagRegionName31=Valley of the Failed
x4tagRegionName32=Glacial Approach
x4tagRegionName33=Kunlun Monastery
x4tagRegionName34=Slaver Camp
x4tagRegionName35=Emperor's Road
x4tagRegionName36=Pingyang Outskirts
x4tagRegionName37=Trade Quarter
x4tagRegionName38=Palace Gardens
x4tagRegionName39=Palace Exterior
x4tagRegionName40=Mausoleum
x4tagRegionName41=Pingyang Highlands
x4tagRegionName42=Lower Ascent
x4tagRegionName43=Upper Ascent
x4tagRegionName44=The Eight Pillars
x4tagRegionName45=Heavenly Gardens
x4tagRegionName46=Jade Court
x4tagRegionName47=Crystalline Corridors
x4tagRegionName48=Frigid Pools
x4tagRegionName49=Antechamber
x4tagRegionName50=Halls of Sihai Longwang
x4tagRegionName51=Chamber Of The Four Seas
x4tagRegionName52=Asyut Encampment
x4tagRegionName53=Temple Region
x4tagRegionName54=Prosoro's Path
x4tagRegionName55=Necropolis Outskirts
x4tagRegionName56=Abydos Necropolis
x4tagRegionName57=Abydos Barrens
x4tagRegionName58=Nile Valley
x4tagRegionName59=Thebes
x4tagRegionName60=Forsaken Wastes
x4tagRegionName61=Dragon Cavern
x4tagRegionName62= 
x4tagRegionName69=Elemental Cave: Wood
x4tagRegionName70=Evil Sage Cave
x4tagRegionName71=Elemental Cave: Metal
x4tagRegionName72=Roadside Tomb
x4tagRegionName73=Feral Cave
x4tagRegionName74=Tomb of Xu Chu
x4tagRegionName75=Elemental Cave: Water
x4tagRegionName76=Winter Stores
x4tagRegionName77=Elemental Cave: Fire
x4tagRegionName78=Monastery Interior
x4tagRegionName79=Shelter of the Failed
x4tagRegionName80=Elemental Cave: Earth
x4tagRegionName81=Slave Pit
x4tagRegionName82=Imperial Palace
x4tagRegionName83=Underground Tunnels
x4tagRegionName84=Yushi Jade Mine
x4tagRegionName85=Subterranean Kilns
x4tagRegionName86=Golden Idol Cave
x4tagRegionName87=Elemental Cave: Convergence
x4tagRegionName88=Shen's Sanctum
x4tagRegionName89=Collapsed Catacombs
x4tagRegionName90=Flooded Temple of Sobek
x4tagRegionName91=Solar Temple of Ra
x4tagRegionName92=Darktread Caves
x4tagRegionName93=Cavern of Serket
x4tagRegionName94=Funerary Temple Ruins
x4tagRegionName95=Burial Vaults
x4tagRegionName96=Great Osiris Temple
x4tagRegionName97=Osireion Crypts
x4tagRegionName98=Abydos Crypts
x4tagRegionName99=Funerary Chapel
x4tagRegionName99b=Mortuary Back Entrance
x4tagRegionName100=Preparation Chambers
x4tagRegionName101=Mortuary Catacombs
x4tagRegionName102=Thieves' Den
x4tagRegionName103=Temple of Serket
x4tagRegionName104=Cavern of Serket
x4tagRegionName105=Lair of the Forbidden Glyph
x4tagRegionName106=Inner Sanctum
x4tagRegionName107=Crowned Scarab Inn
x4tagRegionName108=Dusty Cellar
x4tagRegionName109=Temple of Hathor
x4tagRegionName110=Palace of Thebes
x4tagRegionName111=Forgotten Tombs
x4tagRegionName112=Temple of Aten
x4tagRegionName113=Riverbed Path 
x4tagRegionName114=Back Road
x4tagRegionName115=Abandoned Farms
x4tagRegionName116=Riverside Pathway
x4tagRegionName117=Infested Bog
x4tagRegionName118=Yaoguai Encampment
x4tagRegionName119=Zhaoze Village
x4tagRegionName120=Path of Fenghuang
x4tagRegionName121=Shi Ya City Approach
x4tagRegionName122=Ravaged Shi Ya Square
x4tagRegionName123=Tiantan
x4tagRegionName124=Breeding Grounds
x4tagRegionName125=Mortuary Temple Ruins
x4tagRegionName126=Thebes Farmlands
x4tagRegionName127=Thebes Borderlands
x4tagRegionName128=Floodplains
x4tagRegionName129=City Outskirts
x4tagRegionName130=Cursed Plateau
x4tagRegionName131=Temple of Aten
x4tagRegionName132=Tower Ruins
x4tagRegionName133=Damp Cave
x4tagRegionName134=Secluded Cave
x4tagRegionName135=Akhenaten's Treasure Chambers
x4tagRegionName136=Flooded Hall
x4tagPrefix01=Daji's
x4tagPrefix02=Clairvoyant's
x4tagPrefix03=Soothsayer's
x4tagSuffix01=of Tranquility
x4tagSuffix02=of Harmony
x4tagSuffix03=of Jin Chan
x4tagSuffix04=of Martial Supremacy
x4tagSuffix05=of the Emperor
x4tagSuffix06=of Celestial Might
x4tagSuffix07=of Aten
x4tagSuffix08=of Seth
x4tagSuffix09=of Serket
x4tagSkillNeidanPotionBuff=Potent Elixir
x4tagSkillNeidanPotionBuffDesc=Neidan practitioners often alter their concoctions to grant them additional boons when imbibed.{^n}{^Y}Triggers when a health or energy potion is used.
x4tagSkillNeidanConvergence=Convergence
x4tagSkillNeidanConvergenceDesc=The Neidan's body is attuned to the potions themselves, sometimes granting additional unexpected power.{^n}{^Y}Can trigger when a health or energy potion is used.
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrain=Chi Realignment
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDesc=Realigns an enemy's Chi, wounding them and bolstering your own energies
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDisruption=Reverberation
x4tagSkillNeidanEnergyDrainDisruptionDesc=Severe changes to an enemy's Chi leaves them with lasting consequences.
x4tagSkillNeidanShenPao=Shen Pao
x4tagSkillNeidanShenPaoDesc=Throw a volatile alchemical concoction at a foe that detonates on impact and causes random elemental damage.{^n}{^Y}Can transmit weapon effects.
x4tagSkillNeidanDeathBomb=Echoes of the Ancestors
x4tagSkillNeidanDeathBombDesc=Upon vanquishing enemies with Shen Pao, blast waves emanate from you and deal damage around you.{^n}{^Y}Can trigger on enemy death. 
x4tagSkillNeidanDash=Dash
x4tagSkillNeidanDashDesc=Unleash a burst of chi to move at incredible speed for a short time.
x4tagSkillNeidanDashPhase=Smoke Cloud
x4tagSkillNeidanDashPhaseDesc=Throw a flask that creates a debilitating smoke cloud that can hinder your foes.
x4tagSkillNeidanWeakestChakra=Weakest Chakra
x4tagSkillNeidanWeakestChakraDesc=You become attuned to the elements, emanating lethal energy that weakens enemies and diminishes their vitality.
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreath=Dragon’s Flame 
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathDesc=You unleash the dragon’s flame burning all in front of you and engulfing your enemies with poisonous fumes.
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathFearAndFumble=Dragon Breath
x4tagSkillNeidanDragonsBreathFearAndFumbleDesc=Enemies caught in your Dragon’s Flame will suffer the wrath of the Elements. 
x4tagSkillNeidanLuckyFind=Blessing of Jin Chan 
x4tagSkillNeidanLuckyFindDesc=The blessings of Jin Chan are upon you, granting good fortune.{^n}{^Y}Killing monsters has a chance to grant additional rewards. {&s}Higher levels increase the amount of treasure.
x4tagSkillNeidanGoodFortune=Good Fortune 
x4tagSkillNeidanGoodFortuneDesc=Increasing one's wealth may grant other benefits. 
x4tagSkillNeidanAuraOfTranquility=Aura of Tranquility
x4tagSkillNeidanAuraOfTranquilityDesc=Your mind is a weapon and a shield. You use your Chi to create a renewable barrier around you.
x4tagSkillNeidanEbbandFlow=Inner Equilibrium
x4tagSkillNeidanEbbandFlowDesc=Even when not under the influence of your concoctions, your prowess grows.{^n}{^Y}Bonuses are lost when under the effects of a health or energy potion.
x4tagSkillNeidanMeldingArmor=Melding Armor 
x4tagSkillNeidanMeldingArmorDesc=The strength of your Chi’s flow is such that your barrier is imbued with additional protective energies.
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServant=Terracotta Servants
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantDesc=Throw an alchemically altered figurine that spawns an allied terracotta warrior on impact. More servants can be controlled at once at higher levels.
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantShatter=Shatter
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantShatterDesc=Not even death breaks the bonds of servitude. Your terracotta servant shatters upon death, dealing damage around him.
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantTeachingsOfTheMaster=Forged by Fire 
x4tagSkillNeidanTerracottaServantTeachingsOfTheMasterDesc=Creates a fire aura around the terracotta servant. The aura makes it more fragile but continuously damages enemies in a small area around it.
x4tagSkillNeidanConsequences=Consequences
x4tagSkillNeidanConsequencesDesc=When attacking, you channel ancient mystical powers to lower your foe’s resistances.{^n}{^Y}Attacks have a chance to reduce enemy resistances.
x4tagSkillNeidanLastingConsequences=Huangdi's Favor
x4tagSkillNeidanLastingConsequencesDesc=You channel the wrath of Emperors past and strike your foes with lightning.{^n}{^Y}Assign this skill to your left mouse button. 
x4tagSkillNeidanSplash=Spreading Influence 
x4tagSkillNeidanSplashDesc=You channel the wrath of Huangdi himself, granting your attacks a chance to deal damage in an area.
x4tagSkillNeidanSpreadingRot=Mutual Suffering
x4tagSkillNeidanSpreadingRotDesc=If affected by the consequences of your mystical powers, enemies can spread their weakness on others when stricken.{^n}{^Y}Enemies who die with the Consequences debuff on them have a chance to spread it to nearby allies.
x4tagNeidanMastery=Neidan Mastery
x4tagNeidanMasteryDescription=Master Neidan, the art of internal and external alchemy. Using a combination of deadly concoctions and abilities that make use of their inner energies, Neidan masters are a force to be reckoned with.
x4tagNeidan=Neidan
x4tagNeidanStorm=Channeler
x4tagNeidanDefense=Monk
x4tagNeidanEarth=Wu
x4tagNeidanNature=Hermit
x4tagNeidanWarfare=Daoist
x4tagNeidanHunting=Pilgrim
x4tagNeidanSpirit=Spiritualist
x4tagNeidanRogue=Disruptor
x4tagNeidanDream=Contemplator
x4tagNeidanRune=Esoterist
x4tagMChina=The East
x4tagMZone01=Summer Palace
x4tagMZone02=Xiao
x4tagMZone03=Pingyang
x4tagMZone04=The Ascent 
x4tagMZone05=Heavenly Palace
x4tagMZone06=Asyut Encampment
x4tagMZone07=Necropolis Outskirts
x4tagMZone08=Thebes
x4tagMZone09=Scorched Ridge
x4tagMZone10=Lai
x4tagMPortal01=Summer Palace Portal
x4tagMPortal02=Xiao Portal
x4tagMPortal03=Pingyang Portal
x4tagMPortal04=The Ascent Portal
x4tagMPortal05=Heavenly Palace Portal
x4tagMPortal06=Asyut Encampment Portal
x4tagMPortal07=Necropolis Outskirts Portal
x4tagMPortal08=Thebes Portal
x4tagMPortal09=Scorched Ridge Portal
x4tagMPortal10=Lai Portal
x4tag_PotionOfSpeed=Potion of Speed
x4tag_PotionOfAmbrosia=Potion of Ambrosia
x4tag_PotionOfService=Potion of Service
x4tag_PotionWuTaosElixir=Wu Tao's Elixir
x4tag_PotionJadeEmperorsResolve=Potion of the Jade Emperor's Resolve
x4tag_PotionOfEvasion=Potion of Evasion
x4tag_PotionLifeDrainer=Potion of Life Draining
x4tag_PotionOfNewBeginnings=Potion of New Beginnings
x4tag_PotionOfSpeedDesc=This potion increases your base movement speed.
x4tag_PotionOfAmbrosiaDesc=This potion increases your primary resistances.
x4tag_PotionOfServiceDesc=This potion increases your base armor.
x4tag_PotionWuTaosElixirDesc=This potion increases your bleeding and poison resistance.
x4tag_PotionJadeEmperorsResolveDesc=This potion increases your secondary resistances.
x4tag_PotionOfEvasionDesc=This potion increases your dodge and projectile avoidance chance.
x4tag_PotionLifeDrainerDesc=This potion converts a portion of the damage you deal to Life Leech.
x4tag_PotionOfNewBeginningsDesc=This potion resets your spent attribute points.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Abdicate=Abdicate
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DeathsToll=Death's Toll
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Discharge=Discharge
x4tagSkill_Artifact_Endure=Endure
x4tagSkill_Artifact_AbdicateDesc=Strike terror into your enemies' hearts, temporarily reducing their maximum health, slowing them, and increasing their vulnerability.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DeathsTollDesc=Succumb to a state of frenzy, gaining speed, damage, and resistances with every kill.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_DischargeDesc=Imbue your weapons with the wrath of a tempest, temporarily dealing electrical and cold damage with every strike and exposing your enemies' weaknesses.
x4tagSkill_Artifact_EndureDesc=Flood your body with magic, increasing resilience while wielding axes.
Note_NeidanLetter=Yin Lihua, {^n}{^n}I understand you wish to end your apprenticeship, and I accept your decision. Perhaps it is better this way – you had many virtues, but patience was not one of them.{^n}Six years ago, you sought my mentorship to master Neidan, the art of internal alchemy. I had concerns: You were hot-tempered and quick to judge. And even though you never said so, I know it was not only health and wisdom you seek, but also immortality and power to find revenge against those who took your daughter’s life. Despite all this, I accepted. Why, you ask? Because I can tell a just soul when I see it. Because in your eyes lurked a pain which I know all too well. {^n}{^n}Six years, I trained you, helped you cultivate your Jing, soothe your Qi, and help see your Shen. I taught you my most secret concoctions and recipes, even those meant to harm and not heal. Six years, I felt nothing but pride when I saw you train in the courtyard, up before dawn like every day, driven by that force of will that writes history. {^n}And while it may be true that you have learned all I could teach you, I cannot but wonder: what kind of apprentice makes such a decision without at least looking her master in the eye? Where was this courage you always spoke of?You are a warrior of Neidan now, Yin Lihua, and may it serve you well on the bloody path before you. But if there is one last bit of advice you may take from your old master, let it be this: some demons lurk on the inside. And they cannot be slain like the rest. {^n}{^n}I wish you longevity,{^n}Your Master Fa Xian
Note_HuizhongLetter=My dear friend Ma Yuan,{^n}{^n}I thank you for your kind words. You advise me not to worry, to trust in our Lord, the Son of Heaven’s, wisdom and guidance. And I try, Ma Yuan, I truly try. But tell me this, my dear friend: how much trust does a leader need to reassure a fearful farmer whose fields the Suns’ rage has turned barren? How much trust to inspire the village guards, green-faced boys and pitchfork-wielding men, to stand against the many beasts the Great Peril’s appearance has brought back into our lands? How much trust to console a mother who lost her boy to their claws?{^n}I am no blasphemer. I believe in the Son of Heaven’s wisdom, for he is divine. But I also believe that only trust and faith have yet to vanquish a threat such as the one we face. {^n}Ancestors know we cannot best it alone.{^n}{^n}Sincerely,{^n}Your Friend Huizhong
Note_MogwaiBit=Numerous as the Mogwai are, scholars are still in disagreement as to their origins. While old theories suggest they are nothing but malicious demon spawn with a penchant for malice and destruction, some scholars now offer an alternative explanation: that the Mogwai are actually vengeful spirits seeking to destroy those that caused their suffering. Said scholars also suggest that a monetary sacrifice—coins placed in a bowl at the doorstep—may appease the Mogwai by giving them the funds to traverse the afterlife, but this theory remains shadily doubtful. Whatever the truth, one thing remains certain: if a Mogwai crosses your path, running or fighting is doubtlessly the best course of action.
Note_QiongQiReport=Lieutenant,{^n}{^n}I understand your frustration and apologize deeply. However, it was simply not possible – or beyond my capabilities – to extract any useful information from the poor man, as the events have turned him fully catatonic. Besides describing Qiong Qi’s gruesome attack, all I could get out of him was a confused ramble about fire and the suns. I imagine he refers to the horrible drought. {^n}Let us hope future witnesses bring more clarity.{^n}{^n}Heavens guide you,{^n}Lu Buwei
Note_BookOfTheDeadNote=My Lord, {^n}{^n}I have investigated the matter as per your request. Your suspicions were correct—some does indeed seem to have stolen the Book of the Dead. I shall investigate the matter further.{^n}{^n}Your humble servant,{^n}Yanluo Wang
Note_ReliefedPriest=In peace, Amenmose,{^n}{^n}They say to never speak ill of the pharaoh, for the gods see and hear it all, yet I am certain they would not mind hearing this: it is finally over. After seventeen years of his madness, Akhenaten and his wife Nefertiti are finally dead. They were poisoned, but I do not know nor care by whom—gods know his enemies were countless. {^n}According to word of mouth, they are already preparing his son’s Tutankhamun’s initiation, and it appears Ay will be the new vizier. No one knows where his loyalties lie or what his goals are, but he does have a reputation for being a pragmatist, so I am certain he will put an end to Akhenaten’s mad sun worship cult and lead people back to the pantheon. {^n}Do you know what this means, Amenmose? No more hiding our faith. No more burning of our statues. Our temples will once again shine in all their splendor, full of supplicants of the true faith. All that remains for us to do is to pray we have not yet fallen from grace.{^n}{^n}In deepest friendship,{^n}Duaenre
Note_YingAndYang=Those who wish to understand the Tao must first understand this: the world is a contrast. {^n}Light and dark. Water and fire. Big and small. Neither of these aspects would have meaning without an opposite quality – the yin to the yang, and the yang to the yin. Because there is night, there is day, because there is good, there is evil; they are inevitable.{^n}But if they are, why do they matter to the Taoist? It is simple: they help us see. If the practitioner encounters a problem, physical or spiritual, personal or global, he calmly sees the dry duality where others see only a projection of their own ambitions, fears and wishes. Only once such lucid vision has been attained, the Taoist can and should proceed to act. 
Note_UndeadReport=Commander Azibo,{^n}{^n}I fear the news are dire; the entire desert seems to be crawling with undead. I have tried to track down their nest, but I could not advance far enough; they are simply too many. I am no arcanist, so I cannot say what has caused them to rise, but even I sense a sickening overpowering unease in the desert; it is as though great powers are at work.{^n}It is not my position to advise you, Commander, yet my duties as a Theban command I do so: you must urge the pharaoh and the vizier to not take this threat lightly. Our walls are high, but there is only so much one can do if the foes you are fighting are already dead.{^n}{^n}In peace,{^n}Scout Zuka
Note_BaoNotes=Sun too hot. Bao not like, make skin yuck and shiny things melt. Bao want smash suns, but suns up too high. Maybe human help?
Note_Pamphlet=The line of Pharaoh’s has become corrupt! Their blasphemy and debauchery has gone to far. Oh, great people of Egypt, save your souls, worship the gods with all your heart, and trust your priests to deliver you from sin. Trust your priests to guide you for they are the only ones who know the path to salvation. Let them rule you in matters of body and soul. {^n}{^n}May the blessings of Ra be upon you, you who have suffered so much.   
Note_Qilin=Qilin. The benevolent chimera. {^n}{^n}As it is the case with many divine and supernatural creatures, legends shroud the qilin like stardust; and since sightings of these beautiful beings are so rare and reports differ, it might always remain this way. What almost all of them agree on is this: with beards, upwards-flowing manes, and antlers, qilin resemble wingless dragons. Some witnesses said parts of them were aflame when they appeared, though the fire did them no harm; others say soft down feathers adorn their scales like a most magnificent bird, while another source claims to have seen fishlike scales and bedazzling jewelry.{^n}{^n}Another certainty is this: while a qilin’s magic is powerful, they never harm innocents, seeking exclusively to punish the wicked. Furthermore, their appearance can be seen as an omen of good. Thus, it came as no surprise, when, during the Son of Heaven’s coronation, an entire herd of them appeared at the palace courtyard.
Note_Guardsman=Dear Ziying,{^n}{^n}A drought ravages the land and Qiong Qi of the Great Perils and his minions are butchering innocents by the dozens, yet all this lowlife brigand scum can think about is looting and plundering, like carrion crows feeding off the corpses. So how could I not be upset? Mankind is so quick to complain about its many travails, yet, since we evolved from Pangu’s mites, all we do is tear at each other’s throats. Ancestors forgive me for saying this, but perhaps it would be better if Qiong Qi made short work of us all.But here I am again, being all pessimistic. I will try to be better, my friend. I will try.{^n}{^n}I wish you longevity,{^n}Zhao
Note_HunAndPo=Understand, pupil of the Tao: death is not the end.{^n}It is common knowledge that we continue to exist after death: like everything in this world, we are made of a yin and a yang, the po and the hun.  When we perish, the po splits into two fragments, one of which stays in our buried body, while the other ascends to the Heavens to be judged; the hun, however, remains in the spirit tablet by our grave. {^n}While you may assume our hun and po are immortal, for we have already died, they are wrong: both must be nourished and tended to by our descendants, until, with time, the hun ascends to heaven, only to later descend to the underworld together with the po.{^n}Why is it important to follow the rituals and tend to the deceased’s hun and po? Simple: if you do not, their ghost may come to haunt you.{^n}But this is a story for another scroll.
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_01=If you are reading this, odds are you are experiencing a rather unpleasant event: you are being haunted by a ghost or guei. But do not despair, my friend, for every haunting can be ended, and The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting will show you how.{^n}{^n}The first step must always be to identify the nature of the haunting, hun or po. Let us start with the latter: as you well know, the po is the part of us that stays in our bodies when we perish; when a po haunting occurs, the ghost will return in its original, often decomposing form, which can be a rather unpleasant sight.{^n}The hun haunting, on the other hand, can be infinitely more pernicious; as the hun is the part of us that contains our personality, during a hun haunting, the haunted often sees the ghost in their dreams, or some other incorporeal form.{^n}Now, doubtlessly, the following question burns on your mind: what to do? How do you “un-haunt” yourself?{^n}{^n}I fear to the answer, you will have to buy, The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 2!
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_02=If you are reading this, it means you have already basked in the semantic beauty of The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 1. If not, I strongly recommend you buy it first, for many of the stunning insights provided in Volume 2 may be hard to comprehend otherwise.{^n}{^n}As discussed in the previous volume, there are two types of hauntings, po and hun, corporeal and ethereal. First, here is the good news: most hauntings of either type can be easily remedied by doing what, if I may say so, you should have done before.{^n}Follow the burial customs.{^n}You heard right, my friend: the majority of hauntings is caused by improper burial customs. Kindly assuming you are not a heathen or simply disrespectful, I will omit a lengthy compilation of what these customs are – as you know, there are many. Even so, believe me when I say, that a simple candle or properly placed burial mound has solved many a client’s tribulations.{^n}{^n}If you followed the burial customs or the guei is not even related to you, things might be more difficult. Quite unfortunately, however, my ink has just run out, so I will explain what’s needed in the next volume, The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 3!
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_03=Friend! Client! Haunting-afflicted Soul! It is my pleasure to welcome you to the The Ghost Expert’s Manual to Unhaunting, Volume 3, the sadly last volume of this immensely helpful and affordable guide to unhaunting.{^n}{^n}If you are still reading, it means that your haunting cannot be traced back to improper burial customs. Unfortunate.{^n}{^n}My friend, let me ask you this: have you ever acted unvirtuously? And no, I am not talking of the sweets you stole as a child or the canoodling you engaged in before marriage. I am talking about broken oaths, dubious bargains, betrayed lovers, and things far more sinister to mention. Often, the ghosts who return despite being properly buried do so because they have been wronged, and most likely by the target of their haunting. {^n}{^n}What do I do, you ask me? Simple: undo the wrong. Make amends. Depending on the scope of your misdemeanor, this may bring the restless soul to rest. And if not? Then, my dear friend, you are well and thoroughly done for. {^n}Good luck!
Note_To_Whom_It_May_Concern=That’s it. I’ve had it! Day in and day out we raid the human villages…why do they have to make it so difficult? Pitchfork this, cudgel that. And now there’s rumor of an insane Greek travelling the land, killing everything in sight. No thank you, my insurance doesn’t cover foreign invasions. Apparently two mages in the West are hiring extras for their show – they even provide dental. The audition is tomorrow, wish me luck!{^n}{^n}Signed, {^n}Mittens 
Note_Overtime!?=Overtime! Really?! Even when I’m dead?! The nerve of some people! Was I not a good servant in life? Did I not do enough? Build a city he said. Build temples to Aten he said. All that and I still get called back? {^n}{^n}And on top of all that, I can’t even understand him anymore. All he does is rave on about the Sun and flames, burn this, burn that. Now he wants a temple and all I’ve been given is a skeleton crew… he will be the death of me…again (hopefully).
Note_Odin_Help_Me=Odin help me what are these people on about?! I can’t understand any of them. And what are these helmets without horns? Ever since I devoured the soul of that weird blonde man from far away, I have been seeing things differently. I think I will go west, build a ship and find some coasts to raid as is proper.{^n}{^n}Wiedersehen,{^n}Gustav
x4tagMenuCreateX4Char=Legendary Hero
x4tagBoostedCharDesc=You are creating a hero of suitable level and wealth for adventures in the East. {^n} The journey begins at the start of the Eternal Embers campaign on Legendary Difficulty.{^n}Characters created this way cannot enter Normal or Epic difficulty. 
x4tagRaceHumankind=Humankind
xtag4MoveOnly=Move Only
x4tagTravelQuestion_01=Go through the passage?
x4tagWarriorArmorRack=Warrior's Armor Rack
x4tagHunterArmorRack=Hunter's Armor Rack
x4tagSorcererArmorRack=Sage's Armor Rack
x4tagExperienceGain={%+.0f0}% Experience Gained
x4tag_MQJC002_Reward=+10 Points to Str/Int/Dex
x4tag_SQ_301_Reward=+10% Vitality Damage Resistance
x4tagImperialChest=Imperial Chest
x4tagBoostedCharServerDesc=Unable to connect. You cannot access lower difficulties with this character because it was created with the Legendary Hero boost.
x4tagCanopicJar=Canopic Jar
x4tagPot=Pot
x4tagCoffin=Coffin
x4tagContrast=Contrast
x4tagContrastDescription=Set screen contrast
x4tagBrightness=Brightness
x4tagBrightnessDescription=Set screen brightness
x4tagInviteFriends=Invite Friends
x4tagBackground05=Eternal Embers
x4tagEternalIntro=Eternal Embers Intro
x4tagEternalOutro=Eternal Embers Outro 
tagBuyDLC3=Get Eternal Embers
x4tagStoryScroll_China=Mystic Tome
x4tagStoryScroll_Egypt=Ancient Papyrus Treatise
Note_NeidanLetterTitle=Letter to Yin Lihua
Note_HuizhongLetterTitle=Worries
Note_MogwaiBitTitle=Mogwai 101
Note_QiongQiReportTitle=Field Report
Note_BookOfTheDeadNoteTitle=Theft
Note_ReliefedPriestTitle=An End To The Madness
Note_YingAndYangTitle=The Principles Of Tao
Note_UndeadReportTitle=The Army Of The Dead
Note_BaoNotesTitle=BAO PROPERTY, NO TOUCH
Note_PamphletTitle=Rise! Resist!
Note_QilinTitle=A Study Of The Qilin
Note_GuardsmanTitle=Bandit Scum!
Note_HunAndPoTitle=Hun And Po
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_01Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 1
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_02Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 2
Note_Unhaunting_Manual_03Title=Unhaunting Manual: Vol. 3
Note_To_Whom_It_May_ConcernTitle=To Whom It May Concern
Note_Overtime!?Title=Overtime?!
Note_Odin_Help_MeTitle=Dietary Changes
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff01=Corrupted Shrine: Vitality Drain
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff02=Corrupted Shrine: Poison Touch
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff03=Corrupted Shrine: Torpor
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuff04=Corrupted Shrine: Weakness
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc01=While in range, drains life force.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc02=While in range, deals poison damage.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc03=While in range, slows movement speed.
x4tagAkhenatenPillarDebuffDesc04=While in range, decreases resistances.
x4tagAkhenatenPillar=Corrupted Shrine
SkillChanceWeightFloat={%.1f0}% Chance to be Used
x4tagSunsNovaDebuff01=Nova
x4tagSunsNovaDebuff01Desc=Damages and slows the player while increasing the power and resistance of enemies if standing in the blasted area.
x4tagMZone11=Thebes Outskirts
x4tagUSkill01=Blood Curse
x4tagUSkill01Desc=Causes bleed damage to enemies near you.
x4tagUSkill02=Essence of Thunder
x4tagUSkill02Desc=Orbs of lighting damage your enemies.
x4tagUSkill03=Ice Touch
x4tagUSkill03Desc=A wave of icy water slams your enemies, dealing them physical and cold damage, sometimes even stunning them.
x4tagUSkill04=Venomous Mist
x4tagUSkill04Desc=A venomous mist poisons everything that sets foot in it's domain.
x4tagUSkill05=Hell's Blessing
x4tagUSkill05Desc=The blessing of hell roots nearby enemies, draining their life and mana. The enemies projectiles bounce off your shield.
x4tagUSkill06=Kepher's Sting
x4tagUSkill06Desc=The god Kepher grants his protection. Has a chance to reflect and absorb melee damage for a short duration, upon being hit by a melee attack.
x4tagUSkill07=Ra's Fury
x4tagUSkill07Desc=Hurls five burning molten orbs that explode when they hit the ground, dealing fire and burning damage to enemies in a small radius.
x4tagUSkill08=Aten's Gaze
x4tagUSkill08Desc=Deals burning damage in a small radius over a short period of time.
x4tagUSkill09=Medjai Sand Twister
x4tagUSkill09Desc=Creates a powerful sand storm that buffets your enemies.
x4tagUSkill010=Summon Desecrated Dead
x4tagUSkill010Desc=Summons the skeleton of a desecrated corpse to fight at your side.
x4tagUSkill011=Blade Storm
x4tagUSkill011Desc=Throw piercing blades at opponents in all directions around you capable of causing prolonged bleeding.
x4tagShrine01On=Fires Wrath
x4tagShrine01Off=Remove Fire’s Wrath
x4tagShrine01Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially towards fire, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine02On=Heart of Frost
x4tagShrine02Off=Remove Heart of Frost
x4tagShrine02Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against cold, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine03On=Lightning Feebleness
x4tagShrine03Off=Remove Lightning Feebleness Curse
x4tagShrine03Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against lightning, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine04On=Curse of the Arrow
x4tagShrine04Off=Remove Curse of the Arrow
x4tagShrine04Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against being pierced, but the rewards for your heroism are increased
x4tagShrine05On=Fragile Vitality
x4tagShrine05Off=Remove Fragile Vitality Curse
x4tagShrine05Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against vitality wounds, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine06On=Malevolent Poison
x4tagShrine06Off=Remove Malevolent Poison Curse 
x4tagShrine06Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against vitality wounds, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine07On=Festering Wounds
x4tagShrine07Off=Remove Festering Wounds Curse
x4tagShrine07Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against bleeding, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine08On=Weakness of the Flesh
x4tagShrine08Off=Remove Weakness of the Flesh Curse
x4tagShrine08Desc=Your resistances are decreased especially against being physically damaged, but the rewards for your heroism are increased.
x4tagShrine09Off=Cleansing Blessing
x4tagShrine09Desc=Removes all curses
x4tagShrine10=Altar of Ancient Chaos 
x4tagShrine10Desc=Come hero, look upon the remnant of an age past, an age forgotten and full of secrets. Within these halls ancient and powerful enemies await but also prizes like non other on this good earth. Use the Keys of Chaos to enter or forever wonder what treasures you have forsaken. 
x4tagShrine15Desc=Come hero, look upon the remnant of an age past, an age forgotten and full of secrets. Within these halls ancient and powerful enemies await but also prizes like non other on this good earth. Use the Epic Chaos Keys to enter or forever wonder what treasures you have forsaken. 
x4tagShrine16Desc=Come hero, look upon the remnant of an age past, an age forgotten and full of secrets. Within these halls ancient and powerful enemies await but also prizes like non other on this good earth. Use the Keys of Legendary Chaos to enter or forever wonder what treasures you have forsaken. 
x4tagShrine11=Ancient Altar of Choice 
x4tagShrine11Desc=Take what prizes you have earned and exit this realm or continue on against even greater challenges for chance at true glory.   
x4tagShrine12=Altar of Redeeming 
x4tagShrine12Desc=At this sacred place you can redeem heavenly Electrum for a prized Orb of your choice as a reward for your worthy deeds.
x4tagRegionName137=Temple of Heaven’s Pact
x4tagOrb01=Hellenic Orb
x4tagOrb01Desc=This orb is ladened with items from the Hellenic world and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb01_Question=Do you want to buy the Hellenic Orb?
x4tagOrb02=Epic Hellenic Orb
x4tagOrb02Desc=This powerful orb is ladened with epic items from the Hellenic world and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb02_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Hellenic Orb?
x4tagOrb03=Legendary Hellenic Orb
x4tagOrb03Desc=This orb of majestic power contains legendary and unique items that come from the Hellenic world but it also holds a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb03_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Hellenic Orb?
x4tagOrb04=Pharaonic Orb
x4tagOrb04Desc=This orb is ladened with items from the land of Egypt and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb04_Question=Do you want to buy the Pharaonic Orb?
x4tagOrb05=Epic Pharaonic Orb
x4tagOrb05Desc=This powerful orb is ladened with epic items from the land of Egypt and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb05_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Pharaonic Orb?
x4tagOrb06=Legendary Pharaonic Orb
x4tagOrb06Desc=This orb of majestic power contains legendary and unique items that come from the Land of Egypt but it also holds a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb06_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Pharaonic Orb?
x4tagOrb07=Orient Orb
x4tagOrb07Desc=This orb is ladened with items from the Orient and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb07_Question=Do you want to buy the Orient Orb?
x4tagOrb08=Epic Orient Orb
x4tagOrb08Desc=This powerful orb is ladened with epic items from the Orient and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb08_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Orient Orb?
x4tagOrb09=Legendary Orient Orb
x4tagOrb09Desc=This orb of majestic power contains legendary and unique items that come from the Orient but it also holds a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb09_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Orient Orb?
x4tagOrb10=Orb of Hades
x4tagOrb10Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Hades, contains items from the underworld and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb10_Question=Do you want to buy the Orb of Hades?
x4tagOrb11=Epic Orb of Hades
x4tagOrb11Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Hades, contains epic items from the underworld and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb11_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Orb of Hades?
x4tagOrb12=Legendary Orb of Hades
x4tagOrb12Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Hades, contains legendary and unique items from the underworld and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb12_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Orb of Hades?
x4tagOrb13=Scandian Orb
x4tagOrb13Desc=This orb is ladened with items from the North and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb13_Question=Do you want to buy the Scandian Orb?
x4tagOrb14=Epic Scandian Orb
x4tagOrb14Desc=This powerful orb is ladened with epic items from the North and contains a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb14_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Scandian Orb?
x4tagOrb15=Legendary Scandian Orb
x4tagOrb15Desc=This orb of majestic power contains legendary and unique items that come from the North but it also holds a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb15_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Scandian Orb?
x4tagOrb16=Orb of Tiamat
x4tagOrb16Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Tiamat, contains items from the lost realm of Atlantis and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb16_Question=Do you want to buy the Orb of Tiamat?
x4tagOrb17=Epic Orb of Tiamat
x4tagOrb17Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Tiamat, contains epic items from the lost realm of Atlantis and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb17_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Orb of Tiamat?
x4tagOrb18=Legendary Orb of Tiamat
x4tagOrb18Desc=This orb, imbued with the power of Tiamat, contains legendary and unique items from the lost realm of Atlantis and a part of a secret key.
x4tagOrb18_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Orb of Tiamat?
x4tagOrb19=Orb of the Jade Emperor
x4tagOrb19Desc=This orb, infused with the mystical energies of the Jade Emperor, contains items from the realm of China and also a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb19_Question=Do you want to buy the Orb of the Jade Emperor?
x4tagOrb20=Epic Orb of the Jade Emperor
x4tagOrb20Desc=This orb, infused with the mystical energies of the Jade Emperor, contains items from the realm of China and also a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb20_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Orb of the Jade Emperor?
x4tagOrb21=Legendary Orb of the Jade Emperor
x4tagOrb21Desc=This orb, infused with the mystical energies of the Jade Emperor, contains items from the realm of China and also a piece of a secret key.
x4tagOrb21_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Orb of the Jade Emperor?
x4tagOrb22=Theban Orb
x4tagOrb22Desc=This orb, forged in late Egypt under the rule of Pharaoh Tutankhamun, contains items of power and a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagOrb22_Question=Do you want to buy the Theban Orb?
x4tagOrb23=Epic Theban Orb
x4tagOrb23Desc=This orb, forged in late Egypt under the rule of Pharaoh Tutankhamun, contains items of power and a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagOrb23_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Theban Orb?
x4tagOrb24=Legendary Theban Orb
x4tagOrb24Desc=This orb, forged in late Egypt under the rule of Pharaoh Tutankhamun, contains legendary items of great power and a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagOrb24_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Theban Orb?
x4tagHCDungeon01=The Remnants of Great Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon01Desc=Entrance to the remnants of Great Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon02=The Fissure of Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon02Desc=The entrance to the Fissure of Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon03=The Pit of Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon03Desc=The Entrance to the Pit of Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon04=Halls of Madness
x4tagHCDungeon04Desc=The entrance to Halls of Madness
x4tagHCDungeon05=The Fragment of Havoc
x4tagHCDungeon05Desc=The entrance to the Fragment of Havoc
x4tagHCDungeon06=The Chaos Serpent’s Domain
x4tagHCDungeon06Desc=The entrance to the Chaos serpent’s domain
x4tagHCDungeon07=The Chaos
x4tagHCDungeon07Desc=The entrance to the Chaos
x4tagCThirdStats=III
x4tagCQuartStats=IV
x4tagCDodgePercent=Chance to Dodge Attacks
x4tagCDeflectProjectileChance=Chance to Avoid Projectiles
x4tagCADctH=Weapon Damage as Health
x4tagCEleConversion=Weapon Base as Elemental
x4tagCBlockRecovery=Shield Recovery Time
x4tagCCooldownReduction=Recharge Reduction
x4tagCManaCostReduction=Energy Cost Reduction
x4tagCR_DodgePercent=Allows to avoid damage from melee attacks.
x4tagCR_DeflectProjectileChance=Allows to avoid damage from projectiles and spells.
x4tagCR_ADctH=Percentage of weapon attack damage that is gained as Health.
x4tagCR_EleConversion=How much of your weapon's base Physical Damage is converted to Elemental Damage.
x4tagCR_BlockRecovery=Delay until another shield block can happen
x4tagCR_CooldownReduction=Reduces the recharge time of spells and certain items.
x4tagCR_ManaCostReduction=Reduces the Energy required to use skills.
x4tagCDamageStats=Damage Bonuses
x4tagCDamageStats2=Damage & Duration Bonuses
x4tagCDamageStats3=Damage & Race Bonuses
x4tagCMonsterStats=Monster Race Bonuses
x4tagCPetStats=Pet Bonuses
x4tagCSDctH=Spell Damage as Health
x4tagCR_SDctH=Percentage of spell damage that is gained as Health
x4tagCAttribBonusDex=*{%.2f0} Global Multiplier (Dex)
x4tagCAttribBonusInt=*{%.2f0} Global Multiplier (Int)
x4tagCAttribBonusLvl=*{%.2f0} Global Multiplier (Lvl)
x4tagCAttribBonusStr_W=*{%.2f0} Weapon Multiplier (Str)
x4tagCAttribBonusStr_S=*{%.2f0} Spell Multiplier (Str)
x4tagCAttribBonusDex_W=*{%.2f0} Weapon Multiplier (Dex)
x4tagCAttribBonusDex_S=*{%.2f0} Spell Multiplier (Dex)
x4tagShrine13=Shrine of Ancient Chaos 
x4tagShrine13Desc=All of your companions must enter if you are to proceed to the challenge. 
x4tagShrine14=Shrine of the Ancient Champion of Chaos
x4tagShrine14Desc=You have bested the Champion and all of forces of Chaos. Claim your just reward. 
x4tagHCDungeonKey04=Fragment of Chaos
x4tagButton01=Continue forward 
x4tagButton02=Get the loot
x4tagLockMessage=You cannot enter this cave at this instance. 
x4tagAntiquityOrb=Antiquity Orb
x4tagAntiquityOrbDesc=This orb contains items from antique times gathered from all over the world. It also contains a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagAntiquityOrb_Question=Do you want to buy the Antiquity orb?
x4tagEpicAniquityOrb=Epic Antiquity Orb
x4tagEpicAniquityOrbDesc=This orb contains items of epic might from antique times gathered from all over the world. It also contains a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagEpicAniquityOrb_Question=Do you want to buy the Epic Antiquity Orb?
x4tagLegendaryAntiquityOrb=Legendary Antiquity Orb
x4tagLegendaryAntiquityOrbDesc=This orb contains items of legendary might from antique times gathered from all over the world. It also contains a fragment of a secret key.
x4tagLegendaryAntiquityOrb_Question=Do you want to buy the Legendary Antiquity Orb?
x4tagElectrumGreen={^g}Cost  {%d0} ~ Electrum
x4tagElectrumRed={^r}Cost  {%d0} ~ Electrum
x4tagRequiresContentEE={^r}Requires Content: Eternal Embers
x4tagRequiresContentAtlantis={^r}Requires Content: Atlantis
x4tagRequiresContentRagnarok={^r}Requires Content: Ragnarök
