// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
//encoding = RAW

tagGreeceQ1UiTitle=A Troubled Village{^n}
tagGreeceQ2UiTitle=Spartans at War{^n}
tagGreeceQ3UiTitle=The Words of the Oracle{^n}
tagGreeceQ4UiTitle=The Source of the Monsters{^n}
tagGreeceQ5UiTitle=The Battle for Athens{^n}
tagGreeceQ6UiTitle=The Order of Prometheus{^n}
tagGreeceQ7UiTitle=Under the Labyrinth{^n}
tagGreeceQ7AltUiTitle=The Heart of the Maze{^n}
tagEgyptQ8UiTitle=The Blindness of the Gods{^n}
tagEgyptQ9UiTitle=The Invocation{^n}
tagEgyptQ10UiTitle=A Telkine in Egypt{^n}
tagOrientQ11UiTitle=The Sickle of Kronos{^n}
tagOrientQ12UiTitle=Hunt for the Sickle{^n}
tagOrientQ13UiTitle=Journey to the Jade Palace{^n}
tagOrientQ14UiTitle=Under Wusao Mountain{^n}
tagOlympusQ15UiTitle=Olympus{^n}
tagQ1AObjA=Save Timaeus' horse{^n}
tagQ1AObjB=Speak to Timaeus{^n}
tagQ1AObjC=Investigate the problems in Helos{^n}
tagQ1AObjD=Find and defeat the satyr shaman{^n}
tagQ1AObjE=Return to Diomedes in the village{^n}
tagQ1AObjF=Return to the farmer Eumolpus{^n}
tagQ2ObjA=Find Leonidas in Sparta{^n}
tagQ2ObjB=Defeat the centaur Nessus to gain an audience with Leonidas{^n}
tagQ2ObjC=Return to the Spartan Camp and tell Brasidas of your victory{^n}
tagQ2ObjD=Speak with Leonidas{^n}
tagQ3ObjA=Travel to Delphi and consult the great Oracle there{^n}
tagQ3ObjB=Speak with Timon in Megara{^n}
tagQ4ObjA=Seek answers through the Parnassus Caves{^n}
tagQ4ObjB=Defeat the gorgons{^n}
tagQ4ObjC=Talk to the woman{^n}
tagQ5ObjA=Travel to Athens{^n}
tagQ5ObjB=Speak with Leonidas at the Athens' gates{^n}
tagQ6ObjA=Investigate rumors that monsters have breached the walls of Athens{^n}
tagQ6ObjB=Find the entrance to the catacombs in the Athenian Parthenon{^n}
tagQ6ObjC=Stop the monsters in the catacombs{^n}
tagQ6ObjD=Speak to the old man{^n}
tagQ7ObjA=Locate and protect the artifact in Knossos{^n}
tagQ7ObjB=Meet the Promethean agent at the Athenian docks{^n}
tagQ7ObjC=Defeat the Telkine{^n}
tagQ7ObjD=Speak to Kyros{^n}
tagQ8ObjA=Travel to Rhakotis in Egypt and find Imhotep{^n}
tagQ8ObjB=Retrieve the Scroll of Invocation from the Rhakotis Library{^n}
tagQ8ObjC=Bring the Scroll to the Temple of Ptah in Sais{^n}
tagQ8ObjD=Defeat Scarabaeus{^n}
tagQ8ObjE=Bring the Scroll to Imhotep in Memphis{^n}
tagQ9ObjA=Obtain the Hand of Balance from Giza{^n}
tagQ9ObjB=Obtain the Eye of Chaos in the region near the Fayum Oasis{^n}
tagQ9ObjC=Bring the Hand and the Eye to Imhotep in Memphis{^n}
tagQ9ObjD=Defeat the Pharaoh’s Honor Guard{^n}
tagQ9ObjE=Defeat Nehebkau{^n}
tagQ10ObjA=Search for the Telkine in the Valley of the Kings{^n}
tagQ10ObjB=Defeat the Telkine{^n}
tagQ10ObjC=Take the strange tablet and meet Imhotep in Thebes{^n}
tagQ11ObjA=Travel to Babylon{^n}
tagQ11ObjB=Find and protect the Sickle of Kronos{^n}
tagQ11ObjC=Speak to Feiyan{^n}
tagQ12ObjA=Track the Telkine with the Sickle{^n}
tagQ12ObjB=The Telkine went east on the Silk Road{^n}
tagQ12ObjC=The Telkine went towards Chang'an{^n}
tagQ12ObjD=A woman in Chang'an is looking for you{^n}
tagQ13ObjA=Travel to the Jade Palace and speak to the Yellow Emperor{^n}
tagQ14ObjA=Find Wusao Mountain{^n}
tagQ14ObjB=Find Typhon's Prison{^n}
tagQ14ObjD=Defeat the Telkine{^n}
tagQ15ObjA=Follow Typhon through the portal{^n}
tagQ15ObjB=Kill Typhon{^n}
tagQ1ADescA=Strange beasts have surrounded a poor man's horse.  He needs your help in saving it.{^n}  
tagQ1ADescB=Strange beasts were attacking a poor man's horse.  The horse is safe now.{^n}
tagQ1ADescC=The man said that his village, Helos, which is farther down the road, is having trouble with these monsters.{^n}
tagQ1ADescD=A powerful satyr shaman has been leading boars and satyrs into the village farm land.  These monsters threaten to destroy the crops for the entire village and shatter their weakening defenses.{^n}
tagQ1ADescE=A powerful satyr shaman was leading boars and satyrs into the village farmland.  These monsters threatened to destroy the crops for the entire village and shatter their frail defenses.  With the shaman gone, the village of Helos should be able to hold out against these strange monsters.{^n}
tagQ1DescComplete=A powerful satyr shaman was leading boars and satyrs into the village farmland.  These monsters threatened to destroy the crops for the entire village and shatter their frail defenses.  With the shaman gone, the village of Helos should be able to hold out against these strange monsters.  Long enough, hopefully, for help from the Spartans to arrive.{^n}

tagQ2DescA=Find the great Spartan general, Leonidas, and beg him to send soldiers to protect the village Helos.  Perhaps he will also know more of the strange monsters, and where they come from.  Travel through Laconia and on to Sparta.{^n}
tagQ2DescComplete=Leonidas has pledged to send some Spartan warriors to the village.  He does not know where the monsters are coming from, but told you to go to the Oracle of Delphi for answers.{^n}
tagQ2DescAlt=It is long after you first left the village of Helos.  Diomedes and his people have stood or fallen on their own.  In the meantime, Leonidas and the Spartan forces have traveled to Athens.{^n}
tagQ3DescA=Leonidas has sent you to the great Oracle in the Temple of Apollo in Delphi to seek help in stopping the monster plague.{^n}
tagQ3DescAalt=In Megara, a man named Timon suggested that you should consult the great Oracle in the Temple of Apollo in Delphi in order to learn the cause of this monster invasion – and hopefully how to stop it.{^n}
tagQ3DescComplete=The Oracle delivered not just a prophecy, but a clue – to discover the source of the monsters, you must travel through the Parnassus Caves, which are not far from Delphi.{^n}
tagQ4DescA=The Oracle revealed that the source of the monsters could be learned by traveling through the Parnassus Caves, near Delphi.  What could lie beyond?{^n}
tagQ4DescB=The Oracle revealed that the source of the monsters could be learned beyond the Parnassus Caves, where a vast war-camp has been established – for an army of monsters!{^n}
tagQ4DescC=The Oracle revealed that the source of the monsters could be learned beyond the Parnassus Caves, where a vast war-camp has been established – for an army of monsters.  A frightened beggar who was hiding says at the end of the camp is another cave guarded by three great gorgons.{^n}
tagQ4DescD=The Oracle revealed that the source of the monsters could be learned beyond the Parnassus Caves, where a vast war-camp has been established – for an army of monsters.  When the three gorgon queens were slain, a mysterious woman, half turned to stone, was released from their spell.{^n}
tagQ4DescComplete=The Oracle revealed that the source of the monsters could be learned beyond the Parnassus Caves, where a vast war-camp has been established – for an army of monsters.  When the three gorgon matriarchs were slain, a mysterious woman, half turned to stone, was released from their spell.  She claimed that the monsters were all summoned by a powerful sorcerer called a Telkine.{^n}
tagQ5DescA=A dark sorcerer known as a Telkine is leading a monster army towards Athens.  Whatever his goal, Athens will need all the help it can get.{^n}
tagQ5DescB=A dark sorcerer known as a Telkine is leading a monster army towards Athens.  Even now, Leonidas stands before the gates of Athens with the Spartan forces.  He will want to hear news of the Oracle's prophecy and the Parnassus war-camp.{^n}
tagQ5DescComplete=After telling Leonidas about the Telkine and the Oracle's prophecy, he spoke of his army's failure in Sparta, and how he is working to unite the armies of Greece.  He also spoke of a great battle with the Telkine before the gates of Athens.  Halfway through the battle, the dark sorcerer mysteriously vanished.{^n}
tagQ6DescA=Leonidas has heard reports of monsters within the city walls of Athens. Head into the city and find out how the monsters got in.{^n}
tagQ6DescB=Leonidas has heard reports of monsters within the city walls of Athens.  A panicked man on the acropolis steps claims that they come from atop the Parthenon, and they  are searching for someone in the catacombs beneath it.{^n}
tagQ6DescComplete=The monsters in the catacombs were after an ancient brotherhood called the Order of Prometheus.  Their leader, Phaedrus, said they have fought forces like the Telkine since nearly the beginning of time.{^n}
tagQ7DescA=The Order of Prometheus claims the Telkine is headed for the island  of Crete.  There, beneath the Palace of Knossos, lies an ancient artifact which connects the realm of man to the realm of the gods.  Without this artifact, the gods will be blind to all that is happening beneath the heavens.  The Telkine must be stopped before he reaches the artifact.{^n}
tagQ7DescB=You have defeated the Telkine, but the conduit between the realm of man and the realm of the gods has been destroyed.  The Promethean, Kyros, must have followed you from Athens.  He has opened a secret exit from the chamber.{^n}
tagQ7DescComplete=The Telkine was defeated, but the conduit between the realm of man and the realm of the gods has been destroyed.  The gods can no longer hear the cries of mortals... or see their plight.{^n}
tagQ8DescA=The Order of Prometheus has asked you to seek the Egyptian sage Imhotep.  They believe he may be able to restore the connection to the godly realm.{^n}
tagQ8DescB=Imhotep has asked you to retrieve the Scroll of Invocation from the library in Rhakotis.  This scroll may tell how to restore the connection between the mortal and godly realms.  He said he would be waiting for you at the Temple of Ptah, near Sais.{^n}
tagQ8DescC=Imhotep has asked you to retrieve the Scroll of Invocation from the library in Rhakotis.  This scroll may tell how to restore the connection between the mortal and godly realms.  The Temple of Ptah, where you were to meet Imhotep, has been destroyed!{^n}
tagQ8DescD=There is a second Telkine in Egypt, and it has attacked the Promethean Temple of Ptah, in Sais.  It appears Imhotep escaped unharmed, and traveled on to Memphis.  Seek him there.{^n}
tagQ8DescE=The ancient Scroll of Invocation was kept safe deep beneath the Rhakotis Library.  Perhaps with this scroll, Imhotep could restore the connection between the godly and mortal realms.{^n}
tagQ8DescF=The ancient Scroll of Invocation was kept safe deep beneath the Rhakotis Library.  Perhaps with this scroll, Imhotep could restore the connection between the godly and mortal realms.  It appears that the Temple of Ptah, near Sais, was attacked, and Imhotep has fled to Memphis.{^n}
tagQ8DescComplete=There is a second Telkine in Egypt, and it has attacked the Promethean Temple of Ptah, in Sais.  Fortunately Imhotep is safe, and the Scroll of Invocation is now in his hands.  He seems fervent in his belief that the invocation ceremony will reestablish contact with the gods.{^n}
tagQ9DescA=In order for Imhotep to reconnect the mortal and the godly realms, two powerful ancient artifacts, the Hand of Balance and the Eye of Chaos, must be recovered.{^n}
tagQ9DescComplete=The invocation ceremony has failed.  A new conduit could not be forged, and while a second Telkine plagues Egypt, the gods are beyond all reach.{^n}
tagQ10DescA=A powerful Telkine has been attacking Promethian Temples throughout Egypt in search of something.  The only untouched site still guarded by the Promethians is the tomb of Ramses in the Valley of the Kings, near Thebes.  Find and defeat the Telkine.{^n}
tagQ10DescB=The Telkine was searching for an ancient artifact that was believed to be held in a Promethian Temple in Egypt.  Upon its death, it dropped a tablet covered with strange writing.  Return to Imhotep with the mysterious tablet.{^n}
tagQ10DescComplete=Your triumph over the Telkine in Egypt is darkened by the news that a third Telkine is now in Babylon.  Its purpose seems to be explained by the strange clay tablet you found, which tells of an ancient weapon of great power in Babylon's Hanging Gardens.{^n}
tagQ11DescA=A third Telkine is now in Babylon searching for the Sickle of Kronos.  Use the Scepter of Eternity that Imhotep forged from the Hand of Balance and the Eye of Chaos to create a portal in the Temple of Hatshepsut.  This portal will take you to Babylon.{^n}
tagQ11DescB=A third Telkine is now in Babylon searching for the Sickle of Kronos. The Telkine may already know its location.  Time is of the essence.{^n}
tagQ11DescC=The Telkine is already in the Hanging Gardens of Babylon!  According to the tablet, the Sickle of Kronos lies in the Temple of Marduk, atop the Gardens.  If he finds it, the Telkine will then wield great and terrible power.{^n}
tagQ11DescD=It appears the Telkine reached the Sickle first.  Both are gone, and Feiyan is lying in the Sickle Room, injured, on the floor.{^n}
tagQ11DescComplete=It appears the Telkine reached the Sickle first.  Feiyan tracked him to Babylon, but was not strong enough to stop him.  The Telkine took the Sickle and used it to blast an exit through the east wall.  Where is he headed?{^n}
tagQ12DescA=The Telkine has stolen the Sickle of Kronos and headed eastward, leaving Feiyan injured.  You must track the Telkine, learn his goal, and stop him.{^n}
tagQ12DescB=The Telkine stole the Sickle of Kronos and headed eastward. Feiyan is injured; you must track the Telkine, learn his goal, and stop him…  The Telkine travels east along the Silk Road, his purpose unknown.{^n}
tagQ12DesC=The Telkine stole the Sickle of Kronos and headed eastward. Feiyan is injured; you must track the Telkine, learn his goal, and stop him…  The Telkine was headed towards an Eastern city named Chang'an, his purpose unknown.{^n}
tagQ12DescComplete=The Telkine stole the Sickle of Kronos and fled to the East.  Feiyan, who reached Chang'an quickly by sea, says the Telkine simply vanished when it got to the city.  The Prometheans are at a loss.  What can unravel this mystery?{^n}
tagQ13DescA=Feiyan claims the Yellow Emperor may know where the Telkine went.  Legend states that the emperor lives in a jade palace at the top of Mount Qiyun –  few mortals have been admitted to the palace.{^n}
tagQ13DescB=The Yellow Emperor said that the Telkine has gone to Wusao Mountain to free the Titan, Typhon, from his prison there.  Feiyan may know the location of this mountain.{^n}
tagQ14DescA=The Telkine plans to use the Sickle to sever the adamantine chains binding the great Titan, Typhon, who is imprisoned beneath Wusao Mountain.  If he succeeds, this terrible enemy of the gods will be unleashed on the world.  Feiyan will know how to reach the mountain.{^n}
tagQ14DescB=The Telkine plans to use the Sickle to sever the adamantine chains binding the great Titan, Typhon, who is imprisoned beneath Wusao Mountain.  If he succeeds, this terrible enemy of the gods will be unleashed on the world.  Wusao Mountain lies beyond the Forest of the Ancients at the outskirts of Chang'an.{^n}
tagQ14DescComplete=The Telkine planned to use the Sickle to sever the adamantine chains binding the great Titan, Typhon, who is imprisoned beneath Wusao Mountain.  If he succeeds, this terrible enemy of the gods will be unleashed on the world.  Although the Telkine is slain, Typhon was freed, and has gone through a portal of his own making.{^n}
tagQ15DescA=Typhon has gone to Olympus, seeking revenge on the gods who spitefully imprisoned him beneath Wusao Mountain for thousands of years.  He must be stopped.{^n}
tagRumorDefaultText=Side Quest Log is Empty{^n}
tagRumorGr1Title=Medicines Waylaid{^n}
tagRumorGr1bTitle=Monstrous Brigands{^n}
tagRumorGr2Title=The Cornered Man{^n}
tagRumorGr3Title=The Lost Dowry{^n}
tagRumorGr4Title=The Ancient of War{^n}
tagRumorGr5Title=The Poisoned Spring{^n}
tagRumorGr6Title=Skeleton Raiders{^n}
tagRumorGr7Title=Goods Abandoned{^n}
tagRumorGr8Title=News of a Shipwreck{^n}
tagRumorGr9Title=The Good Centaur{^n}
tagRumorGr10Title=A Master Blacksmith{^n}
tagRumorGr11Title=The Grieving Widow{^n}
tagRumorGr12Title=Trapped in the Ruins{^n}
tagRumorGr13Title=Spartans Lost{^n}
tagRumorGr14Title=A Proper Offering{^n}
tagRumorGr15Title=Monsters in the Market{^n}
tagRumorGr16Title=Xanthippus the Healer{^n}
tagRumorGr17Title=The Undead Tyrant{^n}
tagRumorEg1Title=The Family Heirloom{^n}
tagRumorEg2Title=The Beast of Legend{^n}
tagRumorEg3Title=A Promethean Surrounded{^n}
tagRumorEg4Title=Plight of the Nile Farmers{^n}
tagRumorEg5Title=Lowest of the Low{^n}
tagRumorEg6Title=The High Priest's Request{^n}
tagRumorEg7Title=The Missing Brother{^n}
tagRumorEg8Title=Khufu's Curse{^n}
tagRumorEg9Title=A Hidden Treasure{^n}
tagRumorEg10Title=Caravan Woes{^n}
tagRumorEg11Title=The Corrupted Priest{^n}
tagRumorOr0Title=A Gargantuan Yeti{^n}
tagRumorOr1Title=The Seeds of Destruction{^n}
tagRumorOr2Title=Neanderthal Shaman{^n}
tagRumorOr3Title=Mystery in the Mountains{^n}
tagRumorOr4Title=The Village Temple{^n}
tagRumorOr5Title=Caravan in Trouble{^n}
tagRumorOr6Title=A Lesson in Despair{^n}
tagRumorOr7Title=The Child and the Raptor{^n}
tagRumorOr8Title=Peng Problems{^n}
tagRumorOr10Title=The Wealthy Collector{^n}
tagRumorOr11Title=Stalker in the Woods{^n}
tagRumorOr12Title=The Emperor's Clay Soldiers{^n}
tagRumorOr13Title=Terra Cottas At Large{^n}
tagRumorOr14Title=Behind the Waterfall{^n}
tagRumorOr15Title=The Hermit Mage{^n}
tagRumorOr16Title=Three Sisters{^n}
tagRumorOr17Title=A General in Repose{^n}
tagRumorGr1DescA=A shepherd came running up to Helos.  Monsters had attacked him as he led his flock home from pasture.  They grabbed his friend, Tellis, and dragged him into a cave by the roadside.  Find the nearby cave and save Tellis from the satyrs.{^n}
tagRumorGr1DescB=A shepherd came running up to Helos.  Monsters had attacked him as he led his flock home from pasture.  They grabbed his friend, Tellis, and dragged him into a cave by the roadside.  Luckily, he was still alive, and you were able to save him.{^n}
tagRumorGr1DescC=It appears a group of the satyrs dragged a terrified shepherd into a cave by the roadside.  Luckily, he was still alive, and you were able to save him. {^n}
tagRumorGr1DescD=A shepherd came running up to Helos.  Monsters had attacked him as led his flocks home from pasture.  They grabbed his friend, Tellis, and dragged him into a cave by the roadside.  The satyrs are dead.  Speak to Tellis.{^n}
tagRumorGr1DescE=It appears a group of the satyrs dragged a terrified shepherd into a cave by the roadside.  The satyrs are dead.  Speak to the shepherd Tellis.{^n}
tagRumorGr1bDescA=Satyrs had surrounded a man after setting torch to his home in a small lumber camp.  Fortunately you were able to defeat the satyrs.{^n}
tagRumorGr2DescA=A traveler sitting by the roadside says he is stuck because satyrs, led by a champion, guard the narrow pass ahead.  This man bears medicines for a strange illness in the village of Tegea, and many will die if the way is not cleared.  Defeat the satyr brute blocking the pass and return to Euphadimus.{^n}
tagRumorGr2DescB=Euphadimus, a traveler sitting by the roadside was stuck because satyrs, led by a champion, were guarding the narrow pass ahead.  The man bore medicines for a strange illness in the village of Tegea.  Hopefully he will reach the sick in time.{^n}
tagRumorGr3DescA=A man lost the dowry for his daughter's wedding when beasts smashed his cart and ran off with his goods.  The monsters have taken refuge in a nearby cave not far from the road.  Find and return the dowry.{^n}
tagRumorGr3DescB=A man lost the dowry for his daughter's wedding when beasts smashed his cart and ran off with his goods.  The dowry was a fine gold necklace.  Return the dowry to its owner, Theages.{^n}
tagRumorGr3DescC=A man lost the dowry for his daughter's wedding when beasts smashed his cart and ran off with his goods.  With the necklace returned to him, wedding preparations can begin.{^n}
tagRumorGr4DescA=An old Spartan named Hippias wandered from the camp, and hasn't been seen.  One of the soldiers is worried about him.  Find Hippias and make sure he is unharmed.{^n}
tagRumorGr4DescC=An old Spartan named Hippias was resting in the Pellana valley.  At first it seemed like he might be in danger, however it seems he was more of a threat to the monsters than they were to him!{^n}
tagRumorGr4DescB=An old Spartan named Hippias was resting in the Pellana valley.  At first it seemed like he might be in danger, however it seems he was more of a threat to the monsters than they were to him!  Bring the news to Euthycles in the Spartan camp.{^n}
tagRumorGr5DescA=The local spring in Tegea recently turned foul and undrinkable.  Search for the cause of the taint in the Tegea Woods.{^n}
tagRumorGr5DescB=Recently, in Tegea, the local spring has been poisoned and turned foul.  The spring belongs to the naiad Pegaea.  She explained that spiders now taint the spring's source in a cave nearby.  Destroy the spiders that dwell in the cave at the source of the spring.{^n}
tagRumorGr5DescC=Recently, in Tegea, the local spring has been poisoned and turned foul.  The spiders that tainted the spring's source are dead.  Speak to the naiad, Pegaea.{^n}
tagRumorGr5DescD=In Tegea, the local spring had turned foul and undrinkable.  The spring, which belonged to the naiad Pegaea, had been tainted by giant spiders in a cave near its source.  Now that they are gone, the spring will soon be drinkable again.{^n}
tagRumorGr6DescA=People in Megara say they have been attacked by bands of skeletons and other creatures.  Perhaps others in town have seen these undead and would know more.{^n}
tagRumorGr6DescB=People in Megara say they have been attacked by bands of skeletons and other creatures.  The undead seem to be coming from the ruins of an ancient city called Old Eleusis.  Ask around to learn more of Old Eleusis.{^n}
tagRumorGr6DescC=People in Megara say they have been attacked by bands of skeletons and other creatures.  The undead seem to be coming from the ruins of an ancient city called Old Eleusis, where an old legend tells of three princes, whose remains haunt the place.  Seek out the ancient ruins and destroy the three undead princes.{^n}
tagRumorGr6DescD=People in Megara say they have been attacked by bands of skeletons and other creatures.  Now that the three undead princes are gone, the undead should no longer wander from the ruins of an ancient city called Old Eleusis.  Bring news of your victory to Autolycus in Megara.{^n}
tagRumorGr6DescE=People in Megara say they have been attacked by bands of skeletons and other creatures.  Now that the three undead princes are gone, the undead should no longer wander from the ruins of an ancient city called Old Eleusis.{^n}
tagRumorGr7DescA=A trader was camping near a ruined city - only to be scared off by skeleton warriors!  He told you his goods were free for the taking, if you could find them.{^n}
tagRumorGr7DescB=A trader was camping near a ruined city - only to be scared off by skeleton warriors!   Although the camp was destroyed there were a few chests that remained untouched.{^n}
tagRumorGr8DescA=A sailor in Megara said his ship was wrecked by sirens.  He washed ashore with the ship's wreckage on a beach along the Halcyon Coast.  He said some of the ship's cargo washed up intact.  Look for those chests among the wreckage.{^n}
tagRumorGr8DescB=A sailor in Megara said his ship was wrecked by sirens.  He washed ashore with the ship's wreckage on a beach along the Halcyon Coast.  Some of the ship's cargo washed up intact, full of gold and equipment.{^n}
tagRumorGr9DescA=A friendly centaur named Chiron stands in the woods, untroubled by the other beasts.  He says he has a problem of some kind.  Speak to him again to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorGr9DescB=A friendly centaur named Chiron stands in the woods.  He claims a maenad named Ino grabbed his magic bow and ran into a nearby cave.  Caves seem to unnerve Chiron, and he can't follow her.  Retrieve the bow from Ino and return it to Chiron.{^n}
tagRumorGr9DescC=A friendly centaur named Chiron stands in the woods, untroubled by the other beasts.  A maenad named Ino grabbed his magic bow and ran into a nearby cave.  The wise centaur was grateful to have his bow back, and is generous in this thanks.{^n}
tagRumorGr10DescA=A villager said there is a master blacksmith, named Termerus, who lives alone off of the road to Delphi.  He will sell his weapons and armor to any who find him.{^n}
tagRumorGr10DescB=A villager said there is a master blacksmith, named Termerus, who lives alone off of the road to Delphi.  His stock of weapons and armor are unmatched anywhere else in Greece.{^n}
tagRumorGr11DescA=A widow in Delphi lost her husband to a giant boar-man.  In a dream her husband told her he could not cross into Hades to find rest among the dead while the boar-man lived.  He told her the boar-man hides now in the Parnassus Caves.  Find the boar-man and avenge her husband's death.{^n}
tagRumorGr11DescB=A widow in Delphi lost her husband to a giant boar-man.  In a dream her husband told her he could not cross into Hades to find rest among the dead while the boar-man lived.  Return to the widow Iodame with the news of the boar-man's defeat.{^n}
tagRumorGr11DescC=A widow in Delphi lost her husband to a giant boar-man.  In a dream her husband told her he could not cross into Hades to find rest among the dead while the boar-man lived.  Now that his death has been avenged, perhaps he has found his way to peaceful Elysium.{^n}
tagRumorGr12DescA=A troop of Spartan soldiers have cornered a giant Limos in some ruins near Athens.  They don't seem to have the nerve to take it on.  Aid the soldiers by defeating the Limos.{^n}
tagRumorGr12DescB=A troop of Spartan soldiers had cornered a giant Limos in some ruins near Athens.  They seemed relieved that somebody else was willing to fight it.{^n}
tagRumorGr12DescC=A troop of Spartan soldiers have cornered a giant Limos in some ruins, near Athens.  Now that it is defeated, speak with Pausanias for your reward.{^n}
tagRumorGr13DescA=A Spartan troop near Athens had sent a scouting party into a swamp nearby.  They have yet to report back.  Search for the missing soldiers in the swamp.{^n}
tagRumorGr13DescB=Several Spartan soldiers got lost while scouting a swamp on the road to Athens.  Bring word that they're alive, and are on their way back, to their troop.{^n}
tagRumorGr13DescC=A Spartan troop by some ruins had sent scouts into a nearby swamp.  The scouts are fine, they just got lost, but their troop was worried  With good directions, they will have no problem returning to their troop.{^n}
tagRumorGr13DescD=Several Spartan soldiers got lost while scouting a swamp on the road to Athens.  Their troop was glad to hear that they're alive and are on their way back.{^n}
tagRumorGr0DescA=Timon said it is proper to bring an offering when seeking an audience with the Oracle of Delphi.  He suggested an olive branch from the sacred tree in a grove near Ambrossos.  Retrieve an olive branch and present it at the Temple of Apollo in Delphi.{^n}
tagRumorGr0DescB=Timon said it is proper to bring an offering when seeking an audience with the Oracle of Delphi.  The olive branch from the sacred tree pulses with a soothing, mystical heat.  Present it at the Temple of Apollo in Delphi.{^n}
tagRumorGr0DescD=Timon said it is proper to bring an offering when seeking an audience with the Oracle of Delphi.  He suggested an olive branch from the sacred tree in a grove near Ambrossos.  Defeat the monster Arachne and take a branch from the sacred tree.  Present it at the Temple of Apollo in Delphi.{^n}
tagRumorGr0DescC=The Oracle's attendant took the offering gratefully.  It is well, for the olive branch was hard won.{^n}
tagRumorGr15DescA=There are monsters loose in the market near the base of the Acropolis.  How did they gain entrance to the city?  Find the monsters and eliminate them.{^n}
tagRumorGr15DescB=There were monsters loose in the market near the base of the Acropolis.  How did they gain entrance to the city?   Hopefully no more creatures will breach the walls of Athens.{^n}
tagRumorGr16DescA=When the Telkine came to Knossos, a poisonous fog rolled in, and many of the villagers fell sick.  Xanthippus, a healer, has been up on Tritons Ridge since the Telkine arrived.  Nobody dares fetch him because of the monsters.  Find Xanthippus and tell him of the sick villagers.{^n}
tagRumorGr16DescB=When the Telkine came to Knossos, a poisonous fog rolled in, and many of the villagers fell sick.  Xanthippus cannot heal them without his staff which he dropped in a cave when monsters ambushed him.  Retrieve the healer's staff from the cave.{^n}
tagRumorGr16DescC=The healer Xanthippus dropped his healing staff in a cave when he was ambushed by monsters.  Retrieve the healer's staff from the cave.{^n}
tagRumorGr16DescD=When the Telkine came to Knossos, a poisonous fog rolled in, and many of the villagers fell sick. Now that Xanthippus has his healing staff, he can return to the village and tend to the people of Herakleion.{^n}
tagRumorGr16DescE=Now that Xanthippus has his healing staff, he can once again tend to the sick.{^n}
tagRumorGr17DescA=Old legends in Knossos tell of a wicked tyrant named Leucus who was poisoned by a servant.  The legend claims the tyrant rose from his grave and walked the hills of Knossos.  Search for him in a cave on Tritons Ridge.{^n}
tagRumorGr17DescB=Old legends in Knossos tell of a wicked tyrant named Leucus who was poisoned by a servant.  There was some truth to the legends, but he won't trouble the living any longer.{^n}
tagRumorEg1DescA=A noble warrior refuses to leave his post to search for a sword he lost in the slums, which was passed down in his family for generations.  He puts his duty to protect the people of Rhakotis above all else.  Find the ancestral sword and return it to the warrior Anherru.{^n}
tagRumorEg1DescB=A noble warrior refused to leave his post to search for a sword he lost in the slums, which was passed down in his family for generations.  Return the recovered weapon to the warrior Anherru.{^n}
tagRumorEg1DescC=Anherru refused to go back for a sword he lost, which was passed down in his family for generations.  He puts his duty to protect the people of Rhakotis above all else.  Still, he seemed glad to have it back.  It must have meant a lot to him.{^n}
tagRumorEg2DescA=A local legend tells of a great Ancient Scorpos that lives in a cave in Wadjet Canyon, preying on travelers.  It is said that whoever kills the Scorpos will receive a magical blessing.{^n}
tagRumorEg2DescB=A local legend told of a great Ancient Scorpos in Wadjet Canyon, preying on travelers.    Now it will be no more than a tale.  The beast is dead.{^n}
tagRumorEg3DescA=Near the Temple of Ptah, a sorceress of the Order of Prometheus was surrounded and outnumbered.  She was grateful for the help in defeating the monsters.{^n}
tagRumorEg4DescA=The farmers in Egypt have a hard lot.  These poor farmers are suffering under nightly raids by a strange breed of monster:  part man, part reptile.  Find and eliminate these reptilians.{^n}
tagRumorEg4DescB=The farmers in Egypt have a hard lot.  These poor farmers are suffering under nightly raids by some half breed of creatures; part man, part reptile.   It took some work to find these reptilian raiders, but they won't be troubling the farmers any longer.{^n}
tagRumorEg5DescA=A dignified man in rags stood before a crowd of poor beggars.  He pleaded for help clearing monsters from their flimsy, unprotected homes outside the city walls.  Clear the beasts from the Beggars Quarter so it is safe once more.{^n}
tagRumorEg5DescB=A dignified man in rags stood before a crowd of poor beggars.  He pleaded for help clearing monsters from their flimsy, unprotected homes outside the city walls.  Return to Merab and let him know his home is safe once more.{^n}
tagRumorEg5DescC=A dignified man in rags stood before a crowd of poor beggars.  He pleaded for help clearing monsters from their flimsy, unprotected homes outside the city walls.  His gift of thanks was… unexpected.  Who was that man?{^n}
tagRumorEg6DescA=The High Priest of Memphis seems to want your help.  Speak to him again to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorEg6DescB=The High Priest of Memphis seems to want your help.  Speak to him again, and hopefully he will get to the point.{^n}
tagRumorEg6DescC=The High Priest of Memphis says he needs the staff of Khufu, from the pyramid in Giza, in order to restore his authority and prevent panic and chaos in Memphis.  Retrieve the staff from the Pharaoh's sarcophagus beneath the pyramid and bring it to the High Priest Zazamankh.{^n}
tagRumorEg6DescD=The High Priest of Memphis says he needs the staff of Khufu, from the pyramid in Giza, in order to restore his authority and prevent panic and chaos in Memphis.  Bring the staff to the High Priest Zazamankh.{^n}
tagRumorEg6DescE=Now that he has the Staff of Khufu, the High Priest of Memphis will use his authority for the good of the people, with wisdom and strength in these hard times.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescA=A woman in Memphis is worried – her brother is missing.  Speak with her again to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescB=A woman in Memphis is worried – her brother Unas is missing.  She fears he has gone to Giza, with the hopes of awaking an ancient family guardian for the purpose of fighting the monsters.  Search for him in the family's tomb there.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescC=A woman in Memphis was worried – she feared her brother Unas has gone to Giza, with the hopes of awaking an ancient family guardian for the purpose of fighting the monsters.  You found him terrified, standing on the threshold of the hereditary vault.  Enter the vault and find out what the problem is.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescD=A woman in Memphis was worried – she fears her brother Unas has gone to Giza, with the hopes of awaking an ancient family guardian for the purpose of fighting the monsters.  You found Unas, terrified, before his hereditary vault.  He had awakened the guardian, which was sworn to serve his family – but it fell under the madness of the Telkine.  Speak to Unas again, and return to Tathari with the news.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescE=Unas left Memphis without warning his sister, and made the dangerous trek to Giza with the hopes of awaking an ancient family guardian for the purpose of fighting the monsters.  You found Unas terrified before his hereditary vault.  He had awakened the guardian, which was sworn to serve his family – until it fell under the spell of madness cast by the Telkine.
tagRumorEg7DescF=A man named Unas stands terrified before the threshold of his hereditary vault in Giza.  Go into the vault to find out what the problem is.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescG=A man named Unas stood terrified before the threshold of his hereditary vault in Giza.  The guardian inside is now dead.  Speak to Unas.{^n}
tagRumorEg7DescH=Unas left Memphis without warning his sister, and made the dangerous trek to Giza with the hopes of awaking an ancient family guardian for the purpose of fighting the monsters.  You found Unas terrified before his hereditary vault.  He had awakened the guardian, which was sworn to serve his family – until it fell under the spell of madness cast by the Telkine.  Bring his sister Tathari news in Memphis.{^n}
tagRumorEg8DescA=A frantic man said that monsters have broken into the great pyramid.  He said that if they defile the Pharaoh's sarcophagus, it will unleash a deadly plague on the land.{^n}
tagRumorEg8DescB=A frantic nomad said that monsters have broken into the great pyramid.  If they had defiled the Pharaoh's sarcophagus, it would have unleashed a deadly plague on the land.  The monsters have been defeated.  Return to the nomad Tekenu.{^n}
tagRumorEg8DescC=A frantic nomad said that monsters have broken into the great pyramid.  If they had defiled the Pharaoh's sarcophagus, it would have unleashed a deadly plague on the land.  Thankfully, the monsters were not able to defile the sarcophagus.{^n}
tagRumorEg9DescA=A rather disreputable figure in the market bazaar mentioned some kind of tomb he found, filled with treasure – and monsters.  Search for the tomb and claim the forgotten treasure.{^n}
tagRumorEg9DescB=You have discovered an ancient unmarked tomb.  The monsters could not prevent you from discovering a great cache of treasure.{^n}
tagRumorEg10DescA=There is a man in the market here whose caravan was ambushed.  He managed to escape, but the raiders took all his goods.  Ask around Fayum to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorEg10DescB=It appears that a single dune raider tribe, led by their chieftain, Iznu, has attacked so many caravans that no more are coming.  Find and defeat Iznu.{^n}
tagRumorEg10DescC=It appears that a single dune raider tribe, led by their chieftain, Iznu, has attacked so many caravans that no more are coming.  In fact, there is a man in the market in Fayum whose caravan was just ambushed.  He got away, but the raiders took all the goods.  Find and defeat Iznu.{^n}
tagRumorEg10DescD=It appears that a single dune raider tribe, led by their chieftain, Iznu, had attacked so many caravans that no more are coming.  Now that he and his tribe are gone, perhaps the oasis town can once more receive much-needed supplies.  Return and speak to Fayum villager Pa-neb.{^n}
tagRumorEg10DescE=It appears that a single dune raider tribe, led by their chieftain, Iznu, had attacked so many caravans that no more are coming.  Now that he and his tribe are gone, perhaps the oasis town can once more receive much-needed supplies.{^n}
tagRumorEg11DescA=One brave priest stood against the Telkine, as it passed through the Temple of Seti.  Unfortunately, the priest was defeated and transformed into some kind of monster.  Search for the corrupted priest somewhere near the Valley of the Kings.{^n}
tagRumorEg11DescB=One brave priest stood against the Telkine as it passed through the Temple of Seti.   Unfortunately, the priest was defeated and transformed into some kind of monster.  The poor priest was neither alive nor human, anymore...  At least, now, he will rest peacefully.  Tell the priest Amen-nahte what has happened.{^n}
tagRumorEg11DescC=The brave priest that tried to defend the Temple of Seti from the Telkine was transformed into a terrible monster.  You have laid this creature to rest.{^n}
tagRumorOR0DescA=One of the Shangshung said he went into some ice caverns on the far side of a nearby valley.  He said he saw a gargantuan yeti there, which he had confused with some old myths of a giant that sleeps beneath a mountain.  Search for the yeti in those caves.{^n}
tagRumorOR0DescB=One of the Shangshung said he went into some ice caverns on the far side of a nearby valley.  He said he saw a gargantuan yeti there, which he had confused with some old myths of a giant that sleeps beneath a mountain.  The cries of the yeti will no longer echo through the valley.{^n}
tagRumorOR0DescC=A giant yeti dwelled in the ice caverns in Chumbi valley.  Travelers feared to pass through the caverns.  The great beast's cries will no longer echo through these icy walls.{^n}
tagRumorOr1DescA=In the wake of the Telkine's flight from Babylon, monsters have swarmed over the rolling farmland.  One farmer who had not fled watched the monsters make splinters and wreckage of all he owned.  Save his farm from the monsters.{^n}
tagRumorOr1DescB=In the wake of the Telkine's flight from Babylon, monsters have swarmed over the rolling farmland.  One farmer who had not fled watched the monsters make splinters and wreckage of all he owned.  Return to the farmer Immeru.{^n}
tagRumorOr1DescC=In the wake of the Telkine's flight from Babylon, monsters have swarmed over the rolling farmland.  One farmer who had not fled watched the monsters make splinters and wreckage of all he owned.  He was grateful to see them dealt with, but most likely his troubles are not ended.{^n}
tagRumorOr3DescA=A trader was trapped by monsters in a mountain pass.  After it was safe, he talked about the hardships of trading on the Silk Road.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescA=A Shangshung villager is troubled.  He says that nearby neanderthal tribes have suddenly grown hostile and brazen.  Many humans have been attacked.  Meanwhile, his son has been missing for several days, and he fears the worst.  Speak to other Shangshung villagers, and look for the man's son.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescB=A Shangshung villager spoke of nearby neanderthal tribes growing suddenly hostile and brazen.  His son has been missing for several days, and he fears the worst.  Meanwhile, evil spirits have taken up residence in the burial cave by the Shangshung temple.  Defeat the evil spirits.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescC=A Shangshung villager spoke of nearby neanderthal tribes growing suddenly hostile and brazen.  His son has been missing for several days, and he fears the worst.  Meanwhile, the burial cave by the Shangshung temple was plagued with evil spirits.   Speak to the villager Ang Tshe-ring and tell him you have cleansed the cave.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescD=A Shangshung villager spoke of nearby neanderthal tribes growing suddenly hostile and brazen.  His son has been missing for several days, and he fears the worst.  Meanwhile, the burial cave by the Shangshung temple was plagued with evil spirits… and the sacred ancestral weapons kept there have been stolen!  Search for the weapons and the lost son.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescL=The fog of mystery begins to clear.  When the Telkine's influence made the neanderthals mad, the Shangshung villager's son took the ancestral weapons from their place in the burial cave.  He hoped to make these mountains safe forever.  Sadly, he was not the hero he hoped to be, and neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  Now his people are less safe than before.  Find and defeat the Neanderthals who took the sacred weapons.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescE=When the Telkine's influence made the neanderthals mad, a Shangshung villager's son took the ancestral weapons from their place in the burial cave, hoping to make these mountains safe.  His plan failed when neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  The neanderthals were defeated and the weapons recovered.  Speak to Kilu Tem-ba in the Shangshung Village.  {^n}
tagRumorOr4DescF=When the Telkine's influence made the neanderthals mad, a Shangshung villager's son took the ancestral weapons from their place in the burial cave, hoping to make these mountains safe.  His plan failed when neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  Now that the greatest danger has passed, do the Shangshung really want weapons they cannot master?{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescG=It appears that evil spirits have taken up in the burial cave by the Shangshung temple.  Defeat the evil spirits.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescH=The burial cave by the Shangshung temple was plagued with evil spirits… and the sacred ancestral weapons kept there have been stolen!  Search for the stolen weapons.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescI=A young man stood in the wilderness, shaken and dejected.  It seems he took the sacred ancestral weapons from their place in the Shangshung temple burial cave.  He hoped to make these mountains safe forever.  Sadly, he was not the hero he hoped to be, and neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  Find and defeat the Neanderthals who took the sacred weapons.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescJ=A young man stood in the wilderness, shaken and dejected.  It seems he took the sacred ancestral weapons from their place in the Shangshung temple burial cave.  He hoped to make these mountains safe forever.  Sadly, he was not the hero he hoped to be, and neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  With the ancestral weapons out of neanderthal hands, the greatest danger is gone.  Do the Shangshung really want weapons they cannot master?  Speak to the distraught young man.{^n}
tagRumorOr4DescK=A young man stood in the wilderness, shaken and dejected.  It seems he  took the ancestral weapons from their place in the burial cave, hoping to make these mountains safe.  His plan failed when neanderthals ambushed him, taking the sacred weapons.  The neanderthals were defeated and the weapons recovered.  Find and speak to his father, Kilu Tem-ba, in the Shangshung Village.{^n}
tagRumorOr5DescA=A trader was trapped by monsters in a mountain pass.  After it was safe, he talked about the difficulties of trading.{^n}
tagRumorOr6DescA=A proud warrior was standing in the woods, fighting bravely but completely without hope.  He seemed to want to die.  Speak with him to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorOr6DescB=A proud warrior was standing in the woods, fighting bravely but completely without hope.  He seemed to want to die.  After talking with him, he seemed to take heart and overcome his despair.  He began to see that the warrior is bound by duty to protect the defenseless.  By saving the innocent, the warrior makes hope where there was none.{^n}
tagRumorOr7DescA=A terrified woman near a burned out village watched a raptor wander between her and her playing child.  There was nothing she could do.  Slay the beast before it notices the child.{^n}
tagRumorOr7DescB=A terrified woman near a burned out village watched a raptor wander between her and her playing child.  There was nothing she could do.  No words could describe the joy of the mother and child, safely together again.{^n}
tagRumorOr8DescA=A group of soldiers sent to secure the Great Wall are held up, because they dare not face a fearsome peng that has landed on the wall.  Help the soldiers defeat the peng.{^n}
tagRumorOr8DescB=A group of soldiers sent to secure the Great Wall were held up, because they did not dare face a fearsome Peng that has landed on the wall. Bring word of their progress and the peng's death to the commander, farther down the wall.{^n}
tagRumorOr8DescC=A group of soldiers sent to secure the Great Wall were held up, because they did not dare face a fearsome Peng that has landed on the wall.  Their commander was glad to hear of their progress.  He heard nothing of their fear, but no harm is done.{^n}
tagRumorOr10DescA=There is a wealthy man in Zhidan village named Lu Buwei who seems to be interested in any able traveler.  Speak to him again to learn more.{^n}
tagRumorOr10DescB=There is a wealthy man in Zhidan village named Lu Buwei who seems to be interested in any able traveler.  He mentioned that he greatly desires a valuable item buried deep in a cave in Jingyang Woods – and that he would pay handsomely for it.  Find the item and bring it to him.{^n}
tagRumorOr10DescC=There was a wealthy man in Zhidan village named Lu Buwei who greatly desired a valuable item buried deep in a cave in Jingyang Woods.   He said he would pay handsomely for it.  Lu Buwei proved true to his word.{^n}
tagRumorOr11DescA=A local rumor speaks of a giant beast that walks deep in the Jingyang Woods, which flank the road to Chang'an.  Search for it in the forest depths.{^n}
tagRumorOr11DescB=A giant beast walked deep in the Jingyang Woods.  It will trouble lost travelers no more.{^n}
tagRumorOr12DescA=In the Mausoleum of the Great Emperor, the army of terra cotta soldiers have come to life.  They are wreaking havoc in the city of Chang'an.  Enter the Mausoleum and put a stop to the chaos.{^n}
tagRumorOr12DescB=In the Mausoleum of the Great Emperor, the army of terra cotta soldiers had come to life.  An evil wraith named Bandari was apparently behind this mischief.  Thankfully, no more statues will rise and walk due to his magic.  Return to the captain Ma Feibai with the news.{^n}
tagRumorOr12DescC=In the Mausoleum of the Great Emperor, the army of terra cotta soldiers had come to life.  An evil wraith named Bandari was apparently behind this mischief.  Thankfully, no more statues will rise and walk due to his magic.{^n}
tagRumorOr13DescA=Many terra cotta soldiers are loose in the city.  The guards are superstitious and won't go near them, so they cannot secure the rest of the city.  Defeat these clay soldiers throughout Chang'an.{^n}
tagRumorOr13DescB=Many terra cotta soldiers were loose in the city.  The guards were superstitious and wouldn't go near them.  With the clay soldiers gone, the soldiers can return to defending the city.  Return to the guard Wai Zhen for your reward.{^n}
tagRumorOr13DescC=Many terra cotta soldiers were  loose in the city.  The superstitious guards wouldn't go near them, so they were unable to secure the rest of the city.  The reward for removing the clay soldiers was generous.{^n}
tagRumorOr14DescA=A man named Liu Xu described a cave behind a waterfall of the Jinghe River, where the ancestors of his family were interred.  Evil spirits now attack any who go near, and the man cannot revere his ancestors.  Find the cave and defeat the spirits.{^n}
tagRumorOr14DescB=A man named Liu Xu described a cave behind a waterfall of the Jinghe River, where the ancestors of his family were interred.  Evil spirits had infested the cave, but his family may now return there to make offerings.  Speak to Liu Xu with the news.{^n}
tagRumorOr14DescC=A man named Liu Xu described a cave behind a waterfall of the Jinghe River, where the ancestors of his family were interred.  Evil spirits had infested the cave, but his family may now return there to making offerings.{^n}
tagRumorOr15DescA=A peaceful Taoist mage lived by himself in this valley.  He used to visit the village monthly, but no one has seen him for some time.  Look for his home in the Jinghe Valley.{^n}
tagRumorOr15DescB=A peaceful Taoist mage lived by himself in this valley.  Nobody had seen him – and with good reason.  His home was burnt and ravaged by the monsters.{^n}
tagRumorOr16DescA=A strange girl on the mountain path did not fear the monsters.  She said she could not be harmed.  She spoke of her sisters that lived in the Jinghe Wetlands.  Look for her sisters there.{^n}
tagRumorOr16DescB=A strange girl on the mountain path did not fear the monsters.  She said she could not be harmed.   By the cottage you found one of her sisters terribly upset.  The third sister is in trouble.  Find and save her.{^n}
tagRumorOr16DescBAlternate=A beautiful young woman stood by a humble cottage, terribly upset.  Her sister is in trouble.  Find and save her.{^n}
tagRumorOr16DescC=Once safe, the woman told her story :  long ago, the great sage Lao-Jun traveled the lands as a beggar.  None in the land offered him food or shelter - none but these three good sisters.  In return, he gave them each a magic seed, and said that when they ate the seeds, no harm would come to them, so long as they did no harm.  Alas, Ru Zhao saw a tiger-man about to kill a deer, and she struck and killed it.  The spell was broken, her immortality lost.  Bring this news to her sister, Li Hua.{^n}
tagRumorOr16DescD=Long ago, the great sage Lao-Jun traveled the lands as a beggar.  None in the land offered him food or shelter - none but these three good sisters.  In return, he gave them each a magic seed, and said that when they ate the seeds, no harm would come to them, so long as they did no harm.  Alas, Ru Zhao saw a tiger-man about to kill a deer, and she struck and killed it.  The spell was broken, her immortality lost. {^n}
tagRumorOr17DescA=A man who was once a powerful general has fled to the wilderness, where he contemplates the passage of existence.  He mentioned that he abandoned his weapons and armor in a cave nearby.  Look for them there.{^n}
tagRumorOr17DescB=A man who was once a powerful general has fled to the wilderness, where he contemplates the passage of existence.  You found his abandoned weapons and armor in a cave.{^n}
tagRumorGr1Level=Helos
tagRumorGr2Level=Sparta
tagRumorGr3Level=Megara
tagRumorGr4Level=Delphi
tagRumorGr5Level=Athens
tagRumorGr6Level=Knossos
tagRumorEg1Level=Rhakotis
tagRumorEg2Level=Lower Nile
tagRumorEg3Level=Memphis
tagRumorEg4Level=Giza
tagRumorEg5Level=Fayum Oasis
tagRumorEg6Level=Thebes
tagRumorOr1Level=Babylon
tagRumorOr2Level=Silk Road
tagRumorOr3Level=Great Wall
tagRumorOr4Level=Chang'an
tagRumorOr5Level=Qiyun
tagRumorOr6Level=Forest of the Ancients
tagQuestItem01=Eye of Chaos
tagQuestItem02=Hand of Balance
tagQuestItem03=Scroll of Invocation
tagQuestItem04=Cuneiform Tablet
tagQuestItem05=Sacred Olive Branch
tagQuestItem06=Scepter of Eternity
tagQuestItem07=Sickle of Kronos
tagQuestItemDescr01=A wild fire burns in the heart of the luminous green stone.
tagQuestItemDescr02=The Hand is strangely weighty, as if under the constant pull of some unseen world.
tagQuestItemDescr03=The ancient papyrus is covered with heavy, ornate pictograms.
tagQuestItemDescr04=The strange wedge-shaped markings in the clay resemble birds' feet.
tagQuestItemDescr05=A small branch taken from the sacred olive tree above Helicos Pass.
tagQuestItemDescr06=Formed from the Eye of Chaos and the Hand of Balance, the scepter seems to tremble gently with the vast power it contains.
tagQuestItemDescr07=A legendary artifact of mysterious and unspeakable power.
tagQuestObject01=Eternity Altar
tagQuestObject02=Portal to Babylon
tagQuestObject03=Portal to Thebes
tagQuestObject04=Typhon's Portal
tagQuestObject05=Sacred Olive Tree
tagQuestObject06=Khufu's Sarcophagus
tagJournalItem01=Dowry Necklace
tagJournalItem02=Chiron's Bow
tagJournalItem03=Staff of Xanthippus
tagJournalItem04=Family Sword of Anherru
tagJournalItem05=Staff of Khufu
tagJournalItem06=Jade Figurine
tagJournalItemDescr01=A simple necklace, wrought of fine gold.
tagJournalItemDescr02=This sturdy and beautiful bow appears to have been carefully built by its owner.
tagJournalItemDescr03=The magical healer's staff fills all who touch it with a warm, soothing glow.
tagJournalItemDescr04=Although scratched and old, this fine sword is covered with intricate hieroglyphs and designs.
tagJournalItemDescr05=The great hero's staff is covered with precious stones and intricate markings, and a dusky sense of power hangs around it.
tagJournalItemDescr06=Ancient and graceful, the tiny jade carving glows coolly in almost any light.
tagEndPortal=Victory Portal
tagEndChest01=Typhon's Essence
tagEndChest02=Mystical Orb
tagJournalUpdate=Side Quest Updated :
tagQuestUpdate=Main Quest Updated :
tagQuestUnsolvable=Cannot Complete :
tagQuestAdded=Quest Added :
tagQuestComplete=Quest Complete :
tagLogUnsolvable=You cannot complete this quest in this multiplayer session.{^n}(When playing as a group, form a party to share quests.)
tagQError01=Quest {%t0} Reset
tagQError02=Invalid Quest Data
tagQError03=Quest State Reset
tagRewardGold=Gold
tagRewardExperience=Experience
tagRewardAttribute=Attribute Points
tagRewardSkill=Skill Point(s)
tagReward=Reward :
tagLogReward=You Will Receive :
tagLogRewardComplete=Rewarded :
tagLogGold=Gold
tagLogExperience=Experience
tagLogAttPoints=Attribute Points
tagLogSkillPoints=Skill Point(s)
tagLogInventoryBag=Inventory Bag
tagLogInventoryBagDesc=This bag adds an additional 40 slots to your inventory.
tagLogMagicWeapon=Magical Weapon
tagLogMagicArmor=Magical Armor
tagLogMagicGeneric01=Magical Item
tagLogMagicGeneric02=Magical Equipment
tagLogRelic=Completed Relic
tagLogRelicShard=Relic Shard
tagLogCharm=Completed Charm
tagLogCharmShard=Partial Charm
tagLogJewelry=Magical Jewelry
tagLogHealth=Health Point Bonus
tagLog Health=Health Point Bonus
tagLogEnergy=Energy Point Bonus
tagLogResistance=Bonus Resistance
tagLogRing=Powerful Ring
tagLogAmulet=Powerful Amulet
tagJG10RewardNormal=+75 Health
tagJG10RewardEpic=+150 Health
tagJG10RewardLegendary=+200 Health
tagJG14RewardNormal01=+5% Permanent Fire Resistance
tagJG14RewardNormal02=+5% Permanent Cold Resistance
tagJG14RewardNormal03=+5% Permanent Lightning Resistance
tagJG14RewardNormal04=+5% Permanent Poison Resistance
tagJG14RewardEpic01=+7% Permanent Fire Resistance
tagJG14RewardEpic02=+7% Permanent Cold Resistance
tagJG14RewardEpic03=+7% Permanent Lightning Resistance
tagJG14RewardEpic04=+7% Permanent Poison Resistance
tagJG14RewardLegendary01=+5% Permanent Elemental Resistance
tagJO06RewardNormal=+3 Bonus Damage to all Weapons
tagJO06RewardEpic=+5 Bonus Damage to all Weapons
tagJO06RewardLegendary=+8 Bonus Damage to all Weapons
tagRewardHealthMana=Health and Energy Restored
I=I
II=II
III=III
IV=IV
V=V
VI=VI
VII=VII
VIII=VIII
IX=IX
X=X
XI=XI
XII=XII
XIII=XIII
XIV=XIV
XV=XV
