// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagGadir_aulosplayer_A1=Do you like me playing the aulos? The merchants tell that this instrument was invented by Athena herself. But she threw it away after seeing what blowing it made her face look like! Luckily for you, we bandsmen don't mind looking silly if you enjoy it!
x3tagGadir_aulosplayer_A2=They say the first mortal to pick up the aulos was a satyr named Marsias. He was a skillful player and captivated many with its sound, so much that one night he would challenge the god Apollo and his lyre, in what he thought was a playful bet. But Apollo won, then strung him up from a tree and punished him horribly for his hubris!
x3tagGadir_aulosplayer_A3=It was a cruel lesson, yes. But much like with Arachne and her weaving, Marsias should have known better than to challenge a god.
x3tagGadir_aulosplayer_A4=You greeks have such grim stories... but I kinda like them.
x3tagGadir_aulosplayer_A7=Enjoy the performance!
x3tagGadir_storyteller_A1=By the favor of the muses, I will tell of the task that first brought lord Herakles to our humble city. It was to Erytheia that he was sent, just west of here, to steal the red cattle of the giant Geryon, as his tenth and final labour. {^n}{^n}Geryon was a fearsome warrior with the bodies of three men growing from his hips! So he fought with three shields, three spears, and three helmets on his heads! And he would have won their fight if cunning Herakles had not used the poison of the Hydra to bring him down.
x3tagGadir_storyteller_A2=After acquiring the cattle, Herakles had to herd it back through here, which caused quite the commotion, especially when Hera interfered as she often did. And then Herakles learned that he was not finished, but that two additional labours were required of him... but that is another story.
x3tagGadir_storyteller_A7=Have you heard the stories of Herakles' other labours?
x3tagGadir_historian_A1=If you are a treasure hunter, you may also have an interest in the mystical kingdom of Tartessos, just north of here. They say it was so rich in silver that they named their ruler the Silver King - Arganthonios. {^n}{^n}At some point it vanished, however, and nobody quite knows why.
x3tagGadir_historian_A2=Some say it was a great flood that wiped them out, but in that time the scholars did not keep any written records yet.
x3tagGadir_historian_A3=The northern parts of the Necropolis are very old, definitely older than Gadir. As such, they may be Tartessian... and may once have been full of silver.
x3tagGadir_historian_A7=I am still trying to find out more.
x3tagGadir_historian_B1=You found Tartessian artifacts in the tombs? Oh, that is great! So my theory was correct!
x3tagAtlas_storyteller_A1=Ah, you come from Gadir? With the Phoenicians? They really do travel to every land selling their purple dye. And successfully so, even though they charge more than its weight in gold. {^n}{^n}Did you know they harvest it from the shells of sea snails? According to legend, their goddess Tanit discovered the dye while out walking on the beach with Melqart, patron god of Tyre. She noticed that the mouth of her dog was stained purple after biting into some washed up mollusks. Loving the color, she asked Melqart to dye her a garment, and that was the beginning of their famous craft.
x3tagAtlas_storyteller_A2=They also sell very good wine.
x3tagAtlas_storyteller_A3=We Ghumāra also trade with them. Luckily the Phoenicians keep to the coasts, so they are not a threat to our lands.
x3tagAtlas_storyteller_A7=Personally, I do prefer blue dye.
x3tagGarden_storyteller_A1=What, the garden? Yes, it lies to the west. - As far west as one can go. But we always give that place a wide berth. It is the end of the world, they say, and the daughters of Nyx are guarding it fiercely! {^n}{^n}You would be a fool to enter. A fool, you hear me? Though I can tell you more about it.
x3tagGarden_storyteller_A2=The Hesperides were fathered by the titan Atlas, though some say it was the Hesperos, the star of the evening. In any case Atlas was the only one who ever managed to take their apples away for a while. And he did so for lord Herakles, while he stood in for Atlas in his usual task of holding the world.
x3tagGarden_storyteller_A3=The tree in the center of the garden was a wedding gift from Gaia to Zeus himself, and its apples are said to be the reason for the gods' immortality. But I guess you know that, because that is what all silly fools who go there are after.
x3tagGarden_storyteller_A4=There are more dangers in that place than the nymphs of the evening, even though you will find that they are not the gentle maidens people imagine! A spawn of Echidna also guards it, a foul monster with several heads!
x3tagGarden_storyteller_A7=Do not go there. Take it from me, it is not worth it.
x3tagAtlas_warrior_A1=Where are you from? Carthage? Then go back there. Or better yet, all the way back to Canaan. We already see too many of your kind coming here.
x3tagAtlas_warrior_A2=We people of the Rif like to keep to ourselves. We do not need your fancy clothes, nor your strange child-devouring gods!
x3tagAtlas_warrior_A7=Go away.
x3tagAtlantis_priest_X1=No... no... {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A1=Aaaah! {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A2=They... did it. Somehow... {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A3=They summoned her! {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A4=They should not have done it! {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A5=They should not have... the power. {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A6=N... no! {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlantis_priest_A7=Poseidon save us!
