// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagMq_Title=The City of Atlas
x3tagMq_Desc_A=Marinos has invited you to join his search for Atlantis. But first you must must travel to Gadir and gather some clues on how to get there. Take the boat to Gadir and Marinos will tell you more.
x3tagMq_Desc_B=Having arrived in Gadir, Marinos tells you that the key to Atlantis is finding the Journal of Herakles. It is rumoured to be buried in the Necropolis to the north of Gadir. You should talk to the Head Priest at the temple further up the road.
x3tagMq_Desc_C=Having arrived in Gadir, Marinos tells you that the key to Atlantis is finding the Journal of Herakles. The Head Priest has told you that the Journal is buried with old King Arganthonios in the Necropolis, north of town. However, they seem to be having a ghost problem so you should proceed with caution.
x3tagMq_Desc_D=Having arrived in Gadir, Marinos tells you that the key to Atlantis is finding the Journal of Herakles. After defeating King Arganthonios you picked up the Journal and should now return to Marinos in Gadir.
x3tagMq_Desc_E=Reading the Journal of Herakles, Marinos found out that two artifacts are needed to get to Atlantis. You first need to find an ancient navigational instrument located somewhere on Gaulos. A boat should be ready for you on the eastern dock in Gadir. Explore Gaulos and find the artifact.
x3tagMq_Desc_F=Reading the Journal of Herakles, Marinos found out that two artifacts are needed to get to Atlantis. You found the first artifact below the megalithic temples of Gaulos and should return it to Marinos in Gadir.
x3tagMq_Desc_G=Reading the Journal of Herakles, Marinos found out that two artifacts are needed to get to Atlantis. The second artifact he needs is a Golden Apple from the mythical Garden of the Hesperides, far to the west. A boat that will take you to Aithiopia is waiting on the dock next to the one Marinos boat is moored at. You should explore the Atlas Mountains to see if you can find the Garden.
x3tagMq_Desc_H=Reading the Journal of Herakles, Marinos found out that two artifacts are needed to get to Atlantis. The second artifact he needs is the Golden Apple from the mythical Garden of the Hesperides, which you found on the western edge of the world. You picked up the Golden Apple and should return to Marinos in Gadir.
x3tagMq_Desc_I=Marinos is clearly shaken and impressed that you have managed to retrieve both the navigational instrument and the golden apple. At last, it is time to sail for Atlantis! Marinos has been preparing his ship for this voyage for a long time.
x3tagMq_Desc_J=After travling through the ocean storms, you have finally made it to Atlantis. The island is probably full of secrets and Marinos tells you to go inland and scout out the surroundings…
x3tagMq_Desc_K=You have met the last living Atlantean and he told you that the island is beseiged by dark powers centered around the ruined Temple of Poseidon in the highest district. The temple is sealed off by a spell that can only be broken by neutralizing the leaders of the three factions occupying the city. Their names are Isagonus, Caanthus, and Vvisssllisss.
x3tagMq_Desc_L=You have met the last living Atlantean and he told you that the island is beseiged by dark powers centered around the ruined Temple of Poseidon in the highest district. As you killed the three leaders, the spell is now broken and you can enter the Temple of Poseidon to see what it is that the Serpentoid priests are doing in there.
x3tagMq_Desc_M=Inside the ruined Temple of Poseidon in the heart of Atlantis, you defeated the ancient god Tiamat which the Serpentoids had somehow managed to summon from the Abyss to whatever evil end. Ascend to the Acropolis to see what lies beyond the temple.
x3tagMq_Desc_N=After defeating Tiamat, you discovered the true mastermind behind the Serpentoid cult and the summoning - a fourth Telkine, who brutally killed the last Atlantean before making his escape. Chase him down and finally put an end to their evil schemes!
x3tagMq_Desc_O=The last Telkine lies dead, his evil plan foiled and his allies defeated. And with Poseidon's blessing, Atlantis can finally rest beneath the sea. Well done!
x3tagMq_marinos=Marinos ~ Intrepid Explorer
x3tagMq_HighPriest=Azmelqart ~ Head Priest of the Cult of Herakles
x3tagMq_Mehedi=Mehedi ~ Bedouin
x3tagMq_Acrocatus=Acrocatus ~ The Last Atlantean
x3tagMq_MagicCompass=Ancient Navigational Device
x3tagMq_MagicCompassDesc=Holding the device makes your head spin and you feel mysterious forces tugging at it, pointing you in the direction of Atlantis.
x3tagMq_GoldenApple=Golden Apple
x3tagMq_GoldenAppleDesc=It appears in the form of an almost golden sphere but inside you can faintly hear an ocean storm raging.
x3tagMq_LostDiary=Journal of Herakles
x3tagMq_LostDiaryDesc=The ancient handwriting has mostly faded with time. You wonder what other secrets this journal once held.
x3tagMQ_FirstDiscipleSarco=Sarcophagus of King Arganthonios
x3tagMQ_Isagonus=Isagonus ~ Commander of the Tritons
x3tagMQ_Caanthus=Caanthus ~ Princeps of the Potamoi
x3tagMQ_Vvisssllisss=Vvisssllisss ~ Serpentoid High Priest
