// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagRhodes_marinos_A1=Hello there hero, fancy meeting you at a place like this... You are the one who opened that fascinating portal in the Temple of Hatshepsut, are you not? {^n}{^n}Let me introduce myself, I am Marinos. I am an explorer of ancient places. I've visited many a strange place in this ship of mine. Perhaps I can entice you to go on an adventure with me? You see, your reputation precedes you, and I believe my latest venture is bound to become... perilous.
x3tagRhodes_marinos_B1=I've come across old manuscripts that I have only partially translated, but I'm pretty sure the path to an old kingdom is described within them... A kingdom of unimagined technology and wonder... I'm talking about the fallen realm of Atlantis! One can only begin to imagine what secrets are hidden there... A prize well worth seeking. However, I'm in need of some assistance. {^n}{^n}You see, so far I've only been able to figure out that the key to deciphering these documents lies in another manuscript; the Journal of Herakles, functioning as a sort of cipher. I believe this text can be found in the city of Gadir which is said to have been founded by the man himself, far away west in the peninsula of Iberia. {^n}{^n}I would ask you to join me in exploring this city and, gods willing, being part of the rediscovery of Atlantis! Think of the fame and fortune that will be ours!
x3tagRhodes_marinos_B2=I am not a fool! These manuscripts seem genuine. I got them from a trader in Sais, where the local temple has recently been giving away some of their inventory. Or so he said. 
x3tagRhodes_marinos_B3=It would be nice to get going again. That Kraken was a sight to behold, but now that it is dead there is not much more to see here. {^n}{^n}On the other hand, it taught me that bringing a monster slayer along might be a good idea!
x3tagRhodes_marinos_B7=When you are ready to go to Gadir, please speak with my captain. A stout fellow is he, stranger to neither tide nor squall.
x3tagRhodes_agapetos_X1=Excuse me! {^n}{^n}
x3tagRhodes_agapetos_A1=Excuse me, stranger. The captain of the strange ship over there told me to look out for any capable warriors coming to town. Says he has an offer to make.
x3tagRhodes_agapetos_A7=There at the beach, just outside the city gate.
x3tagGadir_marinos_A1=Here we are! The city of Gadir, rich with dyes and wine. Seems like a nice enough place to settle down in. But we're here for business! As you know, I can't decipher the manuscripts without a certain book; the Journal of Herakles, said to be found somewhere in this area... {^n}{^n}To learn more about the whereabouts of this diary I think we should seek out Azmelqart, the current head priest. He is sure to know where the book is, or at least have some clue. He ought to be up by the temple, further into the city.
x3tagGadir_marinos_A7=Find Azmelqart by the temple!
x3tagGadir_marinos_B1=You return! My friend, you are wonderful. Now let's just have a look here... Yes, now I understand it all. The path ahead will be fraught with danger, good thing I have you! {^n}{^n}We need to find two artifacts to open the path to Atlantis, one will help us find our way, the other will still the lethal whirlpools that are churning around the island ever since Poseidon struck down the city in anger. {^n}{^n}The first item is hidden on a small island not too far from here, known as Gaulos, it was once a colony of the Atlanteans. It seems this island had a specific purpose, serving as a religious complex where rites and sacrifices were made... {^n}{^n}As it happens, I already know a captain who frequents those waters. Just tell him you're with me and he'll take you along. His ship is moored on the southern coast, just beyond the harbour.
x3tagGadir_marinos_B7=Return when you have found the artifact! I'll wait here. Maybe I can make some more connections at the local wine-bar over there...
x3tagGadir_marinos_C1=What a curious device! This thing is the key to our fortune? And it was guarded by snakes? Ha, I can't believe it, but who am I to challenge the Atlanteans... Now we only need the other artifact, and this one might prove a tad bit harder to procure I'm afraid... {^n}{^n}You see, we, well you, need to steal a golden apple from the... Garden of the Hesperides. According to the scrolls, offering this fruit to the ocean will appease the violent sea spirits that nest around Atlantis. This should ensure our safe passage... {^n}{^n}I have already made some arrangements. On the northern pier of the harbour a ship awaits. It will take you to the north coast of Aithiopia, from there you must find your way on foot. The Garden is said to exist on the western edge of the world, beyond the Mountains of Atlas.
x3tagGadir_marinos_C2=The Garden is a place steeped in myth, not even Herakles dared to desecrate its boundaries himself... It is said to be guarded by the dragon Ladon, as well as the handmaids of the gods - the Hesperides. I'm not making this up, it is all in the books, I promise!
x3tagGadir_marinos_C7=I'm sorry, but I'm not going near that place... mythical beasts are your special area. But then again, you do great work when left to your own devices!
x3tagGadir_marinos_D1=Oh! You scared me, I thought you were a goner for sure... Not yet maybe... {^n}{^n}So, what were they like, the Hesperides? Beautiful beyond mortal comprehension no doubt... Wait, don't tell me, I see you have brought something! Ohh, you actually found it did you? It looks so... ordinary. And not quite golden. I don't think that is an apple... {^n}{^n}Well Hero, I guess this is it... Never thought the day would come, but according to the texts we have all that we need. Are you ready to go to Atlantis? I know I'm not, Gadir is treating me well... But forget about that. Let us set sail and go forth boldly, no time like the present!
x3tagGadir_marinos_D7=There is no time like the present!
x3tagNecropolis_azmelqart_A1=Hail traveller! You gaze upon the chiseled muscularity of the head priest of the Cult of Herakles, patron deity of this city. Azmelqart be my name! {^n}{^n}You search for the Journal of Herakles you say? Ah, you mean the Sacred Texts! They can be found in the tomb of the legendary king Arganthonios the Old, of course! A wise king ruling the lands before either greek or phoenician settlers walked upon these shores. He is said to have been the first disciple of Herakles... {^n}{^n}I would take you to his grave myself but... Well, to be frank, I am afraid our beautiful burial grounds are currently closed to visitors. We're... doing some maintenance work. Now bother me no longer, you are disturbing my exercise routine!
x3tagNecropolis_azmelqart_B1=...Okay, you got me! We're having a bit of a ghost problem right now. The dead have grown restless and walk again! Ill omens have been observed! Mayhaps the hound of the Underworld has slipped his bonds... What can mere mortals do against such sorcery, I ask you?! And to make matters worse, it seems that old King Arganthonios himself has crawled out of his sarcophagus in search of blood, leaving the Sacred Texts unguarded. {^n}{^n}You can handle it, you say? I suppose I could let you borrow the Sacred Texts if you make it, although I doubt it... But I can tell that you've already made up your mind... The Necropolis lies farther inland, just exit the city through the main gate and follow the path, it should be easy enough to find. May Herakles give you strength!
x3tagNecropolis_azmelqart_B7=I really do need to continue my exercise.
x3tagNecropolis_azmelqart_C1=Welcome back. I am impressed, and grateful. You've cleared the graveyard of the undead, a labour befitting Herakles himself! Perhaps the Sacred Texts belonged with you all along.
x3tagNecropolis_azmelqart_C7=Let's flex!
x3tagAithiopia_mehedi_A1=Welcome friend! You seem weary, sit down for a moment and share our hospitality. I think you have travelled a long way, my friend... Yet you hail from the lands of Yunan, a stone's throw across the sea. Tell me, what journey brings a person this far?
x3tagAithiopia_mehedi_A2=You search for the Garden of the Hesperides? Hmm... Across the mountains ancient forests linger... Our people seldom go there, but perhaps your path does. Follow the mountain trail and you will find your way.
x3tagAithiopia_mehedi_A7=Good luck to you and your family!
x3tagAithiopia_hesperideguard_A1=Halt! You are not welcome here. If you go any further, you will be punished!
x3tagAithiopia_hesperideguard_A7=Leave!
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_A1=Uhm, is it safe? Am I dreaming, or is this really Atlantis? {^n}{^n}I can't believe it! We braved the open sea and the whirlpools, yet emerged triumphant. Yes, this must be Atlantis, I can feel it! Why don't you go explore inland and see what you can find. Report back here if you come across anything interesting!
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_A7=Ahem... Well... Look at the geology of this place. It is not volcanic, quite remarkable... So much to see...
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_B1=You met a native! Oh my, well... Better follow their instructions I guess... You're the vanguard of this expedition after all. Just don't do anything I wouldn't do!
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_B2=To be honest, I am quite curious about that cult of snake people, ever since you first encountered them in the temple on Gaulos. I don't know who they are, but many cultures tell of a deity in the form of a snake - Apophis in Egypt, the old legend of Illuyanka, and even the Celts and the Norse. {^n}{^n}And the one thing they all have in common... is that they are an embodiment of Evil. 
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_B3=Ah, let's just hope I'm wrong. There are exceptions to the rule after all, like the snakes of your Asklepios. Maybe these guys also practice healing?
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_C1=I talked to your friend, quite a nice fellow, albeit a bit gloomy... I understand some foreign power was threatening the island, but now that this is over, the whole island will slowly sink into the sea... That's just too bad! And yet we were most fortunate! I've already found some quite interesting treatises on statehood and the follies of democracy, interesting reads I promise!
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_C2=Well, I guess our journey ends here. Although it has been hard, I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did. The rewards have been quite exciting to be sure, and there are still much more to be found, if I could only find the time... But alas, Acrocatus, whom I've grown quite accustomed to, tells me we must leave soon, lest we be swept up in the vortex that will form when the island sinks...
x3tagAtlantis_marinos_C7=The ship is ready, and it is time to leave. I suppose you will just take one of your fancy portals to get back to Rhodes... but let it be said that it was a pleasure to travel with you!
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_S1=Oh... a human!
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_A1=Hello, human. I have been wondering how long it would take until someone finds us here. I am the sole survivor of this once great city of Atlantis, my name long forgotten. Poseidon spared me to bear witness of what has happened here, of how his rage ended our civilization. Many centuries have I existed here in solitude, unable to escape... {^n}{^n}I was once chief artificer of this place. Many a wonderful thing have I built, too wonderful... We challenged the God of the Seas with ships built out of metal that could move without his winds. I've seen oceans and lands beyond your known world, where strange cultures grow... Needless to say, our city became rich, but our leaders were corrupted. Our empire became an affront to the gods and we were finally punished for our greed... {^n}{^n}And lately it seems more trouble is brewing... Evil miscreants have come to defile the ruins of our once beautiful island. How they found their way I do not know, but they are here. Have you come to stop them I wonder?
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_B1=The Tritones, the Serpentoids, the Potamoi... A coalition of evil has claimed our once beautiful city. Their commanders bicker and squabble, yet their might is formidable... Something is uniting them, unseen and in the shadows. Its power emanates from the Temple of Poseidon at the heart of Atlantis, but nobody can get inside. {^n}{^n}All three of their leaders were there when they created the magical seal. Each leader had a part in it, so all of them may be needed to break it.
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_B7=Find the three leaders. Only then can you uncover the temple's secrets.
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_C1=You've killed the commanders, all three of them? That is a relief! Atlantis may yet be free again! {^n}{^n}The scrolls they held must together form the ritual that is the key to the Temple of Poseidon. Now you can enter it, and face whoever is behind all this.
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_C7=Go to the Temple, hero. Lift the shadow that has fallen upon it. The Fates will decide your destiny.
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_temple_A1=Hero, you have done it! I arrived just in time to see the end. What a monster! {^n}{^n}We knew the cult leaders had some power, but still... who would have thought they would actually be able to summon their dark god?
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_temple_A2=They may have used the powers of this place. The temple hill is ancient - histories say it was built for the Titans by the Telkines, in a time before the rule of the gods. {^n}{^n}But still... the Serpentoids would hardly have been able to do this on their own. Unless...
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_temple_B1=Wait, do you feel that? There is something...
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_temple_X1=HYAAAAAAARRRRRGH!!!!
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_ghost_A1=Mortal! Heed the will of Poseidon! Today, a great deed has been done. Evil forces tried to claim Atlantis, but this island is for no one anymore - neither man nor beast. {^n}{^n}Only its former inhabitants were to see it, as a reminder of their squandered riches. {^n}{^n}But at long last, it has once again been a place of noble actions where nothing but greed and hubris used to reign. So it shall finally be released, and sink into the ocean where it will forever remain hidden from prying eyes!
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_ghost_A2=You heard him speak through me, a message long prepared - Poseidon has lifted my curse! Not only can I finally die, we are all free thanks to your help.
x3tagAtlantis_acrocatus_ghost_A7=I am eternally thankful for what you have done, traveller. You better leave this place now, lest you sink with it... but my tale ends here. {^n}{^n}I have played out my part, though long have I waited for it.
