// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x3tagGadir_anathe_A1=Hello there! An explorer, eh? Following the call of the great big world! You know, when I was your age I also could never stay in one place. Gadir is my home now, I suppose, but the truth is that my friend Hyram and I havent really had one since we first got on that trade ship in Byblos. You have not met him by any chance, have you? He wanted to make a short trip to the cave just outside Gadir but has been gone for quite a while. Would you mind keeping an eye out for him? Bald guy with a cypress cane.
x3tagGadir_anathe_A7=I hope Hyram is coming back. Would be dull to live out my days without someone to compete against! Seriously though... I pray to Melkart that he is OK.
x3tagGadir_anathe_B1=Hyram is safe! Thanks to you, king of the dark caves and open roads! And here I thought I'd have to go look for him myself.
x3tagGadir_anathe_B7=Thanks again, and safe travels!
x3tagGadir_hyram_S1=Aaaiiieeeh!!!
x3tagGadir_hyram_A1=I... I don't know what happened. I was exploring this cave like any other, then all of a sudden I was surrounded by those devils. And while I would not want to deny anyone their lunch, I was rather eager not to be part of it! Thank you for showing up!
x3tagGadir_hyram_A7=Actually I was looking for another cave, but when I found this entrance I couldn't just leave it unexplored, now could I? Well, I think I have had enough adventure for one day. See you around, Hero!
x3tagGadir_hyram_B1=Anathe is the best, but she worries too much. Probably because I'm starting to get ahead of her, ha!
x3tagGadir_hyram_B7=Tomorrow I think I'll explore that other cave!
x3tagMalta_jibran_A1=Hey! You're... real, aren't you? I am sorry, last night I made camp in a nearby cave and I... may have smoked a bit too much. I started seeing these strange phantoms... Then again, they might have been real! Really hard to tell, I'm too scared... If they are real they... probably have my pipe now. Perhaps you could go have a look? Bring it back to me and I will reward you. The cave is a bit further inland, when you start seeing trees.
x3tagMalta_jibran_A7=My friend! Did you find my shisha yet?
x3tagMalta_jibran_B1=Ah, you got my pipe back! Thank you so much! As for the creatures, I don't want to know if they were real or not... but I better get off this creepy island.
x3tagMalta_jibran_B7=Well, maybe one little pipe first.
x3tagMalta_jibran_C7=Hey... you seem familiar. Want a puff from my shisha? Best leaves from the Rif!
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_A1=My best goat is gone! Have you seen it, traveller? Please help me have a look around - my eyesight is not the best anymore... {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_A2=It was grazing right here under the Argan tree. I only dozed off for a few minutes. And now it is nowhere to be seen. Melita..!! {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_A3=If I had to guess, I would suspect that this mischievous musician who lives up the hill has nicked it. No idea why, but that guy is not right in the head!
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_A7=I hope my goat is alright...
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_B1=You saved my goat! Bless you, stranger, for your honesty! You must also be a friend of animals!
x3tagAtlas_abdhamon_B7=Thank you again, friend!
x3tagAtlas_baaliahon_A1=Yes, of course this goat is mine. Always has been! And today is its special day! But if you are so interested in it, maybe we could come to an understanding... {^n}{^n}How? Well, a group of Aegipans have started coming increasingly close to my little camp. Take care of them and we can make a deal. Oh, and bring me back one of their heads as proof!
x3tagAtlas_baaliahon_A7=A proportionally correct and generally all around decent Aegipan head would be just great right about now...
x3tagAtlas_baaliahon_B1=Wonderful! Such a head is an even better sacrifice to the dark powers of music than this goat. Look at these horns! I'll take that, and you can have the goat. As promised!
x3tagAtlas_baaliahon_B2=While I was waiting for the stars to align right for the blood sacrifice, I trained the goat to climb trees. Pretty swell, right?!
x3tagAtlas_baaliahon_D1=Hmm... Advanced chord progressions. Hmm... Master the circle of fifths. Hmmmm... Blood sacrifice!
x3tagAtlas_okha_A1=Stranger, spare me a moment? You are taking the path to the west, right? I have a letter here that I need delivered to a certain... woman of the Dschazūla tribe up in the mountains. Seeing as, um... I am not a fighter, I don't think I would make the trip. Would you carry it for me? {^n}{^n}
x3tagAtlas_okha_A2=Thank you for helping out! Just... please don't go around telling people about this, ok?
x3tagAtlas_okha_A7=I can't wait for her answer!
x3tagAtlas_okha_B1=May the spirits bless you, stranger! You have made us very happy.
x3tagAtlas_sheyma_A1=Oh, a letter for me? I bet it is from Okha. He always finds some excuse not to come here, but I think he is really just afraid of officially asking for my hand. He should not be! Oh well, thank you for your assistance.
x3tagAtlas_sheyma_A7=I guess I'll have to go to him then. I will not let petty dangers stand in the way of our love!
x3tagAtlas_baka_A1=Warrior! Do you have a moment? I have a proposition for you. I am a trader, making my livelihood on selling exotic spices to the local tribes here. I have a hidden storeroom... but somehow it has been invaded by monsters! I barely managed to escape, but now they are trapped in there, snacking on my precious goods! Would you go and clear it out, for a share of the wares? {^n}{^n}In one of the caves up in the mountains there is a secret door, it is opened by pushing a loose stone in the wall.
x3tagAtlas_baka_A2=I do not know how they got in there, but they must have followed the smell. Apparently the spices were appetizing to them as well.
x3tagAtlas_baka_A3=I... I think they were Basilisks. Majestic, colorful beasts, allegedly with a great affinity to magic. I doubt they will have any affinity to a sharp blade, though!
x3tagAtlas_baka_A7=Please hurry, this is my livelihood we're talking about! I will reward you for sure.
x3tagAtlas_baka_B1=I knew you could kill them, you are a real warrior! Did you see my spices? I hope there were some left so I can recoup some of my losses... But first things first. As promised, here is your guerdon.
x3tagAtlas_baka_B7=Thank you once again, my friend. You are one brave fighter. Good luck on your travels!
x3tagAtlantis_cook_A1=You're going inland to explore I take it? Might I ask you to look around for anything edible? The ship store of food is running rather low and I fear we might get into trouble on the return journey unless we can find some fresh supplies in this strange place.
x3tagAtlantis_cook_A2=Maybe no monster corpses if you can avoid it. Who knows what these will get you! And we actually still have dried meat. Some fresh fruit or vegetables would be nice!
x3tagAtlantis_cook_A7=I sure don't want to die of scurvy.
x3tagAtlantis_cook_B1=By Poseidon, what is this? A fruit? I don't know, it looks icky! But, beggars can't be choosers I reckon. I'll send out some men to look for more, with a little luck this might be it!
x3tagAtlantis_cook_B7=These fruits would probably taste better if we had some Iberian wine...
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_A1=Huh... you do not belong here. Nothing here is how it belongs anymore! You know, in my former life, I was a custodian of special artifacts. But the flood scattered them all, to who knows where. I could find and catalogue those still on the island, but many were lost to the sea. {^n}{^n}It is an impossible task... but if you happen to find any of them, anywhere, it would bring me great satisfaction if you could return them. {^n}{^n}They would have washed up on the shores, but being how advanced they must seem to primitive civilizations, some artifacts may have ended up in treasure vaults.
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_A2=It is all so messy, but I cannot touch anything to bring it back in order! It is the worst punishment!
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_A3=Perhaps you already saw atlantean artifacts on your travels, but did not recognize them? If you could keep an eye out, you would have my eternal gratitude!
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_A7=So many artifacts still missing... none in their place...
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_B1=One of the artifacts! I am so thankful! But there surely are more. Please keep looking!
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_C1=You found a second artifact? How nice! You deserve a big applause! {^n}{^n}Do you think you can find one more? Then I could make them into a new set.
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_D1=Oh my, you managed to find a third artifact! Could you place it exactly between the other two? No, exactly! A little more to the right... see? Now it is a new set, ‘The Returned Pieces'! {^n}{^n}You are very observant, thank you! Here, have a little something for your kindness.
x3tagAtlantis_auriana_E7=We spirits of Atlantis will always be grateful for your help. Just... please try not to make things more messy than they already are.
x3tagAtlantis_airon_A1=Do my eyes deceive me, a living soul in Atlantis? Could this be my blessed day? Hark traveler, I once was a powerful and respected individual upholding great influence over this city. But due to unfair and unfortunate unfoldings, I fell into my current state where I am hitherto unable to execute the simplest tangible task of expelling a couple of belligerent varmints. Be so kind, make my domain placid and eradicate these mischievous fiends from my estate!
x3tagAtlantis_airon_A7=Those two misshapes of Gaia would be hard to miss. Deliver them from their somatic status.
x3tagAtlantis_airon_B1=My mind is dazed, free at last from those feral fiends! Millennia of proprietary injustice have been resolved!  Vigorous adversary, a thousand thanks to thee!
x3tagAtlantis_airon_B7=By Poseidon, may your wayfaring be unperilous!
x3tagAtlantis_airon_D1=One creature is bereft of life you say, what an extraordinary report! Now, if you could tend to the one remaining aberration of nature, my existence could finally return to tranquility.
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_A1=Stay your hand, human. Whatever your quarrel is with these... traitors, we are not here to stop you. {^n}{^n}You see, not all of us ‘Merfolk', as you name us, are aligned with the powers that be on this island. We were once Poseidon's loyal soldiers, and in fact we opposed the Potamoi when they tried to rule alone. {^n}{^n}In the end it was the Serpentoids who tipped the scales. One of their high priests, his name is Ssaquath, pretended to be on our side... but then that turbid snake betrayed us! We do not know what they paid him, but he will pay in blood! Or in case you find him first, make sure you do not let him live. {^n}{^n}We would be most thankful.
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_A2=We had expected that the Potamoi might start trouble, but then the Serpentoid mages suddenly turned on us at the height of the dispute. That day those who still held faith in Poseidon lost their power, and our soldiers fell under the command of opportunistic turncoats. We should have known better than to ally ourselves with a disesteemed cult!
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_A3=Ssaquath thinks he is safe now, ruling with his new best friends. But once we find out where he is, we will prepare a little surprise for him.
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_A7=If you find that betrayer, kill him slowly, and tell him Okyroe sends her regards!
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_B1=You really killed him? Are you sure it was him? Ah, this is a great day for the resistance! In fact your whole endeavour here has helped us a great deal.
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_C7=We are in your debt, human. When the time comes to bring their cult down, we will be there to help.
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_S1=Now, brothers and sisters! Send those snakes to the abyss!
x3tagAtlantis_merfolk_D1=Tiamat's rule over our temple is broken, and so is her turbid cult! No longer will they defile lord Poseidon's legacy. {^n}{^n}Thank you again, human. We could not have done it without you.
x3tagAtlantis_meidias_A1=Stranger, I have seen you helping our cause. Other spirits speak highly of your deeds... but what is it you seek here? {^n}{^n}Do you wish to learn about the ancient crafts of Atlantis? If so, I could teach you, yes... but alas, I cannot touch anything. So you would have to bring the appropriate tools with you. {^n}{^n}Which ones? Well, let's see... an artist blacksmith's anvil of course, so you can work. A set of mechanical parts of appropriate quality, then a copper coil, and a rod of ferrophilum. That means a piece of iron that pulls other iron objects towards it. {^n}{^n}Those should be common around the district. Or at least they used to be...
x3tagAtlantis_meidias_A7=Well, you cannot craft anything without materials. Find them all first!
x3tagAtlantis_meidias_B7=Who are you? I don't trust outsiders...
x3tagAtlantis_meidias_C1=I see you did gather everything we need. Finally! Thank you. The coil has a bit of a patina it seems, but should be ok. Now let me show you a few tricks, then you should be able to follow these plans. In them is everything you need to know...
x3tagAtlantis_meidias_D7=I hope you can put your new knowledge to good use!
x3tagAtlantis_serpentoid_A1=You! Human! Do not sslay! Ni'sr is not hoss-tile! {^n}{^n}You kill Potamoi? You could help uss! Earn reward, yess? {^n}{^n}Find contractss!
x3tagAtlantis_serpentoid_A2=Potamoi leaderss have contractss! Not your business! But ourss!
x3tagAtlantis_serpentoid_A7=Find contractss! Obligationss! Do not ssay I ssent!
x3tagAtlantis_serpentoid_B1=Yess! Very nice contractss. With our friendss! I desstroy! {^n}{^n}Here. Thiss iss for you!
x3tagAtlantis_serpentoid_B7=This iss for you!
