// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagGhostly_cabinboy_A7=And we row, and we row, ‘till our fingers go numb, {^n}‘Till the sun turns to blood, and our bodies succumb, {^n}And we row, and we row, ‘till the flesh has gone foul, {^n}‘Till our bones turn to dust, and our souls flicker out. {^n}
x4tagLai_blacksmith_A1=... You're the one who fought back those beasts, aren't you? {^n}{^n}I suppose we owe you our thanks. Heavens, where did all those creatures come from all of a sudden? And what have we done to deserve this? They looted my entire smithy, and for what? I ... oh, forgive me, it is not proper for me to bother you with all this. You saved us, and I am grateful.
x4tagLai_blacksmith_A2=On second thought ... you are headed for Pingyang, aren't you? I suppose a hero like you knows some of the higher ups in the military. If so, perhaps you could ask them if they still need a skilled blacksmith? I heard they're recruiting.
x4tagLai_blacksmith_A7=I am sorry, but it will be a while before I can open up shop again. If ever. Curse those monkeys, curse Qiong Qi ... 
x4tagCourt_lady_X=Heavens ... Over here! Help me! Help!
x4tagCourt_lady_A1=Oh, good Heavens ... for a second, I thought that monster was going to tear my throat out. Shouxing shine upon you for helping us, soldier. You are a soldier, aren't you? Well, I suppose it doesn't matter: you must track this beast before it gets away and can wreak more havoc. I am evidently no scout or pathfinder, but you could try following the shore and talking to the fishermen - they must have seen where it fled to.{^n}{^n}Good luck, and ... thank you. I would no longer be here if not for your help.
x4tagCourt_lady_A2=I still cannot believe those creatures attacked us here ... This place, it has always been such a haven. The drought, now this ... Something horrible is happening to these lands, soldier, I can feel it.
x4tagCourt_lady_A7=Please ... whatever is happening out there, you must stop it.
x4tagWondering_tax_collector_A1=Why, isn't that just lovely ... Another stinking mercenary. Please, hurry along, won't you? I am an official of the Emperor's court, and I wish not to be pestered. 
x4tagWondering_tax_collector_A2=Are you deaf or just daft? I am an official of the Pingyang court! Or I was, before that pernicious slander by my blackguard colleagues condemned me to wandering this country and collecting taxes. Ugh, just thinking about it makes me sick. Go along, now.
x4tagWondering_tax_collector_A7=My lowlife friend, I will say it one more time: move along. I am on important business.
x4tagRice_Farmer_A1=Wh - no! No, please don't harm me, I - wait. You're not one of those brigands, are you? Oh, Heavens be praised. Please, forgive me for believing you were. The past few weeks have been hard, and that's putting it mildly. This never-ending heat is taking its toll on my paddies, and now there's word of Qiong Qi and his tigerspawn rampaging through the country. Hard to stay hopeful, I suppose.
x4tagRice_Farmer_A7=Yes, my friend? If you do not mind, please try not to ruin the soil. Heavens know the Suns have harmed it enough. They have never been this ... fervent.
x4tagHealer_A1=An adventurer, hm? No, a soldier. And Heavens, what impressive Chi you have.{^n}{^n}I will not even ask about your past exploits, as I doubt the afternoon will be long enough for your story. Do take care of yourself, though, won't you? Strong as it may be, I can sense that your Chi is slightly bu tong, blocked. I know it may be hard for someone of your profession, but do remember to treat your body with kindness from time to time.{^n}{^n}I'm always happy to tell you more about Chi, but I would not want to waste your time. Just come back though, should you happen to be in the mood.
x4tagHealer_A2=So you want to know more? Well, where do I start?{^n}{^n}Many people believe Chi is some strange magical power in our bodies, but that is too simplistic a view. Chi is inside and all around us: it's in our blood, our flesh, our bones, it's in the air we breathe and in the trees and in the water. You get the idea. Altogether, there are five aspects of it: metal, fire, wood, earth, and water, and every piece of matter has a different constitution, from objects to living beings.{^n}{^n}Always ensure that your Chi is in harmony and can flow freely if you wish to avoid teng, illness or pain. There are herbs, concoctions and practitioners who can help with that.
x4tagHealer_A3=Back for more? Why, I am honored - few people, especially the young ones, still care about all this nowadays. What else can I tell you? Ah, of course: there are places in this world, nexus points, where one aspect of Chi is extraordinarily strong. For example, there is a cave near the rice fields where Water abounds. Perhaps you could pay it a visit on your travels?{^n}{^n}Anyway, that is it for now. May the Sanxing shine light upon your roads.
x4tagHealer_A7=I wish you longevity. 
x4tagMason_A1=No time to chat, stranger. That cursed tigerspawn tore down our walls, and they won't fix themselves.
x4tagMason_A7=Bloody heat ... What's wrong with the Suns these days?
x4tagNosebleed_Victim_A1=What ... who are you, what do you want? Unless you have a cure for these cursed nosebleeds, just move along, will you? Gah.
x4tagNosebleed_Victim_A7=Third one in a week ... Curse my ancestors. 
x4tagFabeled_Strategist_A7=Just stay alive, soldier. Stay alive.
x4tagMerchant_from_Corinth_A1=Welcome, my friend, welcome! Might I interest you in some of my - wait. Zeus strike me with lightning, I know you! You are the hero who slayed Hades, Typhon, and the Telkine! Let me guess, you're the one who vanquished that gruesome winged tiger as well?{^n}{^n}Gods, I ... I do not even know what to say! Come, join me for a glass of ouzo, won't you? You must tell me what brought a fabled hero such as yourself to these faraway lands. And I will not take no for an answer.
x4tagMerchant_from_Corinth_A2=Hmm ... I see. I understand you cannot tell me too much, but I was also under the impression that greater forces were at work here. I mean, this heat alone ... It's like these ten suns have taken it upon themselves to set the soil on fire.{^n}{^n}Well, I trust you will handle it, just as you handled the Telkine. I will stay another week or so until my business in this city is concluded, then venture back to Corinth. And, believe me, I will make sure your tale travels with me. Farewell, Titan Slayer - it was an honor.
x4tagMerchant_from_Corinth_A7= Yes? I would offer you a look at my wares, but I doubt you have need for my exquisite fabrics. Not very ... practical for monster slaying, hehe. Travel safely!
x4tagImperial_Soldier_A1= Hmm? How may I help you? Wait, wait ... did you just say my mother, Shan, sent you? Heavens ... how is she? With all that's been going on in the countryside, I'm worried sick about her. Please, tell me. How is my mother? How is Lai?
x4tagImperial_Soldier_A2=Yanhuo ... Well, at least it wasn't Qiong Qi and his spawn who attacked the village. Needless to say, I owe you my thanks, stranger. Not only did you save this city from the Eater of Virtuous Souls, you also saved my mother and her village. I wish she would finally see sense and move here to live with me and my brothers, but for all her virtues, she is a stubborn soul.{^n}{^n}Anyway. Take this - it is not much, but the least I can do. Now, time to get back on patrol. The danger is far from over.
x4tagImperial_Soldier_A7= Good fortune to you, stranger. 
x4tagPingyang_Citizen_A1= Hm? What do - wait, I know you. You are the hero who killed Qiong Qi, aren't you? Heavens, the Emperor was wise to send for you. Please, you must help us ... This endless drought is drying up all the rivers and lakes, and the fish are dying. Without them or their oil, we soon won't make enough to keep a roof over our heads. Whatever this is, it must be stopped.
x4tagPingyang_Citizen_A7= Oh my ... I got a little carried away there, didn't I? I should have more faith in the Emperor. He has the favor of the Heavens, and his wisdom and power will save us. It must.
x4tagCourt_Sage_A7=So you're the fabled Titan Slayer ... I see. 
x4tagPilgrim_A1= A fellow traveler! How good to see a friendly face every once in a while. I was going to ask whether you were a pilgrim too, but these weapons suggest otherwise. And ... yes. You have great Chi, I can sense it. What is your quest, my friend? 
x4tagPilgrim_A2=So you are investigating the strange happenings all over the country. That is laudable. You see, I'm a pilgrim, and I am currently on a journey to visit all the sacred places between the realm of earth and the realm of heaven, to meditate and seek enlightenment. These past few moons have been difficult, though - monsters and riled-up animals abound. I will probably take refuge in a town for a while, then continue. {^n}{^n}Anyway, it was good to speak to you, and I am honored to have made your acquaintance. Please - stay safe.
x4tagPilgrim_A7= Stay safe.
x4tagCentral_Altar_Marshal_A1=Titan Slayer ... hmm, I expected more considering the bards won't stop rabbiting on about your exploits. But I suppose your Chi is impressive.{^n}{^n}I am Nezha, though most people know me as the Marshal of the Central Altar. I would join you on your endeavor to slay the Suns, but the Heavenly Duke's instructions were clear. However, I wish you good luck - you will need it.
x4tagCentral_Altar_Marshal_A7=Venture on, Titan Slayer.
x4tagGreat_Inventor_A1=Ha ... a familiar face. It has been a while, has it not? You did well dealing with the third Telkine back then, though I never truly doubted you. Perhaps you are not surprised to learn that it was me who encouraged the Son of Heaven to request your aid.{^n}{^n}Be that as it may, Hou Yi has informed me of the rather gloomy turn that events in the mortal realm have taken, so it appears we must once more forego that lovely philosophical discussion. The Jade Emperor already knows of your arrival and awaits you in the hall, so dally no longer.
x4tagGreat_Inventor_A7=Greetings, my friend.
x4tagYoung_Hero_A1=  So many faces ... So many ... many ... faces ...
x4tagYoung_Hero_A2=  You ... you are also a face? Are you his? I ... I just want to go home ... home ... to ...
x4tagYoung_Hero_A7=  He ... is more than he seems ... makes us see, see faces and things and ghosts and ...
x4tagSeamstress_A1=  Hm? I haven't seen you here before, are you also a refugee? No, don't say anything ... You don't look the type. Too strong.{^n}{^n}I wish I was in your shoes, stranger. To not be helpless before the caprices of fate ... That would be something for a change, wouldn't it? This endless drought dried up the entire farmland of my village, and there was nothing we could do to stop it, nothing. How can anyone still worship the sun? I thought we left those mad days of Akhenaten behind us. Anyway, I'm rambling. Stay safe out there, stranger.
x4tagSeamstress_A7=  Powerless ... that's what we are. Utterly powerless. 
x4tagEgypt_Mason_A1=  What is it? Unless you have something important to say, don't bother me. We need this whole crumbling mess of a temple fixed before next year. 
x4tagEgypt_Mason_A7=  To work on the Pharaoh's new temple in Karnak ... That would be something, wouldn't it? But no, he has me working on that thing instead. 
x4tagAkhenatens_Wife_A7=  A mortal! Oh, by the gods, you must stop my husband Akhenaten, now! He ... he completely lost his mind, and brought me back from Osiris' realm even though I never wished for it. Please, mortal - take him back where he belongs, so we can finally find peace. Please.
x4tagKarnak_Overseer_A1=  Who are you? You have that "hero's air" about you. Tell me, with these magical powers of yours, can you help us with the giant mess that is the construction of this temple? Conjure some sandstone, maybe? Ptah knows I lost way too many workers to this relentless drought and the hordes of undead out there.{^n}{^n}No? Thought as much.
x4tagKarnak_Overseer_A2=  Maybe you could at least clear the wasteland of monsters. We tried to circumvent the sandstone problem by salvaging resources from out there, but that was even less effective.
x4tagKarnak_Overseer_A7=  No time to chat, friend. Unless you can help us out with a miracle.
x4tagHigh_Priest_A1=  An adventurer, aren't you? Well, if you came to marvel at the glory of these beautiful temples, I will have to disappoint you: our last pharaoh, Akhenaten, destroyed all of them. It's a tragedy, truly. Ah, well. I will leave you to it.
x4tagHigh_Priest_A2=  Who is Akhenaten? You don't know? As I said, he was our last pharaoh, and he had ... how should I put it? Radical beliefs. He thought that our faith in the pantheon was misguided and instead ordered all Egyptians to worship Aten, the Sun, instead. What you can see here is the result of this: he ordered all the monuments and temples to the old gods torn down and erected new ones in honor of the sun.{^n}{^n}But thankfully, that's all in the past now. His son Tutankhamun seems wiser than his father, even at his tender age. With the help of his vizier, he will hopefully guide our country and people back to our roots.
x4tagHigh_Priest_A7=  Such blasphemy ... Such tragic blasphemy.
x4tagThebes_Citizen_A1=  Ahh, what a pleasant sight for tired eyes - a fresh face! What brings you here? Wait, I don't even need to know - all you need to know is that I'm Baba, and I have all the juicy stories your heart could possibly desire. Just come here if you're in the mood for some secrets ... because I have them all.
x4tagThebes_Citizen_A2=  Ha, I knew you would come. And at just the right time! Have you heard the scandal around Suten Anu? No? Well, sharpen your ears: word has it he is involved in Aten worship! Can you believe it? I heard it from Suten Anu's mother's cousin's friend's granddaughter, whom I happen to be very close with.{^n}{^n}A tragedy ... just when our Lord, the wise Tutankhamun, is leading Thebes back onto the path of the gods. Some people have no honor!
x4tagThebes_Citizen_A3=  Look, look, my friend from far away has returned! And, once again, you have picked the right moment, for a fresh scandal just reached Baba's perceptive ears.{^n}{^n}Word of the court has it that Udjaj, the famed minstrel, plans on giving a performance here in Thebes, and only nobles such as myself can attend. Isn't it spectacular? His songs are unrivaled, especially You Fill My Heart Like Camel Udders and To This Cute Bosom I Shan't Say Nay. Pity you will probably have left this wonderful city by then.
x4tagThebes_Citizen_A7=  Now, now, what have Amun's Winds brought me today: it's the curious outlander! I have yet another story for you, though, this time, I'm a little skeptical. They say the venerable priest Zazamankh has lost his mind and his trying to resurrect Akhenaten.{^n}{^n}Yes, I know, I know, it sounds mad. I suppose it doesn't matter: Vizier Ay will take care of it. 
x4tagCrazed_Hermit_A7=  ... I don't think it's supposed to work this way.
x4tagFortune_Seeking_Girl_A1=  You! Yes, you! Say, have you seen a frog nearby? A big one, with red eyes, and only three legs? That's Jin Chan, the money frog and fortune bringer! The other girls from the village said they saw him hopping around out here.
x4tagFortune_Seeking_Girl_A2=  What do you mean, "Isn't this dangerous?". My mother always says that for all we know, the world might end tomorrow, so it doesn't matter anyway, does it? I need to find Jin Chan ... Maybe with his good fortune, the other girls will finally stop calling me names.
x4tagFortune_Seeking_Girl_A7=  No time to chat, stranger! I must find Jin Chan!
x4tagShocked_Miner_A1=  They ... they are burning everything. Everything.
x4tagShocked_Miner_A2=  Are you ... are you even real? You must ... get to safety. The suns, they have turned crimson, and ... and ... and ...
x4tagShocked_Miner_A7=  Aren't you listening? You must get to safety, or they'll burn you. Do you hear me? They'll burn you, and everything else, they'll burn you, they'll burn you, they'll burn you, they'll burn you!
x4tagBheni_A7=I...I think I'm on the wrong side of the river. 
