// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagINTRO_EmperorYao_A1=So many times the Fates have tested you...They placed Typhon in your path, yet you prevailed.Hades himself fell to your prowess and might. Did you think that the Fates were done with you?There is no such thing as luck. A malevolent flame is devouring the realms of man.The Gods have abandoned us... will you?Will you take a stand? Will you prevail against not one, but against many?!Destiny awaits.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Wounded_Sailor_A1=... not going to die, Yun, quit jabbering nonsense. Shennong is watching— {^n}What by the— who are you? No, wait ... I think I saw you, didn’t I? Yes, yes, you were fighting Qiong Qi and his spawn. What are you, some sort of elite warrior?{^n}Well, it doesn’t matter—if you’re here to slay that winged beast, you have to take up the chase as fast as you can. He passed right by us, but some of his creatures didn’t, and you see what happened. I don’t know for sure, but I think it went down into the Hinterland Marshes. And please, hurry. Others won't be as lucky as we were.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Wounded_Sailor_A7=You’ll pull through this, Yun. All right? Just think of Feiyan and the children.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Elder_Huizhong_A1=Well, well ... you certainly know how to stand your ground in a fight. First and foremost, let me extend my greetings - I am Huizhong, the Elder of this humble village. Am I correct to assume the Son of Heaven sent you to deal with the Great Peril, Qiong Qi?{^n}If so, then you are in luck - Hou Yi, the god of archery himself, has decided to intervene and take care of that creature and its spawn. An imperial regiment passed through here to intercept him in the abandoned fort near the village. You might still catch up to them if you make haste.{^n}{^n}Heavens know we need all the aid we can get. Whatever prompted Qiong Qi to come out of its lair, it must be the same thing that riled up the Yanhuo. And who knows what else.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Elder_Huizhong_A7=What is it? You must not dally - head to the fort and find the vanguard. Hou Yi should be able to defeat the creature, but the more blades and spears that will stand against this beast, the better.{^n}Heavens ... first that drought, now this. What is going in this world?
x4tagMQ_JC001_Vanguard_Soldier_A1=Wh ... who ... Oh, good heavens, have you ... have you seen him? Hou Y-Yi?{^n}He will come, you know? The others, they said he'll turn his back on us, but I told them the God of Archery would ... n... never...{^n}H-Heavens, it’s – it’s all going dark. H-help me, please, I don't ... I don't want to ...
x4tagMQ_JC001_HouYi_A1=... Titan Slayer. The Son of Heaven told me he had summoned you to hunt down Qiong Qi.{^n}{^n}For better or for worse, I found out what the real danger is, and it is not Qiong Qi: it is the Ten Suns, the grandchildren of the Jade Emperor. They are the ones causing this, the drought, the monster attacks ... They emboldened Qiong Qi to leave its lair. I do not understand what drives them, mortal ... It is as if they completely lost their senses. I came upon them as I headed to the fort to help the imperial soldiers, but ... well, there is no good way to say this. They were too strong.{^n}{^n}Anyway, let us not waste time. I am still wounded, but I should be able to walk again soon – I lost two pieces of my bow as I fought the Suns, and I need them back. You must aid me in that, mortal. Here, this will allow your hands to carry them safely ... The pieces flew off in different directions and struck like a meteor where they landed, so they should be easy to find. Go, now. All this ... it does not bode well. Not well at all.
x4tagMQ_JC001_HouYi_A7=What is it, mortal? You must recover my bow.
x4tagMQ_JC001_HouYi_B1=There you are ... let me see. Yes, those are the parts. It appears you are as honorable and competent as your reputation suggests.{^n}{^n}Now, on to the strategy: the world needs to know that the Suns are behind this. This, we must do first, then we can investigate the “Why”. I will ascend to the Heavenly Palace and see if anyone there knows the meaning behind all this—in the meantime, you should head to Pingyang and inform the Son of Heaven.{^n}Now, let us dally no longer, mortal – if the Suns continue this madness, that rampaging winged tiger will be the least of our worries.
x4tagMQ_JC001_HouYi_B7=What are you waiting for, mortal? Head to Pingyang. We must not dally.
x4tagMQ_JC001_ZhangWei_A1=Oh, thank the Heavens ... You're the hero the Emperor sent for, aren't you? The Titan Slayer? Well, please pardon me for skipping the formalities, but I’m sure you can see what is going on here—Qiong Qi and his spawn reached the residence a few hours ago, and we lost the residence to them. Please, you must slay them, lest they defile this whole place and butcher the remaining servants.{^n}{^n}There is a cave a little south of here that should take you down the precipice safely - it's how I escaped. If you cross the cave, please be on the lookout for the Emperor's sacred armor - I tried to save it from Qiong Qi's spawn, but it was too heavy, so I hid it. I am certain you will put it to good use. Now go, Titan Slayer. Hurry.
x4tagMQ_JC001_ZhangWei_A7=What is it? There are still servants in the residence, you must save them!
x4tagMQ_JC001_MaFang_A1=Another soldier? Hm ... you certainly do not look like ordinary infantry. If you came here seeking Hou Yi, you are too late - he was here, but then he went eastwards. An hour later, we saw him in the sky, fighting something, until the entire horizon went up in a flash of fire and Hou Yi was gone.{^n}We don't know what happened, and, frankly most of us were too afraid to go look, may the Jade Emperor forgive us. I was just glad the fire didn't spread to here. As if this cursed drought hasn't done enough to our fields already.{^n}{^n}Anyway: Cai Lun and Liu Jing were more courageous than most of us and went to see what happened, but they haven't returned yet. Look, if you’re as good with a weapon as you seem, perhaps you could head eastwards and see what happened to Hou Yi and my friends? You should recognize them by their clothing.
x4tagMQ_JC001_MaFang_A7=Yes? Is there anything else?
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_A1=Well, well, the Titan Slayer has arrived. I am glad you heeded my summons. Anyway - good work dealing with the winged tiger, it appears you live up to your reputation.{^n}{^n}Alas. As I told you in my message, I presume Qiong Qi was only a symptom, and not the root of whatever evil has befallen our empire. Tell me what you learned, Titan Slayer. Tell me all.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_B1=So Hou Yi says the Ten Suns are behind this... hm. It explains the drought. Well then, our objective is clear: we must put an end to their deeds. Thankfully, I already have a plan: you must seek out the Jade Emperor in the Heavenly Palace. As you might know, the Suns are his kin, so he must know why they are doing this and might even be willing to lend us his support.{^n}{^n}Here, take this: it is the key to my mausoleum here in Pingyang. There is a secret stairway in the mausoleum’s depths that will lead you to the Ascent - from there, you can reach the Heavenly Palace. And yes, crawling through a dungeon may not be worthy of a hero, but with the battles outside, it is much safer.{^n}{^n}We could kill two birds with one stone: my soldiers report some commotion down there, but have not yet had time to investigate, so perhaps you can take care of that, too. Now hurry: If Hou Yi is right, then Qiong Qi was only the beginning.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_B2=I can't believe the Suns defeated Hou Yi. This is bad news, Titan Slayer. Bad news.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_B3=Droughts, monsters, brigands ... Misfortune has a way of attracting more misfortune, hasn't it?
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_B7=What is it? Find the mausoleum, and ascend to the Heavenly Palace. If anyone has answers, it will be the Jade Emperor.
x4tagMQ_JC001_Emperor_Yao_C7=Greetings, Titan Slayer.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_1=Long ago, there was a peaceful and happy kingdom, reigned over by the King of Pure Virtue and the Queen of Gilt Moonlight. But woe plagued them, for they were growing old and remained heirless: at last, the Primeval Lord of Heaven took pity and answered their prayers, sending the Queen a child in her dreams. One day later, she woke up pregnant and gave birth to a beautiful, golden boy.{^n}{^n}The man was as splendid as his birth promised: the day he came of age, he went out to gift treasures and food to the poor, and when his father passed away, he ruled with wisdom and benevolence. But no matter how just his reign, he soon grasped that he would never break the cycle of death and suffering that plagued humankind. Griefstruck, he abdicated and sought out the mountains, where he pursued the Tao in hope of unraveling the mysteries of the universe and ending the cruel bane of suffering. {^n}{^n}For one hundred million years, he meditated and virtuously cultivated his spirit. And when he finally descended from the mountains, he was a king no longer, but an enlightened being and the ruler of Heaven. He was the Jade Emperor.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_2=The Four Perils. Oh, the Four Perils.{^n}{^n}You know of the Four Symbols: the Azure Dragon, the Vermillion Bird, the White Tiger, and the Black Tortoise. Valiantly, they watch over us, each shielding one cardinal direction.{^n}{^n}But light cannot exist without darkness: and so there are also the Four Perils, malevolent creatures who bring as much terror to our hearts as the Symbols bring joy.{^n}There is the Hundun, a monstrous beast the color of cinnabar fire, with six feet and four hideous wings. {^n}{^n}There is Qiong Qi, the bestial tiger who soars through the sky like a hideous giant falcon. He is the most cunning of the lot, for he always listens, ready to tear the head off those of us whose words show kindness and compassion.{^n}{^n}Taowu is the most tragic of the four – for it was given the gift of divination and intelligence but uses it only to stir up chaos and violence. Look out for its hideous shape on the horizon, wearing a human face, a tiger’s paws, and a tail so long it resembles a colossal snake.{^n}{^n}Lastly, there are the taotie – those hideous beasts whose strength lies in their endless numbers – who breed and breed until their gruesome shapes cloak the lands in black.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_3=A thousand stone tablets could not hold the great deeds of our emperor, the Son of Heaven. It is no secret that great good has befallen our country since his father Shun granted him the throne: so just and virtuous is his rule that sun and moon have grown as resplendent as jewels, phoenixes nest in the palace courtyards, the rivers shine bright as crystals, and the harvests have been plentiful. {^n}{^n}His greatest deed must be his stopping of the Great Flood of Gun-Yu. Lasting for over two generations, it brought calamity upon our lands, forcing families from their homes and crushing livelihoods. Only Yao’s sagacious gaze was it that saw that none other than Gun, the Prince of Chong, was key to stopping the flooding; Gun’s wise strategies helped, but did not end the flood entirely, but when his son Yu came of age, the era of terror finally came to an end. Undoubtedly inspired by the Son of Heaven’s faith in him, Yu’s unrivaled engineering and the help of the gods allowed him to build an intricate network of channels that finally tamed the raging river.{^n}{^n}We can but rejoice that our Emperor’s reign has only begun.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_4=To few deities do we owe as much as to the goddess Nüwa, half human, half snake. On this earth long before any humans, loneliness plagued her and prompted her to create humans from the mud.{^n}{^n}She formed each human with her hands, but soon realized more people were needed to populate the earth; cunning as she was, she took rope, dipped it in the mud and swung it around to release droplets of mud everywhere, conjuring a shower of wet soil from which more humans would arise.{^n}{^n}But the gods are not just: the humans she formed herself became wealthy and prosperous, and the humans from the rope droplets sickly and poor.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_5=What would we be without the Yellow Emperor?{^n}Cavemen. Brutes. Uncivilized nomads, straying from place to place. Huang Di was his name, and he was the first of our legendary emperors. Blessed with four faces, nothing that transpired in the world evaded his watchful gaze, and even the divine realm was not beyond his reach, for his rituals and sacrifices allowed him to speak to it; befitting his glorious nature, he rode an ivory chariot pulled by dragons and elephants.{^n}{^n}Remarkable, but more remarkable still was his knowledge. Patiently and wisely, he passed on many skills to his subjects, teaching them the ways of many a craft. Without him, there would be no wheel, no calendar, no ships, no compass. When Huang Di became sick after a long reign, he meditated for a long time, until he discovered what we, today, know as the Tao. {^n}{^n}And it made him immortal.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_6=Before the universe existed, all there was were chaos and darkness. On and on it warped and twirled, until, in a strange twist of fate, the chaos formed into the shape of an egg. All the universe’s tumultuous substance confined into this tiny space, it grew stormy inside the egg and two opposing forces formed which we now know as yin and yang. They fought very long time, one trying to dominate the other, until they finally found balance – and formed a creature called Pangu.{^n}{^n}Growing aware he was stuck in this tiny egg, Pangu despaired and tossed and writhed – until the egg cracked into two halves, and Pangu burst out along with the egg’s whites and yolk. While the light yolk floated skywards to become the clouds, stars, and sky, the heavy, dense yolks sunk down to become the earth. Lastly, the two parts of the shells flew upward to become sun and moon. {^n}{^n}And so the world was formed.
x4tagSCROLL_Imhotep_1=Give thanks to Amun for the mighty Tutankhamun, the Boy King. Through his words and through his deeds, the pharaoh is restoring balance to this fractured land.{^n}{^n}When Egypt was forced to turn its back on the gods, they had no choice but to turn their backs on us. Every temple we rebuild, every statue we replace, every name we carve into stone, all of it brings the gods back to us. Step by step, day by day.{^n}Amun gave our priests the wisdom to hide away precious reminders of our gods, and now those priests are putting them back where they belong. Our priests are no longer afraid to praise all of the gods, and especially Amun.{^n}{^n}All of this great work will soon be complete. When balance is finally restored, rejoice and remember: it is all thanks to Amun and Tutankhamun.
x4tagSCROLL_Imhotep_2=You may think that you walk alone, but you are mistaken. From the moment of your birth, Shai has been by your side. Shai, master of fate, measurer of lives, is your constant companion right up until the day when your soul faces its final judgement.{^n}{^n}Shai alone knows how long your life will be, for he alone decides the length of life for every mortal. But he is a silent companion, so do not expect him to reveal the secrets of your destiny until it is fulfilled.{^n}{^n}On your dying day, he will accompany your soul into the Duat. Yes, he will not abandon you, even in the land of the dead. He will tell all in the Hall of Judgement, so be sure to live well, so that his tale of your life may be a good one. With Shai’s help, your soul will find peace in Aaru.
x4tagSCROLL_Imhotep_3=Early in the reign of Amenhotep the Fourth, the pharaoh wondered why there were so few places to worship Aten, the disc of the Sun. Amenhotep ordered the construction of temples throughout the land. The grandest of all was the House of the Aten, in Thebes.{^n}{^n}At first, the people did not think this so strange, as pharaohs had a habit of ordering new buildings. But then Amenhotep stopped honoring the other gods. And he changed his name - to Akhenaten, declaring his dedication to Aten and establishing a new capital city, Amarna. The people began to worry.{^n}{^n}Akhenaten had temples to other gods torn down, and had mentions of their names removed wherever they were to be found. But his efforts were in vain. After his death, the people went back to the old ways, and his son changed his name from Tutankhaten to Tutankhamun. Long live the pharaoh!
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_7=Zhu Yingtai had a passion for knowledge, convincing her father to let her dress as a man and attend lessons. She met a scholar named Liang Shanbo, and they studied together for three years. Zhu fell in love with Liang, but his head was too buried in his books to realize that she was a woman in disguise.{^n}{^n}A letter called Zhu home. Before parting, Zhu made Liang promise to visit, so he could propose to Zhu’s ‘sister’. When he arrived, Liang finally discovered Zhu’s true identity, and they pledged to love each other for eternity.{^n}{^n}Zhu’s father shattered their joy, demanding that she marry a wealthy merchant. Liang died of a broken heart before the wedding. On her wedding day, Zhu knelt by Liang’s grave. A clap of thunder opened the grave, so she leapt in to join her love. Their spirits emerged together as butterflies, finally together forever.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_8=Sihai Longwang, the Dragon King of the Four Seas, rules over the water and all the creatures who dwell within it. He rules over the mighty dragons, too. Sihai Longwang bows only to the Jade Emperor, and you would do well to show him your respect.{^n}{^n}When the wind whips the cold rain into your eyes, it is as Sihai Longwang wills it. When the towering waves threaten to overturn your vessel, it is as Sihai Longwang wills it. And when the fish scurry from your net, it is as Sihai Longwang wills it.{^n}{^n}But he can be kind, bringing good fortune to those he deems worthy. He may just bring rain to your parched crops, calm seas to aid your vital voyage, or a bounty of fish to save you from starvation. Such is the might of Sihai Longwang.
x4tagSCROLL_JadeEmperor_9=When you are down on your luck, wondering how you are going to survive until tomorrow, there is no sight more welcome than the bright red eyes of Jin Chan, the frog of good fortune.{^n}{^n}This three-legged amphibian is the bearer of good news, so if you spot him, rejoice! Your money woes will likely soon be over. But he is not always to be found, appearing only under the light of the full moon.{^n}{^n}And remember, if it is meant to be, he will find you. Do not try to hunt him down or keep him for yourself. Good fortune is as delicate as the petal of a lily: hold on too tightly, and it will be crushed.
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_A1=Finally! I was starting to doubt the Son of Heaven would send help at all ... {^n}What a cursed mess this is. The Emperor surely wants to know how these raiders got into the mausoleum, doesn't he? Well, I'm ashamed to admit it, but they found out about the secret entrance he commissioned. I will, of course, take full responsibility for not concealing it better, but for now all that matters is that you slay these blackguards and get us out of here. The defense mechanism that locked them in here uses four keystone pieces - collect them and return them to me, then I can disable it.{^n}{^n}I have one piece right here, and I presume the raiders have the rest. Now, off with you, soldier. Do your duty to the Son of Heaven.
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_A2=What is it now? Have my instructions not been clear?{^n}I ... I am dead? But ... woe, how can this be? What can I - {^n}All right, that was quite amusing, but now truly isn't the time for jesting. I am evidently not dead, otherwise I would not be talking to you, would I? Now please do not dally - you must find the keystones and slay the raiders.
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_A7=I will say it again: do not dally. Slay the raiders and find the keystones, soldier.
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_B1=Good work, soldier - I do not know who you are, but you must clearly be some sort of elite. Anyway, it is about time we got out of here. This is a beautiful place, but it has been too-{^n}What ... what is this? I ... why ... I can't ... move?{^n}I am a bit tired from all the strain. Perhaps you could carry me, soldier? Just to the surface?
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_B2=This nonsense again, a ghost? Clearly, I am not - here, do you see this finger? This hand? Does this look like a ghost's hand to -{^n}Wait. Why ... why is it fading? What is happening? Heavens, soldier, please, help me, something is wrong! Help me!
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_B3=What do you mean, you cannot help me? I saw you slay those raiders, there must be something you can do. I ... oh, Heavens. No. No, this cannot be. I dodged that spear, I dodged it, it did not kill me, it did not!{^n}.. Or maybe it did. Oh, good lord, this is my punishment, is it not? I never meant for things to end this way, all I wanted was a little bit of coin. All those years of hard work, and what did I get for them? Nothing. Nothing.
x4tagMQ_JC002_LiuChangdong_B4=Fine. I suppose I had this coming. Please, do not tell the Son of Heaven about this, will you? Yes, I let in the raiders because they promised me a cut of the riches ... I just wanted a better life, is that so hard to understand? Please, do not tell anyone. I ... I could not bear to have my name sullied for all generations to come. I ... could ... could ... could ...
x4tagMQ_JC002_HouYi_X1=Mortal. Over here, now.
x4tagMQ_JC002_HouYi_A1=So he told you nothing, did he? I thought as much. Heavens forgive me for saying this, but why would he choose to sit and watch as his own kin lays waste to the mortal realm?{^n}{^n}Well, spilt water is hard to retrieve. I would suggest we go after the Suns ourselves, but they are simply too strong. However, if the Jade Emperor will not help us, I know someone else who might: Sihai Longwang. You have surely heard of him, the Dragon King of the Four Seas. He is the Jade Emperor's right-hand man, but he has always had a mind of his own, so odds are we can convince him to help us.{^n}Find him and prove yourself worthy of his attention, then he might lend us his strength. Now go - my thoughts are with you.
x4tagMQ_JC002_HouYi_A7=What is it, mortal? Find Sihai Longwang. He might be our only chance.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Jade_Emperor_A1=Look what the threads of fate have brought into my palace ... Greetings to you, whom they call the Titan Slayer. I fear this will be a short audience, for the answer is "no": I cannot help you against the chaos the Ten Suns are bringing upon your realm. Understand that this has nothing to do with callousness - it is simply how it must be. As to your question of why they are doing these things, let me merely say this: there is something they have found out, and now they are doing everything in their power to stop it. This is all I can say. {^n}{^n}Now go, mortal. Hurry along the threads of fate.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Jade_Emperor_A7=All has been said, Titan Slayer. Leave.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_X1=Well, well ... look what the threads of fate brought into my lair. You are either extremely powerful or extremely foolish. Let us find out which one it is.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_X2=Not bad. Not bad at all. But we are far from done.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_B1=Enough ... That was diverting. It has been too long since my blade faced such a challenge. You, mortal, are worthy of an audience. {^n}{^n}Go on, tell me. Who are you, and what brought you here? I do not concern myself with worldly affairs down here. Mortal quarrels ... they are so tiring.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_B2=So you are the famed Titan Slayer. How curious ... so little flesh, yet so much power. And yes, it is indeed strange that the Suns would turn on the mortal realm. But then again, they were always proud, anxious beings. But as to your request, the answer is "yes:" You brought some diversion to my life, and in return, I will help you and the mortal realm against the Suns.{^n}{^n}As you may know already, it is impossible to defeat the Ten Suns as long as they are up in the sky - however, I can help you with that by forging a seal that will break their magic and make them crash down to earth. After that, you will be on your own.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_B3=That said, there is one thing I must ask of you before I will help you: one of my forge orbs has been stolen. I did identify the culprits, some strange cult from the land called Egypt, but my obligations keep me tethered to this place. I do not know where they hiding it, but if you want my help, you will have to return it to me. {^n}Now, enough words, there is a portal in my forge that will take you straight to Egypt. Oh, and please, take whatever you need - if you're to be my errand runner, I want you to be a well-equipped one. Go now. Bring me my orb, and I will grant you my aid.
x4tagMQ_JC002_Sihai_Longwang_B7=Enough talking, mortal - the portal is in my forge. Recover my orb, then I will help you.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Sadeira_A1=Well, well ... look what the portal brought to us. You are not our enemy, I presume, otherwise we wouldn't be having this conversation. What brings you here? Tell me.{^n}{^n}So ... you say that some great evil haunts China, but cannot tell me any details. Well, fine by me: if you can help make this desert safe again, I won't complain. You can probably tell, but all these undead forced our tribe into a corner. Now, as to this Imhotep character you're looking for, you're in luck, he did indeed travel with us.{^n}However, he left our encampment last night to investigate some magical anomaly in a nearby catacomb, which, according to him, is connected to the monster plague here. I would tell you to be careful, but you look as though you can stand your ground in a fight.{^n}{^n}Now, if you'll excuse me - I have other matters to attend to.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Sadeira_A2=Be vigilant, stranger.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Sadeira_A3=Asyut nomads, trapped on a cliff ... It's a disgrace.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Sadeira_A7=Found your sage yet? As I said, the catacombs down that way would be my guess.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Imhotep_A1=You! Curses, what are you thinking, barging in here and interrupting my studies? I had it under control, do you hear me? I had it under control.{^n}{^n}Ah, well ... perhaps I didn't. Forgive me, this is not the proper way to greet someone, especially not an old friend. Tell me, what brought the Titan Slayer to Egypt again? After your victory over Typhon, I presumed you'd be stretching your legs in some lavish manor, bathing in wine. I know that's what I'd be doing.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Imhotep_A2=The Ten Suns ... hm, I have heard about them. So you are saying they are the masterminds behind all this? That's ... disquieting. Anyway, let's move on to the good news, shall we? I don't know who might have stolen your dragon king's missing orb, but I do know where it might be: the Abydos Necropolis. In fact, I believe the entire undead plague that has been sweeping these lands is linked to a magical disturbance that originated there. Now, missing orb, magical anomaly, undead plague - I don't know about you, but it's not too much of a leap, is it?{^n}{^n}I suggest you head there and investigate. I'd go myself, but, let's face it, these bones aren't the youngest anymore. Good luck - and please don't die.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Imhotep_A7=What is it? That magical orb isn't going to find itself. Abydos Necropolis, deepest levels.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Zazamankh_X1=By the Sun - you!
x4tagMQ_JE001_Zazamankh_A1=Well, well ... look what the winds swept into my domain. I know why you're here, Titan Slayer, and you're too late. The Ten Suns will cleanse the lands with their scorching light, as they should have done long ago.{^n}{^n}We are so ... ungrateful, you know? We foolish humans. My lord Akhenaten, he worked so hard and so long to lead Egypt to the light of Aten and abolish their foolish pantheon, and for a few years, it seemed like he had succeeded. But no, the second he perished, all these fools turned back to their heathen gods. Well, now all of mankind will pay the price for their insolence. As will you.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Zazamankh_B1=C-Curses, I ... forgot how strong you are.{^n}But ... but it doesn't matter. I know why you came here, and it's ... it's too late. The Dragon King's orb. That's - that's why you are here, isn't it? Well, you were too slow, it is already with Akhenaten.{^n}{^n}Yes, you heard - heard right. The Ten Suns told me about it, and that its power could resurrect my lord, so I stole it. He marches to Thebes as we speak, together with his army of undead ... He ... he will be the Suns' champion, Titan Slayer. Isn't ... isn't it beautiful? After d-death, he will finally ... finally get the glory he ... des...
x4tagMQ_JE001_Zazamankh_B7=P-Praise Aten ... Praise ...
x4tagMQ_JE001_Ay_A1=Who are - wait, I do recognize you. You are the slayer of the Telkine, are you not? What brings you to Thebes? I would tell you that this country could use a hero right now, but something tells me you already know.{^n}{^n}So ... you're telling me a sun priest has resurrected Akhenaten? Who is now servant to the Chinese suns? Well, that certainly explains these undead attacks. My Lord, the Pharaoh, must learn of this at once. Please, go on in - the guards will let you through.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Ay_A7=The Pharaoh awaits you, Titan Slayer.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Tutankhamun_A1=Well - and here Ay claimed there would be no more audiences today. Who are you? If he let you in, it must be important. Speak, soldier.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Tutankhamun_A2=... I understand.{^n}{^n}Three things: first, you must slay my father - or rather, the husk that crossing in and out of Osiris' realm has surely turned him into. Please understand that these words do not come easily. I -{^n}Regardless of what my father did to this kingdom with his mad cult of Aten, I am still his son. And this, having to see him die and then be slayed again ... I would not wish it upon anyone. Even so, it has to be done, and you are, beyond a doubt, the right one for the task.{^n}{^n}Second: I believe that my father might be hiding - or rather, preparing for his final attack - in the Sun temple he sought to build during his reign. I cannot be certain, but knowing my father, I believe you should go there.{^n}{^n}And third: thank you for warning us. I know you are here to find the orb of this "Dragon King" first and foremost, and something tells me you might have found my father without our aid.{^n}{^n}Now go - you must not dally. Find my father's husk and put it to rest - once and for all.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Tutankhamun_A7=Find my father, Titan Slayer. Find him and put him to rest.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Tutankhamun_B1=... The monster attacks have stopped. Am I right to presume this means you have ... put my father to rest?{^n}No, do not say anything. I can see it in your eyes. Well, it is better this way - what once was dead must stay dead. Here, please take this as a gift of my kingdom. It is not much, but I hope it will aid you in the rest of your quest. Judging by what you have told us, the true threat is still out there.{^n}Farewell, hero. You have earned your title.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Tutankhamun_B7=Farewell, hero.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Akenaten_X1=... Soil ... burn ... soil ... burn ...
x4tagMQ_JE001_Akenaten_A1=Burn ... burn, burn, burn, burn, burn, burn!
x4tagMQ_JE001_Akenaten_X2=B ... burn ...
x4tagMQ_JE001_Imhotep_2_A1=You ... you slayed him. I think? Curses, with these undead you never know. Yes, yes, I know, what was I doing here all by myself? Let's just say, a few hours after you left, I surmised that the mad sun worshipper Akhenaten was behind this, and my scholastic curiosity got the better of me.{^n}{^n}Be that as it may: it appears you once again saved the day. I am by no means an expert on arcane Chinese orbs, but it seems like this one is still intact, despite Akhenaten's abuse. Return it to this Dragon King of yours, then do what you do best and take care of those Suns. I will facilitate your return.{^n}{^n}Farewell, Titan Slayer. And ... thank you for saving me.
x4tagMQ_JE001_Imhotep_2_A7=Resurrected pharaohs, arcane orbs, renegade Suns ... Talk about a rough day. Ugh.
x4tagMQ_JC003_SihaiLongwang_A1=Well, well ... look who has returned to my lair, bearing my lost treasure. Do not bore me with stories of what happened - I could not care less. All that matters is that you upheld your end of the bargain - and I shall uphold mine. Make yourself comfortable, Titan Slayer. This will take some time.
x4tagMQ_JC003_SihaiLongwang_A2=And here it is ... the Seal. I do not concern myself with names, feel free to choose one if you wish. Either way, the Seal will take effect once you approach the Suns, dampening their immense powers so you may fight them at even odds. Now run, mortal - head back to the realm the Suns have set aflame. Unless, that is, you care for another fight? It is a long time since I had one so diverting.{^n}No? Very well. Then step through the portal and face your destiny.
x4tagMQ_JC003_SihaiLongwang_A7=Go on, Titan Slayer. Slay some ... Suns.
x4tagMQ_JC003_Emperor_Yao_A1=Titan Slayer ... greetings. I trust you bring good news? Heaven knows we need them, for the Suns have embarked on a rampage ever since you left. If we do not put a stop to them soon ... I do not even want to think about it. Now talk, I pray you. Have you found a way to stop them?
x4tagMQ_JC003_Emperor_Yao_A2=A seal that will dampen their powers ... I understand. There is little for us to do other than hope the Dragon King does not deceive us. It troubles me that we still understand so little of the Suns' motivations, however. Did the Jade Emperor truly not provide any answers? {^n}{^n}Well, I suppose it does not matter. You must confront the Suns right away, Titan Slayer. According to my scouts, they have retreated to the Flaming Mountains, probably to launch their final strike. And yes, the irony is not lost on me.{^n}The way to the Flaming Mountains leads through the marshlands, but it would be wiser for you to take the tunnel out of the city - you can enter it through a trapdoor in the Trade Quarter. I have ordered my guards to let you through. Once in the marshlands, the Suns' minions are certain to try and stop you, but something tells me you can handle it.{^n}Now good luck, Titan Slayer. Get out there and stop the Suns before they turn this whole world to ashes.
x4tagMQ_JC003_Emperor_Yao_A7=Go on, Titan Slayer. Stop the Suns before they immolate us all.
x4tagMQ_JC003_Renshu_A1=Turn back, stranger. The marshes are off-limits.
x4tagMQ_JC003_Renshu_A7=Are you testing my patience? I said, "turn back."
x4tagMQ_JC003_Renshu_B7=Turn ba - wait, aren't you that "hero" the commander said was coming? Yes ... you are. Huh. Well, don't let me stop you then. The path is open.
x4tagMQ_JC003_HouYi_A1=I presume this is the Dragon King's seal? So that old beast did not deceive us ... refreshing. Well then, Titan Slayer. Time to end this.
x4tagMQ_JC003_HouYi_A2=It's ... it's over, Titan Slayer. Do it. End their suffering.
x4tagOUTRO_Jade_Emperor_A1=And so destiny has come to pass. At ease, I am not here to avenge my kin.  You must not blame them - this was not an act of hate, but an act of fear. They took that which is forbidden, a record of the birth and death of every being, divine and mortal alike. It was then that the Suns learned of their impending demise – fated to be felled by mortal hands. It was their doing that brought you here - forcing Destiny’s hand. Though destined to perish, their flame cannot be extinguished, for it is tied to life itself. It was your fate to douse the flames, it is mine to rekindle them.Let the new Sun stand as a beacon for all life to follow......and let the world revel in a new dawn. 
