// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagMq01_Title=A Strange Land
x4tagMq01_Task_01A=Reach the Palace
x4tagMq01_Task_01A_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Equip yourself with the hidden armor and reach the palace.
x4tagMq01_Task_01B=Save the Summer Palace
x4tagMq01_Task_01B_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Qiong Qi and his minions have breached the residence's walls - save the Summer Palace.
x4tagMq01_Task_01=Reach the Silk Road
x4tagMq01_Task_01_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Fight your way through the coastline to reach the Silk Road.
x4tagMq01_Task_02=Find the village of Lai
x4tagMq01_Task_02_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}According to the fishermen, Qiong Qi and his beasts went southwards, towards a village named Lai.
x4tagMq01_Task_03=Catch up to the Imperial Army's vanguard
x4tagMq01_Task_03_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Elder Huizhong from Lai informed you that a vanguard of the Imperial Army ventured north to face Qiong Qi - apparently, Hou Yi, the God of the Hunt, promised his aid. Catch up to the vanguard.
x4tagMq01_Task_04=Slay Qiong Qi
x4tagMq01_Task_04_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}You have come across Qiong Qi, slay it and find out what happened to Emperor Yao’s vanguard.
x4tagMq01_Task_05=Search for Hou Yi
x4tagMq01_Task_05_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Qiong Qi escaped once again. According to the dying soldier Hou Yi never appeared. Follow the Silk Road inland, and find out what happened to him. He would never break his promise out of his own volition.
x4tagMq01_Task_06=Head into the rice fields and find Hou Yi
x4tagMq01_Task_06_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}The villagers of Xiao claim to have spotted Hou Yi east of the rice fields, appearing to fight the sky itself. Go beyond the rice fields to the ruined plains and investigate the battlefield. 
x4tagMq01_Task_07=Retrieve the fragments of Hou Yi's bow
x4tagMq01_Task_07_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}You found Hou Yi in a ravaged landscape - as he revealed, the Ten Suns, the kin of the Jade Emperor, attacked and incapacitated him. He believes the Suns to be the instigators of this recent chaos. Hou Yi asked you to find and return the two fragments of his shattered bow, that have fallen from the sky all around the Xiao countryside, while he recovers from his injuries. The prayer beads he gave you will allow you to wield the legendary weapon safely.
x4tagMq01_Task_07b=Return the fragments of Hou Yi's bow
x4tagMq01_Task_07b_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}You found Hou Yi in a ravaged landscape - as he revealed, the Ten Suns, the kin of the Jade Emperor, attacked and incapacitated him. He believes the Suns to be the instigators of this recent chaos. You have found the fragments of his shattered bow. Return them to their rightful owner.
x4tagMq01_Task_08=Cross the cave and reach the city of Pingyang
x4tagMq01_Task_08_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}After helping Hou Yi, he instructed you to travel to Pingyang, where he believes Qiong Qi to be headed. Either way, Emperor Yao must learn of the events and the Suns' involvement. He mentioned a small passage that will lead you directly into the Northern Outskirts.
x4tagMq01_Task_09=Vanquish Qiong Qi
x4tagMq01_Task_09_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}Hou Yi's suspicions turned out to be true: Qiong Qi and his minions set their eyes on Pingyang. Vanquish the beast once and for all.
x4tagMq01_Task_10=Meet Emperor Yao
x4tagMq01_Task_10_Desc=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}You defeated Qiong Qi and his minions, but as long as the Suns are on the loose, peace is fleeting. Tell Emperor Yao of your findings.
x4tagMq01_Task_10_Completed=Emperor Yao called upon you to defend his realm from a great, inexplicable evil: beasts of all kinds are sweeping across the lands causing mayhem, their raids led by the fearsome winged tiger Qiong Qi. Upon arriving, the Emperor's Summer palace was already under attack. {^n}{^n}You defeated Qiong Qi and his minions, but as long as the Suns are on the loose, peace is fleeting. You told Emperor Yao of your findings.
x4tagMq02_Title=Seeking An Audience
x4tagMq02_Task_01=Fight your way through Yao's mausoleum
x4tagMq02_Task_01_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}Use the secret passage through Emperor Yao's unfinished mausoleum and find the ascent to the Eight Pillars, the only way into the Heavenly Palace.
x4tagMq02_Task_01A=Find the keystones
x4tagMq02_Task_01A_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}You have found the ghost of the mausoleum's architect. Get the four keystones needed to pass through the mausoleum and lay his soul to rest.
x4tagMq02_Task_01B=Exit the mausoleum
x4tagMq02_Task_01B_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}You have the keystones. Use them to exit the mausoleum and enter the ascent.
x4tagMq02_Task_02=Fight your way up to the Eight Pillars
x4tagMq02_Task_02_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more. {^n}{^n}The Ascent is being ravaged by crazed beings riled up by the Suns. Fight your way to the portal.
x4tagMq02_Task_03=Speak with the Jade Emperor
x4tagMq02_Task_03_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}You have reached the heavenly palace. Seek an audience with the Jade Emperor and ask him about the Ten Suns. He appears to be expecting you.
x4tagMq02_Task_04=Seek out Sihai Longwang
x4tagMq02_Task_04_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}Shrouding himself in mystery, the Jade Emperor merely told you that the Ten Suns have learned of their own impending fate, and are now trying to avert it. He offered you no help - after all, the Suns are his grandchildren, and he will not move against them. Hou Yi, confused by the Jade Emperor's secretiveness, advised you to take matters into your own hands. Sihai Longwang, the Dragon King of the Four Seas, is powerful enough to challenge the Suns. Traverse the mystical portal into the realm of Sihai LongWang and seek him out. 
x4tagMq02_Task_05=Defeat Sihai Longwang
x4tagMq02_Task_05_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}When you reached Sihai Longwang's lair, he challenged you to a duel. Only the strong are worthy of his time. Stand your ground and live up to your reputation.
x4tagMq02_Task_06=Cross the portal to travel to Egypt
x4tagMq02_Task_06_Desc=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}Impressed with your strength, Sihai Longwang agreed to help you: he will forge a seal that will bind the Suns to the earth. To do so, however, you will need to recover one of the orbs powering his smithy from a place far away: Egypt. Cross the portal and recover Longwang's orb from whoever stole it.
x4tagMq02_Task_06_Completed=Your tale greatly distressed Emperor Yao: why would the Ten Suns move against the mortal realm? And how can they be stopped? He advised you ascent to the Heavenly Palace and seek the council of the Jade Emperor himself. As their grandfather, he must know more.{^n}{^n}Impressed with your strength, Sihai Longwang agreed to help you: he will forge a seal that will bind the Suns to the earth. To do so, however, you will need to recover one of the orbs powering his smithy from a place far away: Egypt. You have crossed the portal and are on your way to recover Longwang's orb from whoever stole it.
x4tagMq03_Title=A Familiar Face
x4tagMq03_Task_01=Find Imhotep in the Temple District
x4tagMq03_Task_01_Desc=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}You sought out your old acquaintance Imhotep, scholar of the Prometheus Order, for pointers, but he was nowhere to be found. Rumor has it he ventured into dangerous catacombs. Find Imhotep.
x4tagMq03_Task_02=Enter the Abydos Necropolis and find the source of the undead invasion
x4tagMq03_Task_02_Desc=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}You found Imhotep in the Solar Temple of Ra - as it turns out, he was investigating the undead invasion. He does not know about Sihai's orb, but he told you that the undead armies appear to come from the Abydos Necropolis. Perhaps it is all connected? Enter the Necropolis and find the source of the undead invasion.
x4tagMq03_Task_03=Warn Pharaoh Tutankhamun of his father's resurrection
x4tagMq03_Task_03_Desc=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}You found the origin of the undead invasion: the Suns resurrected Akhenaten, the heretic pharaoh, to be their champion. Zazamankh, a supplicant of Akhenaten, stole Sihai's orb to power his master's resurrection. You defeated Zazamankh, but Akhenaten and his undead army are already marching on Thebes to overthrow Pharaoh Tutankhamun, Akhenaten's son. Travel to Thebes and warn the Pharaoh before it's too late.
x4tagMq03_Task_04=Defeat Akhenaten
x4tagMq03_Task_04_Desc=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}The young pharaoh and his advisers were grateful for your warning and pointed you towards the ruined temple of Aten in the wastelands east of Thebes. If Akhenaten is planning an attack, this is where he and his army of undead must be gathering their strength. Head to the temple, vanquish the resurrected heretic, and reclaim Longwang's stolen orb.
x4tagMq03_Task_05=Return to Sihai Longwang's forge
x4tagMq03_Task_05_Desc=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}After a long and terrifying fight, you defeated Akhenaten, the resurrected pharaoh, and recovered Longwang's stolen orb. Return to Sihai Longwang's forge using the portal. Akhenaten might be dealt with, but the Suns are not.
x4tagMq03_Task_05_Completed=A strange, dark spell shrouds Egypt: armies of undead are rising from their graves, heading eastwards and striking terror into the Egyptians' hearts. Could this possibly be connected to the Ten Suns? Either way, you must not dally: find Sihai Longwang's missing orb and return it to him so he can forge a seal for the Suns.{^n}{^n}After a long and terrifying fight, you defeated Akhenaten, the resurrected pharaoh, and recovered Longwang's stolen orb. You have returned to Sihai Longwang's forge and handed him the the orb.
x4tagMq04_Title=A God No More
x4tagMq04_Task_01=Head back to Pingyang
x4tagMq04_Task_01_Desc=Longwang stood true to his promise, and forged you a seal that will force the Suns in their earthly form when used. He teleported you back to Emperor Yao's palace to restock before facing the Suns. Once ready, you must head into the Marshlands and ascend to the Shrine of the Suns atop the Flaming Mountains, where the Suns have last been sighted.{^n}{^n}Speak with Emperor Yao.
x4tagMq04_Task_02=Reach the Marshland
x4tagMq04_Task_02_Desc=Longwang stood true to his promise, and forged you a seal that will force the Suns in their earthly form when used. He teleported you back to Emperor Yao's palace to restock before facing the Suns. Once ready, you must head into the Marshlands and ascend to the Shrine of the Suns atop the Flaming Mountains, where the Suns have last been sighted.{^n}{^n}Exit the city via the secret tunnel near the Pingyang Portal, cross the Marshlands and climb the Flaming Mountains. 
x4tagMq04_Task_03=Climb the Flaming Mountains
x4tagMq04_Task_03_Desc=Longwang stood true to his promise, and forged you a seal that will force the Suns in their earthly form when used. He teleported you back to Emperor Yao's palace to restock before facing the Suns. Once ready, you must head into the Marshlands and ascend to the Shrine of the Suns atop the Flaming Mountains, where the Suns have last been sighted.{^n}{^n}A terrifying sight met you upon reaching the mountains: the Suns have completely scorched the lands, their fires spreading fast. Fight through their minions and reach the Shrine before it is too late.
x4tagMq04_Task_04=Defeat the Ten Suns
x4tagMq04_Task_04_Desc=Longwang stood true to his promise, and forged you a seal that will force the Suns in their earthly form when used. He teleported you back to Emperor Yao's palace to restock before facing the Suns. Once ready, you must head into the Marshlands and ascend to the Shrine of the Suns atop the Flaming Mountains, where the Suns have last been sighted.{^n}{^n}Longwang's seal worked, transforming the Ten Suns into their earthly forms. Vanquish them all before they can lay waste to the earth.
x4tagMq04_Task_04_Completed=Longwang stood true to his promise, and forged you a seal that will force the Suns in their earthly form when used. He teleported you back to Emperor Yao's palace to restock before facing the Suns. Once ready, you must head into the Marshlands and ascend to the Shrine of the Suns atop the Flaming Mountains, where the Suns have last been sighted.{^n}{^n}Longwang's seal worked, transforming the Ten Suns into their earthly forms. You have vanquished the Suns, and the Jade Emperor has rekindled them. Now the world has seen a new dawn and humanity will prosper again.
x4tagXIX=XIX
x4tagXX=XX
x4tagXXI=XXI
x4tagXXII=XXII
x4tagQAct07=Act VI
