// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagSq101_Title=The Root of the Problem
x4tagSq101_Desc1=Ghosts haunt the area around an ethereal tree, strange markings carved into the ground. {^n}{^n}Follow the faint chanting in the distance and find it's origin.
x4tagSq101_Desc2=Ghosts haunt the area around an ethereal tree, strange markings carved into the ground. {^n}{^n}The cause of the corruption seems to spring from beneath the haunted tree. Seek the caverns entrance at the river's source.
x4tagSq101_Desc3=Ghosts haunt the area around an ethereal tree, strange markings carved into the ground. {^n}{^n}You found a cave behind a waterfall near the tree, swarming with restless ghosts. Locate the source of the haunting.
x4tagSq101_Desc5=Ghosts haunt the area around an ethereal tree, strange markings carved into the ground. {^n}{^n}You came upon a dead pirate captain, still unaware of his death. Defeat the ghost and put his soul to rest.
x4tagSq101_Desc6=Ghosts haunt the area around an ethereal tree, strange markings carved into the ground. {^n}{^n}Vanquishing the ghost captain put the restless sailors out of their misery. You cleared the haunting.
x4tagSq102_Title=A Book and its Cover
x4tagSq102_Desc1=A terrified woman has begged you to ascend Kunlun to find an antidote capable of curing her husband from a dangerous poisoning. {^n}{^n}Find the antidote atop Kunlun.
x4tagSq102_Desc2=A terrified woman has begged you to ascend Kunlun to find an antidote capable of curing her husband from a dangerous poisoning. {^n}{^n}The tower is filled to the brim with monks intent on stopping you from ascending the tower. Fight your way through the temple.
x4tagSq102_Desc3=A terrified woman has begged you to ascend Kunlun to find an antidote capable of curing her husband from a dangerous poisoning. {^n}{^n}The monk Fa Hai is not willing to part with the antidote. Defeat him and retrieve the antidote.
x4tagSq102_Desc4=A terrified woman has begged you to ascend Kunlun to find an antidote capable of curing her husband from a dangerous poisoning. {^n}{^n}After Fa Hai's defeat and the antidote in your possession, the only thing left to do is bring it to Bai Su Zhen and hope it helps bring back her husband.
x4tagSq102_Desc5=A grieving woman has begged you to ascend Kunlun itself and bring back the antidote capable of bringing back her husband from the brink. {^n}{^n}Bai Su Zhen successfully healed her husband with the antidote you provided. Grateful for your service, Xu Xian offered you a prize fit for a champion.
x4tagSq104_Title=The Council of Three
x4tagSq104_Desc1=Bandits plague the Silk Road, blocking off the passage to Pingyang and harassing the area from their hideout. Deal with bandits.
x4tagSq104_Desc2=Bandits plague the Silk Road, blocking off the passage to Pingyang and harassing the area from their hideout. Deal with bandits. {^n}{^n}As it turns out, they were slavers too, locking peasants into cages in a nearby cave. Find the key to their cages and free the peasants.
x4tagSq104_Desc3=Bandits plague the Silk Road, blocking off the passage to Pingyang and harassing the area from their hideout. Deal with bandits. {^n}{^n}You freed the captured villagers - perhaps you should light a few candles at the nearby shrine to honor those who didn't make it.
x4tagSq104_Desc4=Bandits plague the Silk Road, blocking off the passage to Pingyang and harassing the area from their hideout. Deal with bandits. {^n}{^n}When honoring the fallen, a Qilin, a mystical chimera, appeared to you and rewarded you for your virtue and kindness.
x4tagSq105_Title=Monkey Business
x4tagSq105_Desc1=Monkey beasts riled up by Qiong Qi attacked the village of Lai and stole their idol. {^n}{^n}Shan, a crone from Lai, begged you to find the idol and return it to the village, lest it lose the favor of the gods.
x4tagSq105_Desc2=Monkey beasts riled up by Qiong Qi attacked the village of Lai and stole their idol. {^n}{^n}A gorilla shaman guards the idol - defeat it, then return the sacred object to Shan.
x4tagSq105_Desc3=Monkey beasts riled up by Qiong Qi attacked the village of Lai and stole their idol. {^n}{^n}A gorilla shaman guarded the idol - return it to the village.
x4tagSq105_Desc4=Monkey beasts riled up by Qiong Qi attacked the village of Lai and stole their idol. {^n}{^n}The gorilla shaman guarded a stolen idol, return it to the village of Lai, where it belongs.
x4tagSq105_Desc5=Monkey beasts riled up by Qiong Qi attacked the village of Lai and stole their idol. {^n}{^n}Upon defeating their shaman, the frenzied monkeys made off into the forest. You returned it to Lai and restored the favor of the gods.
x4tagSq201_Title=Emperor Yao's Bell
x4tagSq201_Desc1=You met Kwan-Yu the bellmaker and learned of his troubles. {^n}{^n}To help him you must find the courtier Ming Lin and get the plans for the bell from him.
x4tagSq201_Desc2=You met Kwan-Yu the bellmaker and learned of his troubles. {^n}{^n}You have found Ming Lin and got the plans for the bell. Fight your way through the brigands and bring them to Kwan-Yu.
x4tagSq201_Desc3=A group of bandits took the life of a courtier and stole what appears to be plans for some sort of bell. {^n}{^n}Find someone who can tell you more.
x4tagSq201_Desc4=You met Kwan-Yu the bellmaker and learned of his troubles. {^n}{^n}You have found Ming Lin and got the plans for the bell. You brought them to Kwan-Yu. You have the honor of first ringing the bell.
x4tagSq201_Desc5=You met Kwan-Yu the bellmaker and learned of his troubles. {^n}{^n}You returned his plans and defeated the brigands.
x4tagSq202_Title=Love and Loss
x4tagSq202_Desc1=Wang Wei, a citizen of Pingyang is devastated: Li Qiang, a notorious brigand, abducted Wang Wei’s bride, Li Min. He asked you to find and save her.{^n}{^n}Find Li Min and defeat Li Qiang.
x4tagSq202_Desc2=Wang Wei, a citizen of Pingyang is devastated: Li Qiang, a notorious brigand, abducted Wang Wei’s bride, Li Min. He asked you to find and save her.{^n}{^n}As it turned out, Li Min wasn't stolen - she ran off with Li Qiang, whom she describes as her true love. Return to Wang Wei and tell him you were not able to find her.
x4tagSq202_Desc3=Li Min, a bride from Pingyang, has run away from her betrothed to be with her true love, the brigand Li Qiang. {^n}{^n}As it turned out, Li Min wasn't stolen - she ran off with Li Qiang, whom she describes as her true love. Return to Wang Wei and tell him you were not able to find her.
x4tagSq202_Desc5=Wang Wei, a citizen of Pingyang is devastated: Li Qiang, a notorious brigand, abducted Wang Wei’s bride, Li Min. He asked you to find and save her.{^n}{^n}You returned to Wang Wei, telling him that Li Min was nowhere to be found. The two lovers can now live in peace.
x4tagSq203_Title=Lust for Jade
x4tagSq203_Desc1=Mogwai have seized the Yùshí jade mine and butchered the miners. You took care of the ones guarding the entrance, but you can hear their grunts from within the mine's tunnels. {^n}{^n}Venture into the mine and deal with the Mogwai infestation.
x4tagSq203_Desc2=Mogwai have seized the Yùshí jade mine and butchered the miners. You took care of the ones guarding the entrance, but you can hear their grunts from within the mine's tunnels. {^n}{^n}You defeated the Mogwai Taskmaster in the depths of the mine. Look for survivors on the surface.
x4tagSq203_Desc3=Mogwai have seized the Yùshí jade mine and butchered the miners. You can hear their grunting from deep within the mine's tunnels. {^n}{^n}You defeated the Mogwai Taskmaster in the depths of the mine. Look for survivors on the surface.
x4tagSq203_Desc4=Mogwai have seized the Yùshí jade mine and butchered the miners. You can hear their grunting from deep within the mine's tunnels. {^n}{^n}You defeated the Mogwai Taskmaster in the depths of the mine. Take care of the Mogwai at the entrance, then look for survivors on the surface.
x4tagSq203_Desc5=Mogwai have seized the Yùshí jade mine and butchered the miners. You can hear their grunting from deep within the mine's tunnels. {^n}{^n}You defeated the Mogwai Taskmaster in the depths of the caves, and returned the mines to the miners.
x4tagSq204_Title=Fire and Gold
x4tagSq204_Desc1=The fire god Huoshen has aligned himself with the Ten Suns and is melting down the idols of Jinshen, the god of gold - terrible calamity will befall heaven and earth should Jinshen's Golden Idols of Heaven ever be destroyed. {^n}{^n}Venture into the Golden Idol Cave and stop Huoshen before it is too late.
x4tagSq204_Desc2=The fire god Huoshen has aligned himself with the Ten Suns and is melting down the idols of Jinshen, the god of gold - terrible calamity will befall heaven and earth should Jinshen's Golden Idols of Heaven ever be destroyed. {^n}{^n}Fight your way through Huosen's fire demons and stop the mad fire god before it is too late.
x4tagSq204_Desc3=The fire god Huoshen has aligned himself with the Ten Suns and is melting down the idols of Jinshen, the god of gold - terrible calamity will befall heaven and earth should Jinshen's Golden Idols of Heaven ever be destroyed. {^n}{^n}You have defeated Huoshen, averting a catastrophe. Return to Jinshen and tell him of your victory.
x4tagSq204_Desc4=The fire god Huoshen aligned himself with the Ten Suns and was attempting to melt down the idols of Jinshen, the god of gold - terrible calamity would have befallen heaven and earth should Jinshen's Golden Idols of Heaven ever be destroyed. {^n}{^n}You told Jinshen of your victory, and he rewarded you greatly.
x4tagSq205_Title=Heavenly Lovers
x4tagSq205_Desc1=Zhinu, the Jade Emperor's divine granddaughter, is devastated: her grandfather allows her to see her mortal husband Niu Lang but once a year, when he creates a bridge between heaven and earth. Now demons, seemingly under the command of the Ten Suns, have seized the bridge, keeping Niu Lang from seeing Zhinu. She asked you to defeat the demons so she can be reunited with her lover. {^n}{^n}Find the heavenly bridge and defeat the Suns' demons.
x4tagSq205_Desc2=Zhinu, the Jade Emperor's divine granddaughter, is devastated: her grandfather allows her to see her mortal husband Niu Lang but once a year, when he creates a bridge between heaven and earth. Now demons, seemingly under the command of the Ten Suns, have seized the bridge, keeping Niu Lang from seeing Zhinu. She asked you to defeat the demons so she can be reunited with her lover. {^n}{^n}You defeated the demons. Return to Zhinu and tell her of the good news.
x4tagSq205_Desc3=Zhinu, the Jade Emperor's divine granddaughter, is devastated: her grandfather allows her to see her mortal husband Niu Lang but once a year, when he creates a bridge between heaven and earth. Now demons, seemingly under the command of the Ten Suns, have seized the bridge, keeping Niu Lang from seeing Zhinu. She asked you to defeat the demons so she can be reunited with her lover. {^n}{^n}You defeated the demons and reunited Zhinu and Niu Lang.
x4tagSq206_Title=Maze of Mirages
x4tagSq206_Desc1=Traveling to Sihai Longwang, you have found yourself in a surreal landscape filled with eerie presence. {^n}{^n}Delve deeper to find the source.
x4tagSq206_Desc2=Traveling to Sihai Longwang, you have found yourself in a surreal landscape filled with eerie presence. {^n}{^n}You found the source of the illusions - a colossal clam creature capable of weaving illusions. Slay the beast.
x4tagSq206_Desc3=Traveling to Sihai Longwang, you have found yourself in a surreal landscape filled with eerie presence. {^n}{^n}You took care of the source of the illusions, a colossal clam creature capable of weaving illusions.
x4tagSq301_Title=Shadowstone of Anubis
x4tagSq301_Desc1=Khemu, the elder lorekeeper for the Asyut tribe is a wellspring of knowledge for the region, but will only reveal his secrets to those who earn his trust. When asked how to earn it, he mentioned a crypt under the Collapsed Catacombs, which apparently holds a lost amulet known as the "Shadowstone of Anubis."{^n}{^n}Venture into the Collapsed Catacombs and find the Shadowstone of Anubis.
x4tagSq301_Desc2=Khemu, the elder lorekeeper for the Asyut tribe is a wellspring of knowledge for the region, but will only reveal his secrets to those who earn his trust. When asked how to earn it, he mentioned a crypt under the Collapsed Catacombs, which apparently holds a lost amulet known as the "Shadowstone of Anubis."{^n}{^n}You found the Shadowstone, bring it to Khemu.
x4tagSq301_Desc3=Exploring the innermost chambers of the Collapsed Catacombs, you found a peculiar chest bearing a jackal sigil. Inside it, you found a beautifully crafted amulet made of pure onyx. {^n}{^n}Perhaps someone at the Asyut encampment can tell you more about its origin.
x4tagSq301_Desc4=You brought Khemu the Shadowstone of Anubis - what will he do with it?{^n}{^n}Perhaps Khemu will have more such tasks, and rewards, in the near future.
x4tagSq302_Title=A Venom Most Foul
x4tagSq302_Desc1=Numerous soldiers of the Pharaoh have fallen victim to a mysterious strain of poison.{^n}{^n}User, a travelling physician, asked for your help finding the root of the problem. Traverse the bank of the Nile in search for the answer.
x4tagSq302_Desc2=Corpses of soldiers and animals littered the entrance to a cave in the Nile Borderlands - all seem to have died of poison.{^n}{^n}Explore the cave and find the source of the poisonings.
x4tagSq302_Desc3=Numerous soldiers of the Pharaoh have fallen victim to a mysterious strain of poison.{^n}{^n}Investigating a cave in the Nile Borderlands, you found that the Children of Serket are behind the scheme, intending to cast doubt on Tutankhamun's rulership. Collect samples of the scorpions' venom as proof.
x4tagSq302_Desc4=Numerous soldiers of the Pharaoh have fallen victim to a mysterious strain of poison.{^n}{^n}You collected enough samples of venom from the scorpions. Bring them back to User.
x4tagSq302_Desc5=Corpses of soldiers and animals littered the entrance to a cave in the Abydos Barrens - all seem to have died of poison.{^n}{^n}You collected enough samples of venom from the scorpions. Bring the samples to someone who can make use of it - perhaps a physician.
x4tagSq302_Desc6=Numerous soldiers of the Pharaoh have fallen victim to a mysterious strain of poison.{^n}{^n}You investigated the strange plague and unraveled a scheme by the Children of Serket. User will use the samples to create an antidote putting an end to their machinations.
x4tagSq303_Title=No Peace for the Fallen
x4tagSq303_Desc1=You have talked to Re’yesh. He told you that the bandits have entered into the funerary temple and are raiding the tombs. {^n}{^n}You must defeat the looters so that the workers can repair the temple.
x4tagSq303_Desc2=You stumbled upon several corpses of workers that were killed by bandits intent on looting the the necropolis. {^n}{^n}Fight off the looters.
x4tagSq303_Desc3=The leader of the looters has been slain, regrettably, none of the workers survived the ordeal. {^n}{^n}Return Re'yesh and inform him that his workers have perished.
x4tagSq303_Desc4=The leader of the looters has been slain, regrettably, none of the workers survived the ordeal. {^n}{^n}Find whoever was in charge of the restoration project and inform him that his workers have perished.
x4tagSq303_Desc5=Re’yesh and his workers were attacked while restoring a funerary temple for the Pharaoh. Bandits came in, killed his workers and tried to defile the temple. {^n}{^n}The workers were slain but you dealt with the looters and Re'yesh can continue restoring the funerary temple.
x4tagSq401_Title=The Phoenix and the Frog
x4tagSq401_Desc1=Jin Chan, a golden toad, is in trouble: The Jade Emperor sent a phoenix named Fenghuang to rescue him, but Fenghuang is nowhere to be seen.{^n}{^n}Search the Marshland and find out what happened to Fenghuang.
x4tagSq401_Desc2=Jin Chan, a golden toad, is in trouble: The Jade Emperor sent a phoenix named Fenghuang to rescue him, but Fenghuang is nowhere to be seen.{^n}{^n}For some reason, Fenghuang has retreated into its egg - you arrived just in time to save it from the demons trying to pry it open. Release Fenghuang.
x4tagSq401_Desc3=Jin Chan, a golden toad, is in trouble: The Jade Emperor sent a phoenix named Fenghuang to rescue him, but Fenghuang is nowhere to be seen.{^n}{^n}You released Fenghuang. Return to Jin Chan to tell him the good news.
x4tagSq401_Desc4=Jin Chan, a golden toad, was in trouble: The Jade Emperor sent a phoenix named Fenghuang to rescue him, but Fenghuang is nowhere to be seen.{^n}{^n}Fenghuang and Jin Chan have been reunited and will return to the Heavenly Palace.
x4tagSq402_Title=Just Desserts
x4tagSq402_Desc1=You came across a peculiar Yaoguai who tasked you with bringing another demon to justice and saving his dinner. {^n}{^n}Head up to the Scorched Ridge and search for the demon.
x4tagSq402_Desc2=You came across a peculiar Yaoguai who tasked you with bringing another demon to justice and saving his dinner. {^n}{^n}You have unlocked the entrance to the cave. Find the demon.
x4tagSq402_Desc3=You came across a peculiar Yaoguai who tasked you with bringing another demon to justice and saving his dinner. {^n}{^n}You have defeated the demon. Return to Bao.
x4tagSq402_Desc4=You came across a peculiar Yaoguai who tasked you with bringing another demon to justice and saving his dinner. {^n}{^n}You have defeated the demon and returned to Bao.
x4tagQuestRegionSQ101=Mainland China
x4tagQuestRegionSQ102=Mainland China
x4tagQuestRegionSQ104=Mainland China
x4tagQuestRegionSQ105=Mainland China
x4tagQuestRegionSQ201=Pingyang
x4tagQuestRegionSQ202=Pingyang
x4tagQuestRegionSQ203=Pingyang
x4tagQuestRegionSQ204=Pingyang
x4tagQuestRegionSQ205=The Heavens
x4tagQuestRegionSQ206=The Heavens
x4tagQuestRegionSQ301=Lower Egypt
x4tagQuestRegionSQ302=Lower Egypt
x4tagQuestRegionSQ303=Lower Egypt
x4tagQuestRegionSQ401=The Marshland
x4tagQuestRegionSQ402=The Ravaged Square
