// AUTOGENERATED FILE
// DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// ALL EDITS MUST BE DONE IN THEIR RESPECTIVE EXCEL SHEETS AND EXPORTED!
// encoding = unicode (16-bit)
x4tagThree_Dots=...
x4tagSQ_101_pirate_captain_A1=What are you waiting for, you lazy, rotten fools? Row, for Heaven's sake! Row, or we're never going home ag-{^n}{^n}Wait. Wait, you're not one of my men, so what are you doing on my ship? No ... don't say anything, I know that look. Men, over here! We got ourselves a stowaway!
x4tagSQ_101_pirate_captain_A7=...
x4tagSQ_105_Oldwife_Shan_Dia_A1=Heavens be praised, you killed them all! I feared they would wipe out the entire village. Perhaps you could track the ones that got away? You see, those beasts took our temple idol, and if we don’t get it back—well, I have lived long enough to know only fools gamble with the favor of the ancestors.{^n}{^n}Please, I implore you, at least consider it. We have little, but if you help us, you will not go unrewarded. I promise.
x4tagSQ_105_Oldwife_Shan_Dia_A7=Yes? Please, you must track down those beasts - we cannot afford to lose the favor of the ancestors.
x4tagSQ_105_Oldwife_Shan_Dia_B1=Gods, you did it! I don’t even know how to thank you ... Here, take this, I drummed it up from the other villagers. Those fools think we should have just let those beasts get away with the idol, but they don’t know a thing about how this world works.{^n}{^n}Say, would you happen to be bound for Pingyang? My son Xian lives there, and I haven’t heard from him in almost a year. If you could just let him know his mother is all right ... well, it would mean a lot to me.
x4tagSQ_105_Oldwife_Shan_Dia_B7=Safe travels. And thank you again for helping us.
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_X1=Heavens ... Oh, Heavens, what did I do. What did I do?
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_A1=What ... who are you? No, wait. Wait, I know you, you're the one who slayed the Telkine! What by the Heavens brought you back here?{^n}{^n}Well ... it does not matter. I can sense that you are a good soul, and I need your help. Something horrible happened, and I - Heavens, there is no good way to say this. My name is Bai Su Zhen, and I am a snake demon. Not the malicious sort, I never did or wished any harm upon anyone ... All I wanted was to live my life in peace with my husband, Xu Xian. {^n}{^n}Now, I know what you are wondering: what in the world happened? Well, two days ago, a supposed "monk", Fa Hai, came by and poisoned my husband. He is still alive, but without the antidote, he will not last much longer, and Fa Hai says he will not give him it until I leave Xian. I am a demon, he says, and our kind must not consort with humans. {^n}{^n}Please, mortal – if you have any heart left in you, you must help me. I love Xian, I always have, and all I want is a quiet life with him, regardless of my true form. Climb the Kunlun to find Fa Hai and his antidote. If you do, you will have my eternal gratitude.
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_A7=Yes? You must find the antidote, else Xian will be lost to me forever. Please.
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_B1=Oh, Heavens, you did it, you did it! Please, give me the antidote, I will give it to him right away. In the meantime, tell me ... what happened on top of that mountain? I sensed a great battle.
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_B2=Hm. I was hoping you could reason with him ... Heavens, I don't even know what to say. {^n}You know ... it is ironic, isn't it? Fa Hai wanted to protect himself and the world from the "evil influence" of a demon, and now that very act cost him his life.{^n}Anyway, I have taken enough of your time - you are probably here to investigate the strange things that are happening across China. Here, take this, it should help you on your quest. Travel safely, Slayer of the Telkine.
x4tagSQ102_bai_su_zhen_B7=Slayer of the Telkine ... I trust you are well? My dear Xian is looking healthier every minute, all thanks to you.
x4tagSQ104_qilin_A1=And perished have their wicked souls,{^n}How foolish were they not to know, {^n}That we all reap the death we sow.
x4tagSQ104_qilin_A7=Hero.
x4tagSQ104_slave_caged_1_X1=Oh, thank you! You spared us from a miserable fate. I don't even know what to say - may the Heavens smile on you.
x4tagSQ104_slave_caged_2_X1=Oh, good Heavens, thank you! These men would have sold us to who knows who.
x4tagSQ104_slave_caged_3_X1=Oh, Heavens, freedom! Whoever you are, thank you!
x4tagSQ104_slave_caged_4_X1=Finally! I thought we were going to die in there. Thank you, stranger, thank you!
x4tagSQ104_slave_caged_5_X1=... And here I thought I'd die in these shackles. You saved me ... thank you.
x4tagSQ104_slave_hero_caged_A1=Well, well, you certainly know how to fight. Thank you for saving us. I hope it is not too much to ask, but should you happen to pass by a shrine, could you perhaps light a candle for the folk who perished here? Their souls ... they will need guidance.
x4tagSQ104_slave_hero_caged_A7=My friend.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_X0=Come on, Lin ... come on.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_A1=Wait - yes, you there, soldier. Look, I am terribly sorry to ask this, but I need your help. And before you go on, I work for the Son of Heaven himself, so by helping me, you are helping him too. Convinced?{^n}Good. My name is Kwan-Yu, and I am a bellmaker. The Son of Heaven tasked me with forging a new bell for his palace, an honor beyond words. The problem is, my associate, Ming Lin, should have brought me my schematics hours ago, but he is nowhere to be seen. Please, my friend, could you go look for him? He's small, haggard, and always wears his imperial uniform, you will recognize him. Please - I will make it worth your while.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_A7=Yes? Please, I need those schematics. If he lost them ... Heavens, let's not even think about that.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_B1=There you are! What happened? Did you find Ming Lin and my schematics?{^n}He ... he is dead? Good Heavens, I ... I don't even know what to say. His wife, Lihua, she must know right away. I feel horrible even asking this, but did you find the schematics? Let me see ... yes, here they are. Let me get to work and apply the finishing touches. Dead friend or not, one must not keep the Son of Heaven waiting.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_X1=Let's see ...
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_X2=Almost there ...
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_X3=Now this ... and ...
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_C1=There we are. Say, would you like to ring it? You returned the schematics, so the honor should be yours.
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_C2=Good - thank you. Here, take this, it is the least I can do. Now please, I have to think. How should I tell Lihua about this?
x4tagSQ201_kwan_yu_C7=Oh Lin ...
x4tagSQ202_wang_wei_A1=Oh, thank the Heavens - you are a fighter, aren't you? A mercenary, perhaps? Well, it doesn't matter, if you can stand your ground in a fight, I must ask for your help. I will be swift: someone abducted my soon-to-be bride, Li Min, some blackguard of a brigand. I followed them to the tunnels, but it's just too dangerous down there to push through on my own. Maybe you could help me? To think what this brute will do to my Li Min ...{^n}{^n}Please, find her. I am not a man of means, but what little I have shall be yours if you bring her back. I will wait for you right here.
x4tagSQ202_wang_wei_A7=What is it? Please, you need to hurry!
x4tagSQ202_wang_wei_B1=Yes? Wait, what's this, her comb? What happened? Tell me, soldier, tell me now. {^n}I ... I see. And you're sure they're gone? Foolish question ... You would not be here if you weren't. Well, I don't know what to say, stranger. I need some time to myself now. I need to think.
x4tagSQ202_wang_wei_B7=Please, just ... leave me be.
x4tagSQ202_li_qiang_X1=We'll find a way, trust me. We-{^n}Wait. Wait, someone's coming - stay back!
x4tagSQ202_li_min_X1=Qiang! NO!
x4tagSQ202_li_min_A1=No! No, please, don't harm him! Please! {^n}{^n}Ancestors ... what a mess this is, what a cursed mess. Wang Wei sent you, didn't he? Of course he did. Look, this man here, Li Qiang, he didn't "steal" me, I went with him of my own free will. He and I ... well, we love each other. Wang Wei, he's a good man, but this marriage, it's what my parents want, not I. {^n}{^n}What to do, what to do ... wait, I have an idea. ... this comb here, take it to Wang Wei and tell him we escaped. If you have ever truly loved, don't force me to go back to him, I would spend the rest of my life embittered, and so would he. Please, I beg you ... do the right thing.
x4tagSQ202_li_min_A7=Please ... do the right thing.
x4tagSQ202_li_min_B7=Thank you. I will never forget what you have done for us, stranger. Never.
x4tagSQ203_mingyu_A1=Did you ... did you slay the Mogwai? All of them? They just barged in here and started butchering us. I don't understand this, when did those beasts get so bold, and why? Oh, well ... I suppose it doesn't matter.{^n}{^n}I will stay here a little longer to see who they killed, so I can pass on the names. There will be a lot of mourning in my village tonight. Oh, and ... here. I am probably not allowed to give you this, but you deserve a reward for delivering vengeance.
x4tagSQ203_mingyu_A7=The drought, now this ... What's happening to these lands?
x4tagSQ204_jinshen_A1=A m-mortal ... What are you - ah, it ... it does not matter. Huǒshén, the g- god of fire. He ... is trying to melt down the cave's idols. You must ... must not let that happen, mortal, it ... it would destroy ...
x4tagSQ204_jinshen_A7=... Huǒshén ... stop ...
x4tagSQ204_jinshen_B1=My powers are returning ... This means you stopped him.{^n}Mortal, you probably do not have the slightest inkling of the calamity you averted here. Had Huǒshén succeeded in melting down my idols, he would have burnt down heavens and earth alike. I still do not understand why he would do this ... but he has been embroiled with the Ten Suns, the Jade Emperor's kin, not too long ago, so perhaps there is a connection.{^n}{^n}Anyway, you acted valiantly, so you deserve to be rewarded. Here, take this - may it serve you well on your travels. Now go on - I assume you are headed to the Heavenly Palace, so you still have a journey ahead of you.
x4tagSQ204_jinshen_B7=Mortal. Travel safely.
x4tagSQ_205_Zhinu_A1=Who - oh, Heavens, forgive me, you should not see me like this. {^n}{^n}That is ... I hesitate to ask, but perhaps you might help me? My name is Zhinu, and I am, as you might know, the Jade Emperor's granddaughter. I will not bore you with the details of my tale, but suffice it to say that my husband Niu Lang is a mortal, much to my grandfather's chagrin. He only allows us to see each other once a year, and he forms a bridge between heaven and earth solely for this purpose. Now, you might have heard that my cousins, the Suns, have been acting ... erratically lately. In addition to all they did to your realm, they sent demon spawn to the celestrial bridge my grandfather created, and are keeping Niu Lang out. {^n}{^n}You can see where this is headed: the bridge will only persist a few hours longer before it vanishes. I know we are strangers, but could you slay these demons so I can see my Niu Lang? Please ... if nothing is done, we will be apart for another year.
x4tagSQ_205_Zhinu_A7=Yes? Have you slain the demons on the bridge already?
x4tagSQ_205_Zhinu_B1=Oh, mortal, you did it! I do not even know how to thank you. Here, this should be of use to you on your journey - now forgive me, I will go see Niu Lang. There is so much I must tell him, so much.
x4tagSQ_205_Zhinu_B7=Mortal. I will not forget this.
x4tagSQ301_Khemu_A1=Well, well ... I know an intrepid adventurer when I see one. Say, could I interest you in aiding an old Asyut? My name is Khemusenatef, but you may call me Khemu - I am the elder of this tribe, and our lorekeeper.{^n}{^n}You look like a busy adventurer, though, so I will be brief: beneath this humble encampment lies a ruined shrine, dedicated to Khonsu, the god of the moon. I have reason to believe that, buried in its depths, lies an amulet called the Shadowstone of Anubis. If you happen to explore this shrine during your travels and find the Shadowstone, I would be forever grateful if you brought it to me. We will compensate you generously.
x4tagSQ301_Khemu_A7=The shrine of Khonsu, adventurer ... It will be dangerous, but, let me assure you, I will make it worth your while.
x4tagSQ301_Khemu_B1=Look at that, the intrepid adventurer has returned. And is that ...{^n}{^n}By the stinging desert winds, it's the Shadowstone - you found it. I cannot even begin to imagine what dangers you had to face to get it. But let that be a story for another time - here is your promised reward. Do come back in the future, won't you? I might have more tasks for you.
x4tagSQ301_Khemu_B7=Safe travels, adventurer. Thank you again.
x4tagSQ302_User_A1=Well, I'll be damned, a healthy, ruddy face. What a pleasant change. Say, you're not a soldier looking to make some coin or do some good, are you? If you are, I have just the thing: these lovely fellows here did not die from heatstroke. Someone poisoned them, and there are soldiers in the barracks who show similar symptoms.{^n}{^n}I was able to secure a small sample of the poison, and it seems to stem from a specific type of cave scorpion, but I'll need more samples. Could you help a Thebean physician in need? Oh, and if you also find the ones who are responsible while you are at it, let me know. I believe they need a taste of their own medicine.
x4tagSQ302_User_B1=The altruistic hero returns. I take it you collected some samples? Show me.{^n}{^n}Yes ... yes, those will do. I can make an antidote out of this. Thank you. As it happens, I have not been idle in the meantime: I believe I know who is behind this: the Children of Serket. Religious fanatics who will do anything to advance medicine. I wonder how they justify poisoning hundreds of soldiers, but I'm certain they found a way. Be that as it may, I will make further inquiries once I have prepared the antidote. Thank you again for helping - you saved many lives today.
x4tagSQ302_User_B7=Hm? Is there anything else? We've already started to replicate the antidote, and should be able to hand out the first doses this evening. Thanks to you, Thebes will sleep soundly tonight.
x4tagSQ303_Re’yesh_A1=Oh, thank Ra ... You came from Thebes, didn't you? Did the Pharaoh send you? Well, it doesn't matter, you must help me: I'm Re'Yesh, and I lead the reconstruction works of this temple. Just this morning, we were doing our work as we should, but then these people charged in and started butchering everyone. Tomb raiders, probably, hoping for loot. {^n}{^n}It's madness. Utter madness. Please, if you have any kindness left in your heart, you must go into the temple and take care of these faithless heathens. For Thebes, for the Pharaoh, for the Gods.
x4tagSQ303_Re’yesh_A7=Yes? What about the tomb raiders?
x4tagSQ303_Re’yesh_B1=You killed the raiders! Oh, I don't even know how to thank you. Are there ... are there any survivors? No, don't say anything: your eyes speak volumes. Oh, curse those derelicts. Still, you did a great service to the kingdom - here, this is the least I can do. Now forgive me, I must assess the damage.
x4tagSQ401_Jin_Chan_X1=You there! Yes, you, over there in that blood-splattered armor! This may be your only chance to converse with a true icon, so I suggest you use it!
x4tagSQ401_Jin_Chan_A1=Heavens, that took you a while, didn't it? Ah, well. The name's Jin Chan, or, as some of my many admirers rather crudely call me, the 'Money Frog'. Yes, yes, you heard correctly, that Jin Chan. You are honored and privileged to have me here. Now, moving on to the nature of my request: I must return to the Heavenly Palace. No, don't even ask what brought me here, it would be too difficult for a, no offense, simple warrior type such as yourself to understand. What matters is that, in all that lava and fire, I can't return by myself without ending up as fried frog's legs.{^n}{^n}The Jade Emperor himself already sent for help, a little phoenix called Fenghuang, but the dear lady is taking her time getting here as usual. Could you do me a favor and see if anything happened? What's that? You will, without compensation? Why, how very generous. I shall wait here patiently.
x4tagSQ401_Jin_Chan_A7=Are you one of those adventurers who need everything written down for them? Find Fenghuang so she can get me out of here. Now, shoo, get on with it.
x4tagSQ401_Jin_Chan_B1=You found her? Why, good work. I have been thinking, and realized it would be improper to let you go completely empty handed, especially since you have that look of a hero about to do something terribly important. Sadly, I am out of autographs, so this will have to do. {^n}Now go, be on your merry way. And let's hope that glorified parrot doesn't take too long to reassemble.{^n}Phoenixes ...
x4tagSQ401_Fenghuang_A1=Oh, curse it, I was just getting comfortable. Couldn't you have let me stay in there for a little longer? Now I have to listen to that insufferable loudmouth yabber on for the entire flight back to the Heavenly Palace. Ah, well, what can you do. Thank you ... I guess. I will need a while to get used to these wings again, though, so tell the frog he has to wait.
x4tagSQ401_Fenghuang_A7=What? I won't resurrect any faster if you stand there gawking. Go tell the frog I'm coming. When I'm good and ready.
x4tagSQ402_Bao_A1=Demon ruined Bao dinner. Bao Mad. You help Bao and Bao help you.
x4tagSQ402_Bao_A2=Take key. Bash demon on flamy hill. Save dinner.
x4tagSQ402_Bao_A7=Shoo go. You scare Bao dinner away.
x4tagSQ402_Bao_B1=Demon dead? Dinner dead? Bao sad. Shiny make Bao happy, you give shiny thing?
