// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
//encoding = RAW

xtagXVI=XVI
xtagXVII=XVII
xtagXVIII=XVIII
xtagXIX=XIX
xtagXX=XX
xtagXXI=XXI
xtagxQuestMonster01=Kallixenia ~ Liche Queen
xtagxQuestMonster02=Ascacophus ~ Gate Keeper
xtagxQuestMonster03=Gargantuan Karkinos
xtagxQuestMonster04=Surryln the Belligerent ~ Anteok Hero
xtagxQuestMonster05=Nightblossom
xtagxQuestMonster06=Queen Ycht'ssk'l ~ Formicid Hero
xtagxQuestMonster07=Proseia ~ Daemon Captain
xtagxQuestMonster08=Shade Feaster ~ Stygian Hydradon Hero
xtagxQuestMonster09=Krog the Toothless ~ Urn Guardian
xtagxQuestMonster10=Brontes ~ Cyclops
xtagxQuestMonster11=Steropes ~ Cyclops
xtagxQuestMonster12=Envoy Kor-Lhrut ~ Machae Hero
xtagxQuestMonster13=Bonescourge ~ Soul-feeder
xtagxQuestMonster14=Blood Queen Leucothea ~ Melinoe Hero
xtagxQuestMonster15=Dysnomion ~ Machae High General
xtagxQuestMonster16=Trophonios ~ Machae High General
xtagxQuestMonster17=Makaria ~ Machae High General
xtagxQuestMonster18=Warden of Souls
xtagxQuestMonster19=King Dorus ~ Corrupted Soul
xtagxQuestMonster20=King Aegimius ~ Corrupted Soul
xtagxQuestMonster21=Queen Alkiste ~ Corrupted Soul
xtagxQuestMonster22=Tsakonian Noble ~ Spectral Minion
xtagxQuestMonster23=Tsakonian Courtier ~ Spectral Minion
xtagxQuestMonster24=Troglodyte ~ Jailor
xtagxQuestMonster25=Machae ~ Ballista Operator
xtagxQuestObject01=Altar of Kallixenia
xtagxQuestObject02=Mysterious Urn
xtagxQuestObject03=Daemon Caravan
xtagxQuestObject04=Shard of Erebus
xtagxQuestObject05=Ancient Lock
xtagxQuestObject06=Frost Altar
xtagxQuestObject07=Flame Altar
xtagxQuestObject08=Soul Altar
xtagxQuestObject09=Venom Altar
xtagxQuestObject10=Aestivus Tree
xtagxQuestObject11=Ancient Lock ~ Moon Sign
xtagxQuestObject12=Ancient Lock ~ Sun Sign
xtagxQuestObject13=Lever
xtagxQuestObject14=Ancient Lever
xtagxQuestObject15=Beacon
xtagMedeaPortalToEpirus=Do you wish to enter the portal to Epirus?
xtagMedeaPortalObject=Portal to Epirus
xtagGate01=Portcullis
xtagGate02=Wooden Gate
xtagGate03=Astral Door
xtagGate04=Cell Door
xtagGate05=Eurydice's Portal
xtagGate06=Vault Door
xtagGate07=Wall of Water
xtagGate08=Judgment Gate
xtagGate09=Ancient Wooden Door
xtagGate10=Elysium Gate
xtagGate11=Tartarus Gate
xtagGate12=Ornate Bronze Door
xtagGate13=Palace Gate
xtagGate14=Massive Gate
xtagGate15=Low Gate
xtagGate16=Massive Wooden Gate
xtagGate17=Crystalline Barrier
xtagxQuestItem01=Eye of the Gray Ones
xtagxQuestItem02=Tome of the Liche Queen Kallixenia
xtagxQuestItem03=Waking Stone
xtagxQuestItem04=Curative Elixir
xtagxQuestItem05=Nightblossom Petal
xtagxQuestItem06=Cybe Mushroom
xtagxQuestItem07=Aestivus Root
xtagxQuestItem08=Sigil of the First Apoktisis
xtagxQuestItem09=Charon's Oar
xtagxQuestItem10=Ashen Powder
xtagxQuestItem11=Daemon Scroll
xtagxQuestItem12=Ancient Moon Key
xtagxQuestItem13=Ancient Sun Key
xtagxQuestItem14=Medicinal Supplies
xtagxQuestItem15=Frost Stone
xtagxQuestItem16=Flame Stone
xtagxQuestItem17=Soul Stone
xtagxQuestItem18=Venom Stone
xtagxQuestItem19=Mirror of Psyche
xtagxQuestItem20=Key of the Warden of Souls
xtagxQuestItemDesc01=The three Gray Sisters shared one eye. Though dull and misshapen, strange colors flicker within the pupil.
xtagxQuestItemDesc02=The ancient spellbook is strangely heavy.
xtagxQuestItemDesc03=A small stone covered in ancient glyphs.
xtagxQuestItemDesc04=The potion that will cure Maera's sick child.
xtagxQuestItemDesc05=The petals are powdery, and tough as leather.
xtagxQuestItemDesc06=The soft blue light under its cap makes the mushroom look almost as if it were breathing.
xtagxQuestItemDesc07=The root is damp and gives off a strange, sweet odor.
xtagxQuestItemDesc08=Clearly ancient, the strange symbols used only by Formicid Queens cover its surface.
xtagxQuestItemDesc09=The oar he used to steer his boat. There is clearly some great power in its ancient wood.
xtagxQuestItemDesc10=This gray powder resembles that of cremated remains. It is surprisingly heavy and seems charged, as if imbued with lightning.
xtagxQuestItemDesc11=The scroll contains strange daemon glyphs, presumably a message destined for the army's front lines.
xtagxQuestItemDesc12=An ancient key, made of gold, engraved with the symbol for the moon.
xtagxQuestItemDesc13=An ancient key, made of gold, engraved with the symbol for the sun.
xtagxQuestItemDesc14=This sack contains various herbs, balms, poultices, and other medicines.
xtagxQuestItemDesc15=A strange, runed stone. It is cold to the touch.
xtagxQuestItemDesc16=A strange, runed stone. It is quite hot to the touch.
xtagxQuestItemDesc17=A strange, runed stone. Dark, mystical power whirls within it.
xtagxQuestItemDesc18=A strange, runed stone. Noxious vapors waft from its surface.
xtagxQuestItemDesc19=An ornate, gilt mirror. Strangely, it sometimes works as a mirror, and at other times seems a window to other places.
xtagxQuestItemDesc20=The master key to all of Hades' dungeon cell doors.
xtagxQ01_Title=A Mysterious Message
xtagxQ02_Title=Medea’s Price
xtagxQ03_Title=The Road to Hades
xtagxQ04_Title=Judgment of the Living
xtagxQ05_Title=The Battle for Elysium
xtagxQ06_Title=The Immortal Throne
xtagxQ01_Obj_A=Find the Sorceress of the Ixian Wood
xtagxQ01_Obj_B=Defeat the Sorceress’ Sentinels
xtagxQ02_Obj_A=Defeat Gray Ones and take their Eye
xtagxQ02_Obj_B=Bring the Eye to Medea
xtagxQ02_Obj_C=Speak with Medea
xtagxQ03_Obj_A=Seek Tiresias in Hades
xtagxQ03_Obj_B=Travel through Medea’s Portal
xtagxQ03_Obj_C=Cross the River Styx
xtagxQ03_Obj_D=Defeat Charon
xtagxQ04_Obj_A=Find a Way to Elysium
xtagxQ04_Obj_B=Seek the Judges in the Tower of Judgment
xtagxQ04_Obj_C=Defeat Cerberus
xtagxQ04_Obj_D=Speak to the Judges
xtagxQ05_Obj_A=Travel through the Judgment Gate
xtagxQ05_Obj_B=Find and speak with Agamemnon
xtagxQ05_Obj_C=Meet Odysseus before Hades’ Palace
xtagxQ06_Obj_A=Defeat Lord Hades
xtagxQ06_Obj_B=Find and free Persephone
xtagxQ06_Obj_C=Enter the Palace of Hades
xtagxQ06_Obj_D=Speak with Persephone
xtagxQ01_Desc_A=An apparition of the famed seer Tiresias appeared before the Temple of Apollo, with dire and ominous warnings. He charged you to find a way to “where all men are destined,” and to do so, you must find the “Sorceress of the Ixian Wood…” whoever that may be.
xtagxQ01_Desc_B=An apparition of the famed seer Tiresias appeared before the Temple of Apollo, with dire and ominous warnings. He charged you to find a way to “where all men are destined,” and to do so, you must find the “Sorceress of the Ixian Wood,” who is none other than the legendary Medea of Colchis.
xtagxQ01_Desc_C=An apparition of the famed seer Tiresias appeared before the Temple of Apollo. He called out as you passed, summoning you to the “Sorceress of the Ixian Wood...” whoever that may be, and charging you to find him, though he is dead.
xtagxQ01_Desc_Complete=An apparition of the famed seer Tiresias appeared before the Temple of Apollo, with dire and ominous warnings. He charged you to find a way to “where all men are destined,” and to do so, you must find the “Sorceress of the Ixian Wood,” who is none other than the legendary Medea of Colchis. She is no one’s ally, and her help comes with a price:  the one Eye of the Gray Sisters.
xtagxQ02_Desc_A=Medea has agreed to help you follow Tiresias’ bidding, by finding a way into the Underworld, but she has also named her price. The Eye of the Gray Ones, she claims, has seen the way to Hades. It would be no surprise if this eye served Medea’s own purposes, as well.
xtagxQ02_Desc_Complete=Medea has agreed to help you follow Tiresias’ bidding, by finding a way into the Underworld, but the help came with a price – the Eye of the Gray Ones, which have seen the way to Hades. It would be no surprise if this eye served Medea’s own purposes, as well. The price is paid and Medea has opened a portal. Through the portal, the path to Hades. Somewhere within those depths, the shade of blind, prophetic Tiresias.
xtagxQ03_Desc_A=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There is nothing to do but hope that Tiresias can be found, and that the reason he summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands.
xtagxQ03_Desc_B=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There is nothing to do but hope that Tiresias can be found, and that the reason he summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands. The entrance must lie somewhere in this region of Epirus. The people here have troubles of their own – strange new monsters have sacked their city, called Paseron.
xtagxQ03_Desc_C=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There is nothing to do but hope that Tiresias can be found, and that the reason he summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands. It is across the River Styx that the dead come to rest and that the god Hades reigns over all.
xtagxQ03_Desc_D=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There is nothing to do but hope that Tiresias can be found, and that the reason he summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands. It is across the River Styx that the dead come to rest and that the god Hades reigns over all… but strangely, Charon is not at his boat. Who will ferry the dead to the other side?
xtagxQ03_Desc_E=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There is nothing to do but hope that Tiresias can be found, and that the reason he summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands. Strange troubles already litter the path. Charon has left his boat, and a newly built bridge that crosses the river. Why would shades need a bridge to cross?
xtagxQ03_Desc_Complete=The path to the Sunless Lands! Few mortals have dared to follow this dread route. There remains nothing to do but hope that the reason Tiresias summoned you is not a challenge beyond the grasp of living hands. Many strange troubles already litter the path. Charon had left his boat to guard a newly built bridge that crosses the River Styx. The apparition of Tiresias appeared again, now on the far side, with a new goal: the hallowed Elysian Fields.
xtagxQ04_Desc_A=Upon the shore of the Hades’ Realm, Tiresias appeared again, bidding you travel to the Elysian Fields. His enigmatic warnings suggested something terrible taking place in that land that has never known sorrow. But how does a living mortal reach Elysium?
xtagxQ04_Desc_B=Upon the shore of the Hades’ Realm, Tiresias appeared again, bidding you travel to the Elysian Fields. His enigmatic warnings suggested something terrible taking place in that land that has never known sorrow. It appears that the only way to Elysium is by way of the Three Judges, who pass judgment on all the dead. There are troubling rumors, however, that the Judges now refuse all petitions. Have they, like Charon, turned?
xtagxQ04_Desc_C=Upon the shore of the Hades’ Realm, Tiresias appeared again, bidding you travel to the Elysian Fields. His enigmatic warnings suggested something terrible taking place in that land that has never known sorrow. It appears that the only way to Elysium is by way of the Three Judges, who pass judgment on all the dead. Before their chamber the deadly Cerberus kept watch. But was he the guard, or the jailor?
xtagxQ04_Desc_Complete=Upon the shore of the Hades’ Realm, Tiresias appeared again, bidding you travel to the Elysian Fields. The only way to Elysium is by way of the three Judges, who pass judgment on all the dead, and they were locked and guarded by the three-headed Cerberus. Once freed, Judge Minos related Hades' refusal to follow the other gods. Instead, the god set his sights on conquering the Realms of the Living. When the Three Judges refused to be his generals, he locked them in their hall and found others for the task. Repeating Tiresias’ urgent plea, the Judges opened the gate to Elysium and bade you help the heroes there.
xtagxQ05_Desc_A=The Three Judges spoke of Hades' plans to conquer the Realms of the Living by force. The heroes of Elysium even now fight upon their hallowed fields to block the dark god’s progress. Minos has opened the gate to Elysium, and instructed you to seek their commander, King Agamemnon.
xtagxQ05_Desc_B=The Three Judges spoke of Hades' plans to conquer the Realms of the Living by force. The heroes of Elysium even now fight upon their hallowed fields to block the dark god’s progress. Tiresias and Minos bade you to help the heroes, but it seems it is Odysseus who will help you – to enter Hades' Palace, where the souls of heroes cannot tread.
xtagxQ05_Desc_Complete=The Three Judges spoke of Hades’ plans to conquer the Realms of the Living by force. The heroes of Elysium even now fight upon their hallowed fields to block the dark god’s progress. Tiresias bade you to help the heroes, but it was Odysseus who has helped you – to enter Hades' Palace, where the souls of heroes cannot tread.
xtagxQ06_Desc_A=On the edge of the battle-scarred lands, which once were gentle pastures, lies the palace of the god Hades. Thanks to Odysseus, a new entrance smolders at the base of the great wall. But Hades has magically forbidden the hero shades from entering. If the ambitious god is to be stopped, mortal hands must do the deed. Odysseus and his men have heard the song of the goddess Persephone from beyond the palace wall. If found, she would surely help in the overthrow of her tyrannical husband.
xtagxQ06_Desc_B=On the edge of the battle-scarred lands, which once were gentle pastures, lies the palace of the god Hades. Thanks to Odysseus, a new entrance smolders at the base of the great wall. But Hades has magically forbidden the hero shades from entering. If the ambitious god is to be stopped, mortal hands must do the deed. The goddess Persephone languished in chains just inside the palace walls. Such was her punishment for not helping her husband, Hades, in his schemes of conquest. Once freed, she gratefully opened the way to the inner palace, the path to the dread Lord of the Dead.
xtagxQ06_Desc_Complete=On the edge of the battle-scarred lands, which once were gentle pastures, lies the palace of the god Hades. With the help of Tiresias, Odysseus, and the goddess Persephone, the difficult path was cleared to reach the Immortal Throne, where tyrannical Hades plotted to conquer the living lands. He had thought, when the other gods departed from this realm, to claim it for himself – to be Zeus, Poseidon and Hades all in one. But the Olympian gods were wiser than he knew. For they saw that mortals would become great, and that they possessed the might to rule their realm, and protect it, even against the mightiest of foes.
xtagxSQLocation01=Rhodes
xtagxSQLocation02=Ixian Woods
xtagxSQLocation03=Epirus
xtagxSQLocation04=Styx
xtagxSQLocation05=Plains of Judgment
xtagxSQLocation06=Elysium
xtagxSQLocation07=Palace of Hades
xtagxSQ01_Title=A Crab Story
xtagxSQ02_Title=An Impossible Task
xtagxSQ03_Title=The Torch-Lighter’s Gauntlet
xtagxSQ03_Title_Alt=Lighting the Beacon
xtagxSQ04_Title=Outpost in the Woods
xtagxSQ05_Title=Lampido’s Potion
xtagxSQ06_Title=The Wealth of Ancient Kings
xtagxSQ07_Title=The Stolen Sigil
xtagxSQ08_Title=The Treasure Hunters
xtagxSQ09_Title=Among the Ruins
xtagxSQ10_Title=A Dangerous Mission
xtagxSQ11_Title=The Enemy’s Captain
xtagxSQ12_Title=One Who Would Lead
xtagxSQ13_Title=The Stygian Lurker
xtagxSQ14_Title=The Dust of a Titan
xtagxSQ15_Title=Eurydice and Orpheus
xtagxSQ16_Title=An Invitation
xtagxSQ17_Title=An Inside Source
xtagxSQ18_Title=The Necromanteion
xtagxSQ19_Title=Hades’ Treasury
xtagxSQ20_Title=Admetus Among the Dead
xtagxSQ21_Title=Flight of the Messenger
xtagxSQ22_Title=The Achaean Pass
xtagxSQ23_Title=To the Eronian Heights
xtagxSQ24_Title=A Noisy Diversion
xtagxSQ25_Title=The Siege Striders
xtagxSQ26_Title=The Shards of Erebus
xtagxSQ27_Title=Hades’ Generals
xtagxSQ01_Desc_A=A great crab has come up on the beach in the small village of Damatria. It seems the fishermen can’t get near their boats. The village must be facing starvation. Worse yet, the only other way to reach the village is by the dangerous Cave of Orthea. Go through the Orthean caves to Damatria.
xtagxSQ01_Desc_B=A great crab has come up on the beach in the small village of Damatria. The fishermen sit idly above the beach, which is now overrun by karkinosi. This village must be facing starvation.  Kill the gargantuan karkinos by the fishing boats.
xtagxSQ01_Desc_C=A great crab had come up on the beach in the small village of Damatria, and the fishermen were forced to sit idly above the beach, which had become overrun by karkinosi. With the crab gone, the villagers need no longer worry where they will find their next meal. Talk to Proteas.
xtagxSQ01_Desc_D=A great crab had come up on the beach in the small village of Damatria, and the fishermen were forced to sit idly above the beach, which had become overrun by karkinosi. With the crab gone, the villagers need no longer worry where they will find their next meal.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_A=Maera’s child has fallen seriously ill. When she begged the sorceress Medea for a cure, she was told she must obtain some ancient tome first. Although Maera despairs of ever finding such a thing, she mentioned that one of Medea’s apprentices, named Procne, seemed to know more. Speak with Medea’s apprentice, Procne.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_B=Maera’s child has fallen seriously ill. When she begged the sorceress Medea for a cure, she was told she must obtain the Tome of the Lich Queen Kallixenia – a fatal task for a common person. Medea’s acolyte, Procne, was sympathetic to the poor mother. She has offered the Waking Stone needed to summon the Lich Queen. The summoning altar is in the Tsakonian Ruins, beyond the Soronian Swamp. Summon the Lich Queen and obtain the Tome.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_C=Maera’s child has fallen seriously ill. When she begged the sorceress Medea for a cure, she was told she must obtain the Tome of the Lich Queen Kallixenia – a fatal task for a common person. Medea’s acolyte, Procne, was sympathetic to the poor mother, and was a great help in summoning Kallixenia. The ancient sorceress did not give up her book without a fight. Bring the Tome to Procne.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_D=Maera’s child has fallen seriously ill. When she begged the sorceress Medea for a cure, she was told she must obtain the Tome of the Lich Queen Kallixenia – a fatal task for a common person. Medea’s acolyte, Procne, was sympathetic to the poor mother, and was a great help in summoning Kallixenia and obtaining the potion once the Tome was secured. Bring the cure to Maera in Rhodes.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_E=Maera’s child has fallen seriously ill. When she begged the sorceress Medea for a cure, she was told she must obtain the Tome of the Lich Queen Kallixenia – a fatal task for a common person. Medea’s acolyte, Procne, was sympathetic to the poor mother, and was a great help in summoning Kallixenia and obtaining the potion once the Tome was secured. It should not be long before Maera will see her child in good health, happily running and playing.
xtagxSQ02_Desc_F=Procne, an acolyte in Medea’s Grove spoke of a woman in Rhodes whom Medea treated cruelly. Medea refused to cure her child unless she performed an impossible task. Speak with Procne again, or look for the woman in Rhodes.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_ASSIGN=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. What could be so dangerous about this bluff? Talk to the foreman, Abderus, to accept the mission.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_A=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. What could be so dangerous about this bluff? Lead the torch lighter safely to the top of the Camirus Bluff.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_B=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. It appears the bluff is haunted by more than a few undead! Return to Abderus to get a new torch lighter.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_C=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. It appears the bluff is haunted by more than a few undead! Defend the torch lighter while he lights the beacon.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_D=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. Although the bluff is haunted by more than a few undead, the beacon has finally been lit. Talk to Abderus.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_E=A foreman needed an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, in order to light the beacon there, telling ships that it was safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. Although the bluff was haunted by more than a few undead, the beacon was finally lit. Ships – and with them, trade, can now return to Rhodes.
xtagxSQ03_Desc_F=A foreman wants an escort to take one of his men to the top of a nearby bluff, where he will light the beacon there, telling ships it is now safe to enter harbor in Rhodes. It appears the bluff is haunted by more than a few undead! The torch-lighter is making progress. Continue to defend the torch lighter while he lights the beacon.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_A=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. This Ixian base appears to be heavily under attack. Help defend the outpost.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_B=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. This Ixian base suffered a heavy attack and is much beleaguered, but are safe for now. Speak with the sergeant, Teisias.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_C=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. This Ixian base suffered a heavy attack and is much beleaguered. Teisias says that these attacks are led by a fearsome anteok, often seen near the waterfall not far from the outpost. Find and slay the anteok.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_D=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. This Ixian base suffered a heavy attack and is much beleaguered, but the great anteok behind these attacks is slain. The brave men stationed here may stand a chance in this wilderness. Speak with Teisias.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_E=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. This Ixian base suffered a heavy attack and is much beleaguered, but the great anteok behind these attacks is dead. The brave men stationed here may stand a chance in this wilderness.
xtagxSQ04_Desc_F=A scout came running out of the woods, looking for help defending his military outpost. The Ixian base appears to be under attack. He said that to reach the outpost, keep to the left along the path he came from. Find the outpost.
xtagxSQ05_Desc_A=The acolyte Lampido says she has invented a new type of potion that would bestow great powers on whoever drank it. She has offered to share some of the potion in exchange for the ingredients, all found in the swamps of Soronis. The ingredients are: cybe mushroom, aestivus root, and petal of night-blossom. Collect the three ingredients.
xtagxSQ05_Desc_B=The acolyte Lampido says she has invented a new type of potion that would bestow great powers on whoever drank it. She has offered to share some of the potion in exchange for the ingredients, all found in the swamps of Soronis. The ingredients are: cybe mushroom, aestivus root, and petal of night-blossom. Bring the ingredients to Lampido.
xtagxSQ05_Desc_C=The acolyte Lampido says she has invented a new type of potion that would bestow great powers on whoever drank it. She has offered to share some of the potion in exchange for the ingredients, all found in the swamps of Soronis. Hopefully Lampido’s potion will be worth the trouble of gathering the items. Speak with Lampido again to receive your share.
xtagxSQ05_Desc_D=The acolyte Lampido invented a new type of potion that would bestow great powers on whoever drank it. She offered to share some of the potion in exchange for the ingredients, all found in the swamps of Soronis. Lampido was generous with her potion, which was well worth the trouble of gathering the items.
xtagxSQ06_Desc_A=Legend has it that an ancient race of kings built a great city, named Propontis, within the nearby Soronian Swamps. The last of these Tsakonian kings is supposed to have hidden his most prized possessions in his tomb, and it is said the treasure has never been uncovered. Search for the hidden treasure in the Tsakonian Ruins.
xtagxSQ06_Desc_B=Legend has it that an ancient race of kings built a great city, named Propontis, within the nearby Soronian Swamps. The last of these Tsakonian kings is supposed to have hidden his most prized possessions in his tomb, and it is said the treasure has never been uncovered. The treasure was well hidden – but worth the search.
xtagxSQ06_Desc_C=There was a strange key in one of the dungeons beneath the Tsakonian Ruins. Could it unlock some ancient door elsewhere in the ruins? Perhaps one of Medea’s acolytes knows the history of these ruins. Discover the purpose of the key.
xtagxSQ06_Desc_D=There was a strange key in one of the dungeons beneath the Tsakonian Ruins. It seems to be part of an elaborate puzzle in the Great Tomb of Dorus. Perhaps one of Medea’s acolytes knows the history of these ruins. Solve the puzzle in Dorus’ Tomb.
xtagxSQ06_Desc_E=There was a strange key in one of the dungeons beneath the Tsakonian Ruins, which turned out to be part of an elaborate puzzle in the Great Tomb of Dorus. It would seem the ancient king placed the obstacles to protect his impressive treasure. It was a well-made gauntlet, which stood the test of time.
xtagxSQ07_Desc_A=Medea’s headmistress, Semele, is greatly distressed. It appears she was ambushed by formicids, who stole an item called the ‘Sigil of the First Apoktisis’ from her. It sounds as if this is a talisman of some power and importance. There must be a formicid colony nearby. Retrieve the Sigil.
xtagxSQ07_Desc_B=Medea’s headmistress, Semele, is greatly distressed. It appears she was ambushed by formicids, who stole an item called the ‘Sigil of the First Apoktisis’ from her. Luckily, the formicid queen never had a chance to master this talisman’s significant powers. Return the Sigil to Semele.
xtagxSQ07_Desc_C=Medea’s headmistress, Semele, is greatly distressed. It appears she was ambushed by formicids, who stole an item called the ‘Sigil of the First Apoktisis’ from her. Luckily, the formicid queen never had a chance to master this talisman’s significant powers.
xtagxSQ07_Desc_D=Among the possessions of the formicid colony in the Ampelian Caves was a mysterious Sigil. Perhaps one of Medea’s acolytes can identify the talisman. Ask about the Sigil in Medea’s Grove.
xtagxSQ07_Desc_E=Medea’s headmistress, Semele, was ambushed by formicids, who stole an item called the ‘Sigil of the First Apoktisis’ from her. Luckily, the formicid queen never had a chance to master this talisman’s significant powers.
xtagxSQ08_Desc_A=A young man stood, injured and terrified, among the Tsakonian Ruins. It appears he and his sister had set out to explore the ruins, with little idea of the danger involved. He says that monsters seized his sister, and that he got away. Find Herodion’s sister within the ruins.
xtagxSQ08_Desc_B=A young man stood, injured and terrified, among the Tsakonian Ruins. He and his sister had set out to explore the ruins, with little idea of the danger involved. Monsters seized his sister, Nysa, while he got away. Luckily, she had not yet been harmed. She and her brother are safe now – and hopefully a little wiser for their adventures.
xtagxSQ08_Desc_C=A young man stood, injured and terrified, among the Tsakonian Ruins. It appears he and his sister had set out to explore the ruins, with little idea of the danger involved. He says that monsters seized his sister, and that he got away. Speak with Herodion’s sister.
xtagxSQ08_Desc_D=A young woman was captured by some of the monsters that dwell in the Tsakonian Ruins. Apparently she had come into the swamps with her brother, Herodion, little aware of the danger involved. She is worried for the welfare of her brother. He must be lost elsewhere in the ruins. Find Nysa’s brother, Herodion.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_A=When a strange non-human army sacked the city of Paseron, those who could escape did. But many were left behind. The day after, Theogenes, of the city guard, has gone with some men to rescue any living humans hiding or trapped among the wreckage of the dreadful scene. He could use every brave soul he can find in the effort. Look for Theogenes in Paseron.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_B=When a strange non-human army sacked the city of Paseron, those who could escape did. But many were left behind. The day after, Theogenes, of the city guard, has gone with some men to rescue any living humans hiding or trapped among the wreckage of the dreadful scene. Unfortunately, the city is filled with the strange monsters – too many for Theogenes and his men. Search for stragglers in Paseron, and help them escape.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_C=When a strange non-human army sacked the city of Paseron, those who could escape did. But many were left. The day after, Theogenes, of the city guard, had gone with some men to rescue any living humans hiding or trapped among the wreckage of the dreadful scene. Theogenes should be grateful to be able to lead his fellow citizens to the safety of the camp. Return to Theogenes.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_D=When a strange non-human army sacked the city of Paseron, those who could escape did. But many were left. The day after, Theogenes, of the city guard, had gone with some men to rescue any living humans hiding or trapped among the wreckage of the dreadful scene. Theogenes was grateful to be able to lead his fellow citizens to the safety of the camp.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_E=People are still trying to flee from Paseron, after it was sacked and razed only the night before. Many are trapped by monsters or among rubble, and cannot escape. Help stragglers in Paseron to escape.
xtagxSQ09_Desc_F=People are still trying to flee from Paseron, after it was sacked and razed only the night before. Many were trapped by monsters or among rubble, and could not escape on their own. No doubt the other refugees will be glad to hear of their successful evacuation. Inform the Paseron refugees.
xtagxSQ10_Desc_A=This refugee camp is filled with the hungry and the injured. They must have fled with only the clothes on their backs. Pisistratus says he sent Admetus back into Paseron for a stash of food and medical supplies, but most of a day has gone by, and there has been no sign of him. Look for Admetus and the stash of supplies in Paseron.
xtagxSQ10_Desc_B=This refugee camp is filled with the hungry and the injured. They must have fled with only the clothes on their backs. Pisistratus says he sent Admetus back into Paseron for a stash of food and medical supplies, but most of a day has gone by, and there has been no sign of him. Alas! Admetus was ambushed as soon as he had the supplies in his hands. His dying wishes are that they be taken to the refugees, who need them. Take the supplies to Pisistratus.
xtagxSQ10_Desc_C=This refugee camp is filled with the hungry and the injured. They must have fled with only the clothes on their backs. Pisistratus says he sent Admetus back into Paseron for a stash of food and medical supplies, but most of a day has gone by, and there has been no sign of him. Alas! Admetus was ambushed as soon as he had the supplies in his hands. His dying wishes were that they be taken to the refugees, who need them. This noble last rite was not in vain.
xtagxSQ11_Desc_A=Pythes says that the strange army which apparently has sacked Paseron is led by a fierce captain, named Proseia. He seems to feel that their ranks would be scattered and weak, were their leader to fall. Find and defeat Proseia.
xtagxSQ11_Desc_B=Pythes said that the strange army which apparently has sacked Paseron was led by a fierce captain, named Proseia. If Pythes is right, their ranks will be scattered and weak, now that their leader has fallen. Return to Pythes.
xtagxSQ11_Desc_C=Pythes said that the strange army which apparently has sacked Paseron was led by a fierce captain, named Proseia. If Pythes is right, their ranks will be scattered and weak, now that their leader has fallen. Let us hope there is no greater army on the march, following on the heels of this one.
xtagxSQ12_Desc_A=The boatman Charon has vanished and shades cannot cross the Styx into the Sunless Lands. They are scared and huddle close to the useless boat. It appears one shade stood up and demanded passage, but he was taken away by the daemons here. Hipparchus, he was called. Find and free Hipparchus.
xtagxSQ12_Desc_B=The boatman Charon has vanished and shades cannot cross the Styx into the Sunless Lands. They are scared and huddle close to the useless boat. One shade, called Hipparchus stood up and demanded passage, but he was taken away by the daemons here. Now freed, he has pledged to help the other shades. He says that to move the boat, he must have Charon’s Oar. Find Charon’s Oar.
xtagxSQ12_Desc_C=The boatman Charon has vanished and shades cannot cross the Styx into the Sunless Lands. They are scared and huddle close to the useless boat. One shade, called Hipparchus stood up and demanded passage, but he was taken away by the daemons here. Now freed, he has pledged to help the other shades. He says that to move the boat, he must have Charon’s Oar. Hipparchus will be waiting by Charon's Dock. Bring Charon’s Oar to Hipparchus.
xtagxSQ12_Desc_D=The boatman Charon has vanished and shades cannot cross the Styx into the Sunless Lands. They are scared and huddle close to the useless boat. One shade, called Hipparchus stood up and demanded passage, but he was taken away by the daemons here. Now freed, with Charon’s Oar in hand, he has pledged to ply the ferry for all shades who come to his dock. With Charon gone, will he himself ever touch the farther shore?
xtagxSQ12_Desc_E=Although he left his boat, Charon kept his oar close at hand. Some deep magical power within the wood is plainly apparent to the touch. What power does it possess? Most likely, the oar is magically tied to Charon’s boat. Investigate the purpose of Charon’s Oar.
xtagxSQ13_Desc_A=A hunter near Charon’s boat says he has seen a stygian hydradon that swims the Styx and sometimes rises to swallow helpless shades whole. Apparently the beast normally dwells in the Stygian Marsh, beyond the river. Find and kill this Shade Feaster.
xtagxSQ13_Desc_B=A hunter near Charon’s boat had seen a stygian hydradon that would swim the Styx, sometimes rise to swallow helpless shades whole. The beast normally dwelt in the Stygian Marsh. The Shade Feaster will trouble shades on either side no more.
xtagxSQ14_Desc_A=Long ago, Zeus smote a titan with his lightning bolt, reducing him to ash. From these ashes Prometheus fashioned the first humans. It is said that a little of the ash was left over, and that the god Hades appointed a trusty guardian to protect it, somewhere in the Plains of Judgment. The shade-priestess Leda says she could prepare these ashes into a vital and potent elixir. Find the dust of the titan.
xtagxSQ14_Desc_B=Long ago, Zeus smote a titan with his lightning bolt, reducing him to ash. From these ashes Prometheus fashioned the first humans. It is said that a little of the ash was left over, and indeed, Hades ensured that the dust was well hidden and well guarded within the Plains of Judgment. The shade-priestess Leda says she could prepare these ashes into a vital and potent elixir. Bring the dust to Leda.
xtagxSQ14_Desc_C=A fierce daemon guarded a mysterious urn. All the urn contained, however, was a strange ashen powder. Discover the nature of this powder.
xtagxSQ14_Desc_D=Long ago, Zeus smote a titan with his lightning bold, reducing him to ash. From these ashes Prometheus fashioned the first humans. It is said that a little of the ash was left over, and indeed, Hades ensured that the dust was well hidden and well guarded within the Plains of Judgment. The shade-priestess Leda has generously prepared these ashes into a vital and potent elixir.
xtagxSQ15_Desc_A=Eurydice has been separated from her famed lover, the great musician Orpheus, since he was banished from Hades. Legend has it that a charmed mirror, called the Mirror of Psyche,  which will show the face of one's true love. It is said to be buried somewhere deep in the Cave of Whispers. Find this mirror and bring it to Eurydice.
xtagxSQ15_Desc_B=Eurydice has been separated from her famed lover, the great musician Orpheus, since he was banished from Hades. With the help of the Mirror of Psyche, which will show the face of one's true love, she has seen that he is imprisoned and guarded deep within the earth. She has created a portal to this place and begged you to rescue him. Travel through the portal and find Orpheus.
xtagxSQ15_Desc_C=Eurydice has been separated from her famed lover, the great musician Orpheus, since he was banished from Hades. With the help of the Mirror of Psyche, which will show the face of one's true love, she saw that he is imprisoned and guarded deep within the earth. Eurydice created a portal to this place, allowing for his escape. Bring Orpheus safely back to Eurydice.
xtagxSQ15_Desc_D=Eurydice has been separated from her famed lover, the great musician Orpheus, since he was banished from Hades. With the help of the Mirror of Psyche, which will show the face of one's true love, she saw that he was imprisoned and guarded deep within the earth. Eurydice created a portal to the dungeon, allowing for his escape. The lovers are now re-united. Speak to Eurydice.
xtagxSQ15_Desc_E=Eurydice had been separated from her famed lover, the great musician Orpheus, since he was banished from Hades. With the help of the Mirror of Psyche, she saw that he is imprisoned and guarded deep within the earth, and then created a portal to the dungeon, allowing for his escape. The lovers are now re-united.
xtagxSQ16_Desc_A=Few shades on the Plains of Judgment can boast great deeds in life. Nevertheless, a few have organized and are quietly doing what they can against the daemon forces. In the City of Lost Souls, Callicrates says he knows of a shipment of valuable supplies that have stopped on the Salt Flats. He says that if these were destroyed, it would be a serious setback to the daemons. Find and destroy the caravans.
xtagxSQ16_Desc_B=Few shades on the Plains of Judgment can boast great deeds in life. Nevertheless, a few have organized and are quietly doing what they can against the daemon forces. In the City of Lost Souls, Callicrates told of a shipment of valuable supplies that have stopped on the Salt Flats. They have been destroyed, which hopefully will prove a serious setback to the daemons. Return to Callicrates.
xtagxSQ16_Desc_C=Few shades on the Plains of Judgment can boast great deeds in life. Nevertheless, a few have organized and are quietly doing what they can against the daemon forces. In the City of Lost Souls, Callicrates told of a shipment of valuable supplies that have stopped on the Salt Flats. They have been destroyed, which hopefully will prove a serious setback to the daemons.{^N}{^N}It sounds as if he might know of other missions of the same nature.
xtagxSQ16_Desc_D=A train of caravans were stopped on the Salt Flats on the Plains of Judgment. They were well defended, but easily destroyed. Would any shade in the City of Lost Souls know more about the caravans, or where they were destined? Ask about the caravans in the City of Lost Souls.
xtagxSQ17_Desc_A=The shades of these Plains are no heroes, but they are doing what they can against the daemon army. Callicrates says that someone named Keuthonymos is the mastermind behind these operations. To get in touch with him, it is necessary to talk to Pylades first. Find and speak with Pylades.
xtagxSQ17_Desc_B=The shades of these Plains are no heroes, but they are doing what they can against the daemon army. Someone named Keuthonymos is the mastermind behind these operations. Pylades says he can be found somewhere in the lower Daemon Camp, of all places. Look for Keuthonymos in the Daemon Camp.
xtagxSQ17_Desc_C=The shades of these Plains are no heroes, but they are doing what they can against the daemon army. Keuthonymos, the mastermind behind these operations, is himself a daemon! He seems willing enough to turn against his own kind. He says that an envoy with crucial information for the daemon vanguard will pass into the camp, coming from the Vale of Mourning. Intercept the envoy and take the message.
xtagxSQ17_Desc_D=The shades of these Plains are no heroes, but they are doing what they can against the daemon army. Keuthonymos, the mastermind behind these operations, is himself a daemon! He seems willing enough to turn against his own kind. He says that an envoy with crucial information for the daemon vanguard will pass into the camp, from the Vale of Mourning. Bring the intercepted message to Keuthonymos.
xtagxSQ17_Desc_E=The shades of these Plains are no heroes, but they are doing what they can against the daemon army. Keuthonymos, the mastermind behind these operations, is himself a daemon! He seems willing enough to turn against his own kind. With his help, and envoy bearing an important message for the daemon vanguard has been intercepted. Now much can be done to hinder the army’s movements. 
xtagxSQ18_Desc_A=Long ago, on the Plains of Judgment, Hades built the Necromanteion as the one temple and oracle for the dead. But daemons took it over, caging all the shades who served as priests. One of these, Oenobius, managed to escape. Find the Necromanteion and cleanse it of daemons.
xtagxSQ18_Desc_B=Long ago, on the Plains of Judgment, Hades built the Necromanteion as the one temple and oracle for the dead. But daemons took it over, caging all the shades who served as priests. It seems they were using the temple to house a Bone Scourge of enormous size and power. Help the imprisoned shades in the temple.
xtagxSQ18_Desc_C=Long ago, on the Plains of Judgment, Hades built the Necromanteion as the one temple and oracle for the dead. But daemons took it over, caging all the shades who served as priests. It seems they were using the temple to house a Bone Scourge, and were feeding shades to it, until it grew to enormous size and power. If the daemons had finished their plan, this beast would have been a true menace. The Necromanteion belongs to the rites of the dead once more.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_A=According to Aristonymus, the god Hades keeps his wealth in a treasury right in the City of Lost Souls. Though he may have been searching for centuries, Aristonymus has made little progress in unlocking Hades’ vault. Look for a  way into Hades’ Treasury.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_B=According to Aristonymus, the god Hades keeps his wealth in a treasury right in the City of Lost Souls. Though he may have been searching for centuries, Aristonymus has made little progress in unlocking Hades’ vault. A runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in the Treasury. There are four pillars… could there be four stones to match them? Find the other stones.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_C=According to Aristonymus, the god Hades keeps his wealth in a treasury right in the City of Lost Souls. Though he may have been searching for centuries, Aristonymus has made little progress in unlocking Hades’ vault. One runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in the Treasury, and sure enough, finding and placing the other three stones has opened the vault door! Enter Hades’ Vault.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_D=According to Aristonymus, the god Hades keeps his wealth in a treasury right in the City of Lost Souls. Though he may have been searching for centuries, Aristonymus has made little progress in unlocking Hades’ vault. One runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in the Treasury, and sure enough, finding and placing the other three stones has opened the vault door! The treasure room of the God of Wealth was rich, indeed.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_E=A runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in a vault in the City of Lost Souls. There are four pillars… could there be four stones to match them? Find the other stones.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_F=One runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in the vault in the City of Lost Souls, and sure enough, finding and placing the other three stones has opened the vault door! Enter the vault.
xtagxSQ19_Desc_G=One runed stone won from an empusa fit into one of the pillars in the vault in the City of Lost Souls, and sure enough, finding and placing the other three stones has opened the vault door! The treasure inside was rich indeed.
xtagxSQ20_Desc_A=Among shades imprisoned in the Daemon Camp was the lad Admetus. What twist of fate brought him here? Speak with Admetus.
xtagxSQ20_Desc_B=Among shades imprisoned in the Daemon Camp was the lad Admetus. After his death, he traveled to the Tower of Judgment to be judged, but daemons fill the tower, and shades may not enter. Denied the possibility of Elysium, Admetus has sworn to help other shades wherever he can, and finally earn his place in those hallowed fields. Admetus swears he will repay you for rescuing him.
xtagxSQ20_Desc_C=Among shades imprisoned in the Daemon Camp was the lad Admetus. After his death, he traveled to the Tower of Judgment to be judged, but daemons fill the tower, and shades could  not enter. Denied the possibility of Elysium, Admetus has sworn to help other shades wherever he can, and finally earn his place in those hallowed fields. Now he has unexpectedly appeared inside the Tower of Judgment. Speak with Admetus.
xtagxSQ20_Desc_D=Among shades imprisoned in the Daemon Camp was the lad Admetus. After his death, he traveled to the Tower of Judgment to be judged, but daemons fill the tower, and shades could  not enter. Denied the possibility of Elysium, Admetus has sworn to help other shades wherever he can, and finally earn his place in those hallowed fields. He has unexpectedly appeared inside the Tower of Judgment, opening a passage to valuable supplies. Hopefully he will make his rightful way to Elysium. Look for Admetus in Elysium.
xtagxSQ20_Desc_E=Among shades imprisoned in the Daemon Camp was the lad Admetus. After his death, he traveled to the Tower of Judgment to be judged, but daemons fill the tower, and shades could  not enter. Denied the possibility of Elysium, Admetus has sworn to help other shades wherever he can, and finally earn his place in those hallowed fields. He unexpectedly appeared inside the Tower of Judgment, opening a passage to valuable supplies, and then made his way to Elysium, taking his rightful place among the noble.
xtagxSQ21_Desc_A=Wise in battle, Nestor says a messenger must be dispatched to Ajax and his men. He would like you to escort the messenger. Speak to Nestor again to lead the messenger.
xtagxSQ21_Desc_B=Wise in battle, Nestor says a messenger must be dispatched to Ajax and his men, in the Delian Meadows. Lead the messenger to Ajax.
xtagxSQ21_Desc_C=Wise in battle, Nestor says a messenger must be dispatched to Ajax and his men, in the Delian Meadows. The messenger has fallen. Return to Nestor for another messenger.
xtagxSQ21_Desc_D=Wise in battle, Nestor dispatched messenger to Ajax and his men, under your escort. This mission was successful, and Ajax has heard the messenger. Speak with Ajax.
xtagxSQ21_Desc_E=Wise in battle, Nestor dispatched messenger to Ajax and his men, under your escort. This mission was successful, and Ajax has heard the messenger. It seems the news should help preserve the Elysian lines of battle.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_A=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass. He needs reinforcement, but Ajax cannot spare many men. Ajax's second in command, Idomeneus, can assign you the few he can spare. Speak with Idomeneus to collect the reinforcements.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_B=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass. He needs reinforcement, but Ajax cannot spare many men. Travel to the Achaean Pass and aid Menelaus.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_C=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could not spare many men. You have reached the Achaean pass. Menelaus appears to be wounded. Speak to Menelaus.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_D=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could not spare many men. Menelaus has been wounded, and needs your help in the defense. His men will fight as long as the flag stands aloft. Defend the flag in the Achaean Pass.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_E=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could not spare many men. Menelaus has been wounded, and needs your help in the defense. His men will fight as long as the flag stands aloft. You have weathered one attack. Defend the flag against the second wave.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_F=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could not spare many men. Menelaus has been wounded, and needs your help in the defense. His men will fight as long as the flag stands aloft. You have weathered two waves. Defend the flag against the final attack.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_G=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could not spare many men. Menelaus has been wounded, and needs your help in the defense. His men will fight as long as the flag stands aloft. It seems you have weathered all the daemon attacks. Speak with Menelaus.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_H=Menelaus’ men were vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could spare many men. With Menelaus wounded, it was up to you to help in the defense. The flag stood aloft, the men fought bravely, and it seems you have weathered all the daemon attacks. The Elysian Forces have held out against the Daemon onslaught.
xtagxSQ22_Desc_I=Menelaus’ men are vulnerable to a heavy beating from the daemon forces, in the critical Achaean Pass, but Ajax could spare many men. Menelaus has been wounded, and needs your help in the defense. The flag has fallen – the men will lose heart. Encouraged, the Daemon will send more troops. Speak to Menelaus to raise the flag again.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_A=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. He has bravely led his troops far behind enemy lines, only to be stopped by a massive gate. It seems the gate must be opened from the other side. Open the gate for Pyrrhus.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_B=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. With their way unblocked, they are well on their way. They have encountered fire ballistae on their route, and are disabling them. Help destroy the fire ballistae.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_C=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. With their way unblocked, they are well on their way. Among the fire ballistae they have found, one is turned backwards, and can be fired on the daemons below. Fire the ballista.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_D=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. With their way unblocked, they are well on their way.  The fire ballistae they encountered are taken care of. Lead them in the charge to their final destination.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_E=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. With their way unblocked, they are well on their way. Still more fire ballistae are placed above, on the height Pyrrhus is supposed to secure. Help destroy the ballistae.
xtagxSQ23_Desc_F=Pyrrhus was sent to claim the tactical Eronian Highlands, within Daemon territory. With your help, the way has been cleared, and Pyrrhus’ troops have taken out the many fire ballistae that would impede the main force’s advance. They will hold the point, awaiting reinforcements. This is a true victory for the heroes of Elysium.
xtagxSQ24_Desc_B=An intrepid band, led by Menestheus, has made its way into enemy territory to create a diversion, so that Odysseus would have time to do his work. Their plan is to attack a Melinoe Blood Queen, who has command of the area. Lead the charge against the melinoe’s camp.
xtagxSQ24_Desc_C=An intrepid band, led by Menestheus, has made its way into enemy territory to create a diversion, so that Odysseus would have time to do his work. Their plan to attack a Melinoe Blood Queen, who has command of the area, was a success – and a good diversion! Speak with Menestheus, again.
xtagxSQ24_Desc_D=An intrepid band, led by Menestheus, has made its way into enemy territory to create a diversion, so that Odysseus would have time to do his work. Their plan to attack a Melinoe Blood Queen, who has command of the area, was a success – and a good diversion! Menestheus was exultant in his thanks.
xtagxSQ25_Desc_A=The daemons have led siege striders out onto the Aneslasian battlefield, which are inflicting great casualties on the heroes. There are five striders on the field. Destroy the five siege striders in Aneslasia.
xtagxSQ25_Desc_B=The daemons have led siege striders out onto the Aneslasian battlefield, which are inflicting great casualties on the heroes. One has fallen! On to the others. Destroy the remaining siege striders in Aneslasia.
xtagxSQ25_Desc_C=The daemons had led siege striders out onto the Aneslasian battlefield, which were inflicting great casualties on the heroes. They have all been defeated. They will trouble the brave heroes in Aneslasia no more. Speak with Alcinous.
xtagxSQ25_Desc_D=The daemons had led siege striders out onto the Aneslasian battlefield, which were inflicting great casualties on the heroes. They have all been defeated. They will trouble the brave heroes in Aneslasia no more.
xtagxSQ26_Desc_A=The Elysian Heroes have learned that Hades created five crystal shards, so that he could control his troops outside of his realm, in the Living Lands. If these crystals, called the Shards of Erebus, were shattered, Hades would not dare lead his troops up above, for fear of losing control of them. Destroy the five Shards of Erebus.
xtagxSQ26_Desc_B=The Elysian Heroes learned that Hades created five crystal shards, so that he could control his troops outside of his realm, in the Living Lands. Now that these crystals, called the Shards of Erebus, have been shattered, Hades would not dare lead his troops up above, for fear of losing control of them.
xtagxSQ26_Desc_C=There are strange crystal shards in Hades' Palace. Dark magic visibly pulsed from them, and the daemons were fierce in their defense. Perhaps Odysseus or his men would know more about these crystals? Inquire about the crystals among Odysseus’ men.
xtagxSQ26_Desc_D=There were five strange crystal shards in Hades Palace. Dark magic visibly pulsed from them, and the daemons were fierce in their defense. Whatever their purpose, they are shattered now. Perhaps Odysseus or his men would know more about these crystals? Inquire about the crystals among Odysseys’ men.
xtagxSQ27_Desc_A=It seems that when the Judges refused to help Hades, he made high generals of three powerful machae patriarchs, imbuing them with some of his own godly powers. These three dread commanders dwell within his palace and could, possibly, lead his armies without him. Defeat Hades’ three high generals.
xtagxSQ27_Desc_B=It seems that when the Judges’ refused to help Hades, he made high generals of three powerful machae patriarchs, imbuing them with some of his own godly powers. These three dread commanders dwelled within his palace and could, possibly, have led his armies without him. They now lie slain, and will lead nothing among the living or the dead.
xtagxSQ27_Desc_C=A high general of Hades, a fearsome machae, walked within the halls of Hades’ Palace. No more – the general is slain. Is this the only such high commander? Surely Odysseus and his men would be glad to hear this news. Tell Odysseus’ men of the news.
xtagxSQ27_Desc_D=Three high generals of Hades, fearsome machae, walked within the halls of Hades’ Palace. No more – all three high generals are slain. Surely Odysseus and his men would be glad to hear this news. Tell Odysseys’ men of the news.
xtagLogScroll=Magical Scroll
xtagLogArcaneFormula=Arcane Formula
xtagLogStaff=Powerful Staff
xtagLogAttributeBonus=Attribute Bonus
xtagLogPrimaryAttributesPoints_4=+ 4 Points to Str/Int/Dex
xtagLogPrimaryAttributesPoints_6=+ 6 Points to Str/Int/Dex
xtagLogPrimaryAttributesPoints_8=+ 8 Points to Str/Int/Dex
xtagxSQ27RewardNormal=+5% Total Damage
xtagxSQ27RewardEpic=+5% Total Damage
xtagxSQ27RewardLegendary=+5% Total Damage
xtagxSQ05RewardNormal=+6 Str, +80 Health
xtagxSQ05RewardEpic=+8 Str, +150 Health
xtagxSQ05RewardLegendary=+10 Str, +200 Health
xtagMysteriousPortal=Mysterious Portal
xtagxQuestMonster26=Alcestis ~ Guardian of Flame
xtagxQuestMonster27=Metriche ~ Guardian of Frost
xtagxQuestMonster28=Erytheia ~ Guardian of Soul
xtagxQuestMonster29=Tisiphane ~ Guardian of Venom
xtagSecretKey=The Overlord
xtagSecretDoor=Overlord's Passage
