// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
//encoding = RAW

xtagTutorialTip01Title=Caravan Window
xtagTutorialTip01TextA=Use Caravans to store extra possessions. You can access your belongings at any Caravan Driver. Look for them in most major cities.
xtagTutorialTip01TextB=Click on Expand Storage to buy extra space.{^N}{^N}Click on the Transfer tab to share items with your other player characters.
xtagTutorialTip02Tile=Transferring Items
xtagTutorialTip02TextA=Items placed here are shared between all your current player characters.
xtagTutorialTip02TextB=To transfer items, just place them in the Transfer area. When you load another character, visit a Caravan Driver, and collect the desired items.
xtagTutorialTip02TextC=Note: to trade items with other player’s characters in multiplayer games, use the Trade feature instead.
xtagTutorialTip03Title=Enchanters
xtagTutorialTip03TextA=Charmed items are the specialty of Enchanters.
xtagTutorialTip03SubtitleA=Arcane Formulae and Artifacts
xtagTutorialTip03CaptionA=A Formula and an Artifact
xtagTutorialTip03TextB=The powerful magical items called Artifacts are made from Arcane Formulae. Bring a Formula and the required reagents to an Enchanter, to have it built into an Artifact.
xtagTutorialTip03SubtitleB=Altar of Separation
xtagTutorialTip03TextC=Allows Relics and Charms to be removed from items. Place an item with a Relic or Charm attached to it in the slot.{^N}{^N}You can only recover the item or the Relic.{^N}{^N}If you recover the Relic, the item will be lost. If you recover the item, the Relic will be lost.
xtagTutorialTip04Title=Arcane Formulae
xtagTutorialTip04TextA=When an Arcane Formula is placed in the Altar of Creation, the three required Reagents are shown beneath it. Reagents can be Relics, Charms, Scrolls, or other Artifacts. {^N}{^N}Details about the Artifact to be created, and the cost of creation, are shown when you mouse over the Formula.
xtagTutorialTip04SubtitleA=Making an Artifact
xtagTutorialTip04TextB=Place each reagent in its slot. When the three slots are filled, you are ready to build the Artifact by pressing Create Artifact. Your new Artifact will be placed in your inventory.
xtagTutorialTip05Title=Artifacts
xtagTutorialTip05TextA=Artifacts are powerful magical talismans that bestow unique powers on their owners.
xtagTutorialTip05TextB=Artifacts must be equipped. Place your Artifact in its slot, near your character's feet.
xtagTutorialTip05TextC=Lesser Artifacts grant unusual bonuses to your character. Greater and Divine Artifacts may also grant powerful passive skills.
xtagTutorialTip06Title=Scrolls
xtagTutorialTip06TextA=Scrolls contain powerful spells which can be used only once. When a Scroll is used, the ancient symbols vanish from the stretched hide on which they were scribed.
xtagTutorialTip06TextB=Mouse over Scrolls to find out what they do.
xtagTutorialTip06SubtitleA=Quick Casting
xtagTutorialTip06TextC=For handy use in the middle of combat, assign a Scroll to your Quickbar, the same way you would a Skill or Potions.
xtagTutorialTip07Title=Tombstones
xtagTutorialTip07TextA=A tombstone will appear where your hero died. If you return to the Tombstone and click on it, you will regain some of your lost Experience. 
